I grew up in the mountains
as a plainer than average girl.
But after I moved to the city,
I changed completely.
I let my hair down,
...and started wearing contacts for my...
Yep!
My fresh start in high school!
Problem?
Engaged to the Unidentified
asa me ga sametara mou
When I woke up this morning
kinou mitai na nichijou wa nakute
The everyday life I had was nowhere to be found
honto ah mou etto dou shiyou
Seriously, uh, what now?
tameiki majiri ni neru
In the midst of all the sighing
okashi to mousou no recipe no naka ni
I accidentally put in this recipe of sweets and delusions
koigokoro haichatta
A dash of love
chiffon cake ni custard
Chiffon cakes and custard
scone ni clotted cream
Along with some scones and clotted cream
But there really is something off about all this
dakedo yappa korette okashii wa
Why does it have to be me?
doushite watashi nan daro
How could you spring this on me?
kyuu ni sonna koto iidashite
ah dou shiyou
What am I ever to do?
kimi wo suki ni nacchau ka nante wakaranai kedo
I don't know if I'll fall for you
But you'll still be precious to me
taisetsu na hito da
nante ah terekusai kana
Gosh, that's a little embarrassing
kimi wa majime na tone de suki tte nante iu desho
You say you love me in the most serious tone
chotto dokitto shichau jan
That makes my heart skip a beat
nante hinichijouteki na revolution
And sparks an extraordinary revolution within me
Only a Sister Can Heal a Scar Left by a Sister
Are you sure?
Is Suetsugi-san really the same as you?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Hakuya said so too.
...Wow...
Are there, uh,
a lot of "people" like you?
Not really.
We're a rare bunch.
There aren't many mountains where
we can in live in hiding nowadays,
so there's probably a few who come down
to the cities to live amongst people.
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
Cities are definitely a fun place to live in!
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
All right, all right.
Investigation
No.1:
That's fine, but just sit
farther back from the TV, okay?
Investigation
No.1:
UFOs Exist!
You're of the same species,
but you don't know her, do you?
Not at all.
She probably lived somewhere else
with another group that we don't know.
So this was an unforeseen encounter, huh?
Yeah.
She didn't seem to be aware
that we were just like her, either.
At any rate, I feel sick to my stomach!
We may be of the same species, but I don't
think I'll ever be able to get along with her!
I guess the world's always been filled with
mysteries that I've never been aware of.
Right?
You think so too, right?
Like aliens and UMAs!
No, not that.
What's that?
What're you two talking about?
Oh, Nee-sama.
I probably shouldn't tell her that
Suetsugi-san is just like Mashiro and Hakuya.
I mean, they are in the
student council together.
What's wrong, Kobeni?
I-It's a secret!
"A secret"?
Kobeni's hiding something from me?
What, did your boobs get bigger again?
Didn't you measure in
last month at eighty—?
That's not it!
I have some things that I want
to keep to myself, you know!
Some things I can't
even tell you about!
How... How can this be?
How can this be?!
No! Is this her rebellious phase?!
No, it's not!
I'm so sad!
Only a sister can heal a scar left by a sister!
What kind of logic is that?!
My day was completely
ruined thanks to you!
That Suetsugi girl came complaining to me
about how I should address you as "Benio-sama"!
She did?
You were fighting over me?
Oh my.
I'm such a sinner.
Suetsugi Konoha!
Here I go!
Come to think of it, I've yelled
and screamed in front of her sister.
Benio-sama must've
heard about it by now.
How am I supposed to face her now?!
...Still, that darn pipsqueak...
Why does she get to take
b-ba-baths with Benio-sama?!
Anyhow, are those two
really of the same species as me?
...But that guy...
Well, those were a lot
of facial expressions.
Niko-chan!
...Konoha...
The investigation's just getting started.
I still need to get that
questionnaire back from Kobeni-chan.
...Uh, Niko-chan...
Maybe you should think of
another article to write, you know?
Oh, that reminds me.
Here are some new pictures of Benio-sama.
Want them?
Thanks a bunch!
I'm gonna head over to
the newspaper club room.
See ya.
Niko-chan!
Her sister?
...Um...
I won't tell anyone!
I'll, uh... keep it a secret.
So don't worry about it.
Bye!
Er, what?
Does that mean
what I think it means?
I won't tell anyone about your random
outbursts and complaining to Mashiro.
You'd better be thankful.
Ho
She's blackmailing me?!
We should keep it a secret, right?
Your mother said the same thing.
Hakuya, didn't you say that you
realized she was the same as you?
How did you figure it out?
Intuition... I guess?
...Intuition, huh...
Is a
bit
slow
Is a
bit
slow
Is really
What do I do?!
What on earth is Kobeni hiding?!
Why don't you ask her?
...I-It's just...
I dunno what I'd do if she started hating me
because I came on too strong to her.
Don't worry about that.
She already hates you.
Impossible!
Anyway, why isn't this surprising for you?
You and Kobeni are
basically sisters, you know.
Even sisters keep things from each other.
She's not a child, you know.
And if that's not the case, then maybe
she just got sick of you and your clinginess.
Kobeni? Sick of me?
Please, like that'd ever happen.
What's with that confidence?
...A secret... What could it be...
She was talking about
something with Mashiro-tan.
Are they planning some sort
of surprise party for me?!
You're way too optimistic.
Montly Financial Report
The 2014 Fiscal Year
Club Activities Funding
Montly Financial Report
The 2014 Fiscal Year
Club Activities Funding
Montly Financial Report
The 2014 Fiscal Year
Club Activities Funding
Montly Financial Report
Let's see.
Club Activities Funding
The 2014 Fiscal Year
Montly Financial Report
Club Activities Funding
She's hiding something
...from her older sister...
Maybe it's a guy?
Huh?
Kobeni was a guy this whole time?!
Nee-sama.
Nee-sama
So she's actually my brother?!
What's wrong with you?
Kobeni's my little brother?
A guy?
Come to think of it, we haven't
...taken a bath together lately...
But how do you explain those
two large mounds on her chest?
They're proof she can do everything.
There's no way she's a guy.
No way at all.
But wait, what if she's
actually intersexed?!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaargh
It's fine by me! I can accept it!
That's not what I meant.
It might be about a boyfriend.
I mean, she's got a fiancé and all.
What about that would
she be hiding from me, though?
Don't tell me she crossed the line?!
That's not what I said.
Did they hold hands?!
Let them. What's the big deal?
But even I haven't
held hands with her lately!
Who holds hands with their sister?
At any rate, you should know
that she won't tell you everything.
It's not like you tell her
everything either, right?
...Well...
She'd be creeped out if I did.
Wow. You actually do realize it.
S-Sorry I'm late.
mumble grumble
Mumble grumble.
This has to be some kind of mistake.
mumble grumble
Uh, Benio-sama,
How could my beloved, oh-so-adorable
Kobeni hide something from me?
is something wrong?
Oh my god!
She's lamenting the state of the world.
There's no way this is possible.
Benio-sama!
Hnnnnnnnng!
Taiyaki
This is great.
And I passed my make-up exams.
I couldn't be happier!
Salisbury steak
Chestnut red bean paste
Cream-filled
Red beans (Dumplings)
Red beans
Peach
Menu
Okonomiyaki
Curry
Pizza
Chocolate
Cinnamon
What?
Why are there so many types of taiyaki?
Which should I get?
...Er...
I wanna know how the
peach-filled taiyaki tastes,
...but maybe I should play it safe...
...But they do have cream-filled...
And chestnut red bean-filled. And chocolate-filled too!
Wait, they have okonomiyaki-filled too?!
O-One red bean-flavored taiyaki, please.
Mashiro-chan, you're panting.
Do you want anything, Hakuya?
I'll pass.
You sure?
...All right...
I guess I'll have the
red bean-filled one too.
It seems low on calories.
Wait, what?
It's got 300 kcal?
...Why did I look...
Here.
You can have half of mine.
What's this?
You two are getting along really well.
Huh?
No, it's not like that at all.
I like the okonomiyaki-filled one.
It's basically like having a meal.
Huh?
What?
I was wondering if you'd
filled out that questionnaire.
Oh, no. Not yet. Sorry.
Oh, okay.
See you later, then.
Her again?
I guess it's partially my fault
for not turning her down.
Damn it!
Do they fit?
...Well...
If I use waist size, then it's
too tight around my hips.
Why don't you get
something elastic?
I-I'll be relying on those in
the future, so I'll pass for now.
Oh, yeah. I get it. The elastic stuff
is pretty popular with the older ladies.
For Ladies
Shh! Quiet!
I see.
So Kobeni-chan's conscious of her big butt.
Hey.
Wh-What?
Look, I-I just happened
...to be shopping here too.
Her having a big butt
isn't a bad thing.
I didn't say her having
a big butt is a bad thing!
What are you two talking about?!
Oono-san,
Kobeni-chan doesn't like articles
being written about her.
She'd really appreciate it
if you'd stop with this.
Oh, really?
Sorry for all this! Forget about it!
Bye.
That was easy!
She really is a perfect fit for the
newspaper club with all that enthusiasm.
I'm sorry.
You had to say it for me
...because I couldn't...
Oh, it's okay.
Oono-san's the type of person who
needs to be told something straight up.
You're surprisingly capable
of telling it like it is, Mayura.
What?
I can be pretty blunt, you know.
Bam!!
This is a pen!
Is this a big rack?
Yes, it is a big rack.
What are you talking about?
It's not a bad thing.
Just stop!
Aw, I got yelled at.
I guess I can't tackle this head-on.
But that isn't enough to make a
capable reporter like me give up!
Oh, right.
I should let Konoha know.
Kobeni's an angel!
This has got to be a lie.
Oh, excuse me.
Hello? Niko-chan?
Hey, it looks like Kobeni-chan,
Benio-sama's sister,
is conscious of her big butt!
Hey!
E-Excuse me.
I'll make sure to keep you in the loop!
Gotta go!
Wh-What the heck?
Her sister has a big butt?
What is she talking about?
Oh, I guess she is pretty big all over.
On the other hand, my chest
and butt are slim and slender!
I've never once had to
worry about getting too fat!
But if you were to ask
...if that makes me happy...
then I'd have to say, no, it doesn't.
Engaged to the
Unidentified
★
Why can't you and Suetsugi-san get along?
Huh?
You two are the same, right?
You had the good fortune
of meeting one of your own,
so you should try to be friends with her.
No way.
She called me an idiot.
And besides that, she's one of Benio's fans.
Oh, so that's the key factor.
So first off, I need to find out if
those two really are the same as me.
Niko-chan may have fallen for their tricks,
but they won't work on me!
Wait, are they staying with Benio
because they're actually after her?
Maybe she's been tricked too!
D-Damn, I should've
thought of that first!
I'm done taking out the trash.
Good work.
I saw Suetsugi-san out in the hallway.
I wonder if she's looking for someone.
Suetsugi-san?
...Together with Benio-sama...
...Th-This isn't what it looks like! It's, er...
Wh-What's with that look?
Anyway, perfect timing.
We need to talk.
Fine.
How's the roof sound?
Should I come too?
Can't
be too
pushy
Can't
be too
pushy
Oh, no. I just want a
moment with her alone.
Let's go.
Okay.
Are they going to be okay?
Huh? Are they friends?
She and Mashiro-chan seem
a bit different from normal folk.
Despite her calm demeanor,
Mayura is actually pretty sharp,
...so she might have already figured it out...
But there's a limit to how sharp she can be.
Not like I can ask her about it, though.
I'd just be digging my own grave.
I guess so!
It really does seem that way!
AHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAH
Right?
I'll go check on them.
Wait, but she told me not to come.
...And you shouldn't sneak up on people...
It's fine.
They won't see me.
He's so confident!
You darn pipsqueak!
Don't call me that!
I'm not a child!
Hm? Why are those two fighting?
...Wait...
Are they are fighting over me?!
Hurry up and get
back to work already.
I know I said I was fine with the roof,
but it's way too windy up here!
I-It's so cold!
We have a load of
paperwork to go over.
You'd better sort it all out, and quick.
Where do you think you're going?
It's not like I'm going to see what
Mashiro-tan and Suetsugi are up to, okay?
It sure seems that way, though.
I'm just going to recover a party
that got wiped out in a dungeon.
Is that the best you can come up with?
Wanna go somewhere else?
Let's go somewhere else!
All right.
The first place that comes to mind when
calling someone out is the back of the gym!
Fine by me.
Mashiro-tan! Suetsugi!
Huh? They're not here.
How come?
So we really are the same.
Looks like it.
Anyway, I can't believe you.
We may be of the same species,
but how dare you just sneak into
Benio-sama's home like that?!
Mashiro-chan and Hakuya-kun
sure are taking their time.
Yeah.
Mayura, go home without us.
I kinda wanna see
what's going on, after all.
Kobeni-chan?
Judging by how things have gone
so far, I can't see this ending well.
What if Hakuya gets caught up
in it and things get all messy?
Oh, Kobeni!
Nee-sama?
Kobeni!
She's so far.
Hey, I saw Mashiro-tan
and Suetsugi together earlier.
What happened?
Do you know anything?
Huh?
What now?
I need to avoid spilling anything.
It has nothing to do with you!
Nothing to do with you!
With you!
O-Oh... I-Is that s-so?
Yep!
It has absolutely nothing to do with you!
Bye!
Shall we head back now,
Ms. Total Outsider Benio-sama?
Huh? They're not here.
Where's Hakuya?
Mashiro?
Hey, c-cut it out!
It's unfair to just start crying!
But Benio had absolutely nothing to do with it!
Th-That's pretty rude in itself!
"Nothing to do with me"?
That can't be true.
My seventh sense says so!
mumble
grumble
Yeah. There's no way that's true.
mumble
grumble
Nope. No way. No way in hell.
Yeah, sure. Now can you go
through these papers already,
I mean, I'm her sister!
O' Great Benio-sama
with the seven senses?
What's wrong, Mashiro?
Hakuya!
Want some chocolate?
I do!
You baby!
What did you do to her?
All I said was it isn't fair that
she gets to live with Benio-sama!
What the heck is this?
You're making me
look like the bad one.
Wait, don't tell me
you're after Benio-sama too?!
Mashiro
No!
Hakuya?! Are you okay?
What, was I right?
So you did come here for Benio-sama.
And you even used your powers
...to live with her! I'm so envi—
Wait, that's not it.
You're playing dirty!
Seriously, why would you
jump to that conclusion?
I only came here because
I was worried about Hakuya!
Hakuya didn't come
here for Benio either!
Really?
Really!
I feel so bad for you.
You don't realize how
wonderful Benio-sama is yet.
Wait, what?
What on Earth are you talking about?
But that's good, though.
...If you're not interested in Benio-sama...
You're kinda absentminded
...and not really my type of guy...
That's rude!
What is with you?
...My mom told me...
Huh?
"You won't meet one
of our males very often,
so if you do, make sure
to call dibs on him."
Dibs?
Oh, there they are.
Hakuya even said
he wouldn't be spotted.
You there.
Marry me.
Yes, curry is my favorite
sou desu curry wa daikoubutsu desu
But if I may be a bit greedy
tada yoku wo iwasete moraereba
You prefer it mild, don't you?
amakuchi ga iindeshou
Oh, but sticky food is fine by me too
mou nebaneba datte mo mochiron
zenzen heiki de taberaremasu
I can eat it, no problem
nigate nan dana
You don't like it, do you?
mou mitame wa chokotto chikkoi desu ga
Sure, I may look a bit on the smaller side
kore demo shikkari kojuuto datte shimasu
But I'm a proper sister-in-law
senobi shicchatte (yes!)
Look at you, pushing yourself (Yes!)
ryouri mo souji mo sentaku mo daijoubu desu
You can handle cooking, cleaning, and laundry just fine
sore ni anzangata desushi
And you've got great child-bearing hips
ki ni shiteru noni
Hey, I'm conscious of that
ie de wa annani annan nanoni
You're so crazy at home
Did you brainwash the people at school?
ittai douiu sennoujutsu desu ka
shitto shichatte mou (more!)
Aww, don't be jealous (More!)
shinpai da toka riyuu wo tsukete
We make excuses, saying we're worried about you
chakkari to ima sennyuu seikou
And now we've finally snuck into your heart
nakayoku nattara
Once we get close to each other
uchiakenakya demo
And we have to be frank
Will we still be able to understand
aimai na koto
What's left unsaid?
rikai dekiru kana
sorya maa oyatsu toka
My love for snacks and other things
May make me seem childish
kodomoppoi desu ga
sore demo zutto nakayokushite kuremasuka
But will you still be my friend forever?
This is an E cup!
This is an E cup.
Nah,
it's
-actu-
ally
an F
cup.
This
is an
E cup.
What're
you two
talking
about?!
Nah, it's actually an F cup.
What are you two talking about?!
F?
What?!
G
?
F
G?
What?!
This
is a
-rom-
-com!
Next time: This is a Disgrace; I've Been Shamed.
Next Time
This is a Disgrace; I've Been Shamed
This is a romcom!