...Jeez...
What should I do?
...Maybe I should apologize to Hakuya...
Hakuya dove after you,
resulting in you both getting hurt.
...Wait...
Maybe I should thank him first
since he saved me?
Despite being really badly hurt himself.
It might be a bit rude,
considering I don't remember any of it.
Oh, it's this late already?
Huh?
...Wait...
What?
Engaged to the Unidentified
asa me ga sametara mou
When I woke up this morning
kinou mitai na nichijou wa nakute
The everyday life I had was nowhere to be found
Seriously, uh, what now?
hontou ah mou etto dou shiyou
tameiki majiriau
In the midst of all the sighing
I accidentally put in this recipe of sweets and delusions
okashi to mousou no recipe no naka ni
koigokoro haichatta
A dash of love
chiffon cake ni custard
Chiffon cakes and custard
Along with some scones and clotted cream
scone ni clotted cream
But there really is something off about all this
dakedo yappa korette okashii wa
Why does it have to be me?
doushite watashi nan darou
How could you spring this on me?
kyuu ni sonna koto iidashite
What am I ever to do?
ah dou shiyou
kimi wo suki ni nacchau ka nante wakaranai kedo
I don't know if I'll fall for you
But you'll still be a precious gift to me
taisetsu na gift da
Gosh, that's a little embarrassing
nante ah terekusai kana
kimi wa majime na ko de suki tte nante iu deshou
I bet you'd say you love me and all my honesty
That makes my heart skip a beat
chotto dokitto shichau zo
nante himitsu jouteki na revolution
And sparks a secret emotional revolution within me
She's Just a Pervert
Huh?
Kobeni's sick?
Does she have a cold or something?
She has a very weak body,
so this happens every now and then.
I see.
She's probably still in shock since
I told her about the time Hakuya-kun saved her.
Maybe it was too much to take in?
...I see...
Huh?
What?!
What have you done?!
Oh, come on!
Even I wouldn't be so mean as to
ask her to sleep with me when she's sick.
What were you planning to do?
Tee-hee.
...I have to cook...
Hakuya said he doesn't mind
if she doesn't remember!
Besides, why did you
wait until now to tell her?!
I just didn't want to tell her.
I thought it was better that
she'd forgotten all about it.
And why's that?
Because, on that day,
I was supposed to accompany Grandpa.
But I wanted to play with my friends,
so I suggested he take Kobeni instead.
It's all my fault.
That's why I didn't want to tell her.
Aren't I the worst?
It's not your fault, Nee-sama.
Kobeni!
It wasn't anyone's fault.
...If only I...
...Oh, right...
Hakuya got hurt because of me.
And then I forgot all about it
and was rude to him.
I'm sorry that I'm such
a terrible sister, Kobeni!
Go ahead and hit me if you want.
Nice and hard, now!
Hey, Kobeni!
Are you okay?
...Wha—?
You told Kobeni?
Yeah!
Benio wasn't thinking
and spilled the beans to her.
And now look, Kobeni's sick!
I guess it really was
...too much to take in...
To be honest, I thought you guys
would've told her by now.
...W-Well...
Hakuya told me not to tell her.
So, what is this?
My all-out critical hit creation:
The Benio Special!
Actually... that's not
what we wanted to know.
It's my fault that Kobeni got a fever,
so I felt like I needed to
make up for her absence.
But I was so, so worried about her!
And here we are.
Can't we have Akane-san cook?
Mom's too busy to cook.
She also said she couldn't make it home tonight
due to some emergency calls she got.
I never realized
what I had until I lost you!
I-I'm not dead.
...Hey...
I'm sorry I forgot about it.
...I'm such a...
What? Oh no!
Don't start crying on me now!
What's Hakuya doing?
He seems a bit down in the dumps.
I love my little sister more than anything,
but she was always by my side.
And, because I was older,
I'd have to look after her.
Sometimes, I just wanted
to play with my friends.
Hey, Grandpa!
Why don't you take Kobeni along today?
I was too careless back then.
It's all my fault.
I want to go back in time
and punch myself.
Maybe I should squeeze myself
into my desk drawer?
Where did that come from?
I see.
So you finally told her.
I don't think that Kobeni blames you,
and I think you should
stop beating yourself up over it.
Don't you think it's time to let it go?
Oh, and since we're on
...the subject of your sister...
Even if you take what
happened into account,
I think your love for your
sister's a bit excessive.
You think?
I have no idea how to face Hakuya.
I can't even think straight with this fever.
My body's burning up,
but I still feel a chill spreading out.
When was it, again?
...Oh, I remember this...
...But wait, back then...
there was something
warm and fluffy next to me.
Is Kobeni still sick?
It seems like she's
going to take today off too.
I'll stay home too, then.
Huh?
We can't leave Kobeni alone.
It's too risky.
Listen to yourself!
It's more risky for two engaged minors
to spend a day all alone!
What about me?
It's too risky for me to go to school with Benio
if you two aren't going to be there!
Why would it be risky
if I were alone with Kobeni?
Well, why wouldn't it be?
I don't care if you're engaged, I can't have
you doing something indecent with my sister!
What do you mean?
Kobeni's going to stay pure
until she gets married, all right?!
Well, obviously.
What's so obvious about it?
Now I'm more worried about
a teenager not thinking about that!
Thinking about what?
Nothing!
...We're, uh...
We're talking about cabbages.
Oh.
Yeah, I heard they're
good for tummy aches.
Wait, don't tell me Kobeni
has a weak tummy too!
This is too much.
How can she be this cute?
And, with that said, I've decided
that I will be staying home today.
So you two don't have
anything to worry about!
Would you just shut up
and go to school already?!
Kobeni yelled at me!
I could hear her all the way from here.
That was scary!
Oh well.
We should leave now
if we want to make it in time.
Come on, Hakuya.
Do you want Kobeni to yell at you too?
Kobeni-chan's not coming in today?
No, she's not.
I had no idea that
her body was that weak.
This has happened every
so often for years now.
It made it so that she couldn't
join us for field trips and such.
I felt so bad for her.
I wonder if she
wore herself out this time.
That was pretty loud.
Didn't you have breakfast?
I haven't had anything
since last night.
Here.
Thank you!
Is Hakuya-kun depressed
because Kobeni-chan's absent?
My fever isn't going down.
And I'm drenched in sweat.
...I'm so thirsty...
I want some water,
...but I don't want to get up...
This sucks.
No matter how old I get,
I can never get used to
being alone like this.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I wake you up?
You're back already?
It's past three now.
Hakuya and I rushed back home.
Hakuya's back too?
I'll wipe you off.
Can you get up?
Yeah.
See that scar?
I'd forgotten all about it.
I got this back when
Hakuya saved me, right?
Do you really not remember
getting hurt at all?
Well, I was really young back then,
and apparently, I was
unconscious for an entire month.
Did that happen to Hakuya too?
I don't know.
No one's told me the
whole story yet, either.
Is that why Nee-sama is so protective of me?
She's just a pervert.
Where's Nee-sama?
She had some student council work
that she couldn't sneak away from.
She said to text her once we were done.
Sub: How's the fever?
Inbox
Yonomori Benio
Sub: Is there anything you want?
Sub: Are you okay?
Yonomori Benio
Edit
Mailboxes
Sent
Inbox
I have 85 new messages?
She wasn't her usual self without
you around. It was a huge relief!
Sorry, I think I'll go
back to sleep for a while.
Don't worry about it.
Bye.
...Oh...
You kept reminding me of something,
...but I couldn't put my finger on it...
...A dog...
...A large dog...
O-Oh, she was talking in her sleep?
Anyway, how can she be that
voluptuous even when lying face up?
Isn't it hard to handle?
Good morning.
Are you feeling better?
You don't look too good.
No, I'm fine now.
Sorry to cause you all that trouble.
I see.
Glad to hear it.
What are you doing?
...Well, I think you look pretty cute, so...
Oh, Kobeni!
Are you feeling better?
Oh no.
What should I do?
How should I face him?
Kobeni doesn't
...want to look at me...
...She's crying...
Hakuya, don't!
Huh?
What?
Engaged to the
Unidentified
★
Wait up, Hakuya!
That was the sound of him hitting
his pinky toe on the wall, staggering,
falling by the entrance, running into
the umbrella stand, and then leaving.
Wh-What the heck?
Wasn't it a bit weird?
Like, the way he just took off.
What do you mean?
Everyone back home is like that.
Living in the mountains
really strengthens our lower body.
That was on a whole
different level, though.
Maybe you're just going blind, Benio!
Th-That's not the issue here!
...Huh? Er, uh...
You're right!
What now? We need to get to school!
We need to go find him!
Kobeni's pretty diligent, huh?
Don'tcha think it's cute?
...Oh no...
What have I done?
It's all my fault again.
I hurt him!
...She hates me...
She thinks I'm just an annoyance
now that she knows about the injury.
Mommy!
Hurry up!
W-We're so sorry!
There he is!
Hakuya!
W-Wait... up!
...S-Sorry...
About the injury?
Y-Yeah.
I'm sorry.
If only I'd kept an eye on you,
you wouldn't have gotten hurt.
What?
I-I'm the one who
should be apologizing!
You got hurt because of me.
Well, I don't really
...remember what happened...
No, it was my fault.
It was mine!
Mine!
Whoa! We're late!
Hey, so, uh...
This might come off a bit rude,
considering I don't remember any of it,
but the only reason I'm
standing here is thanks to you,
so I figured I should th-thank you.
I just didn't know how to face you.
So, uh, I'm sorry about earlier.
O-Oh, and since we're
not getting anywhere,
let's just call it even for now.
I-Is that okay?
Yeah.
A-Anyway, let's get going!
We've gotta get to school!
Hopefully we'll make it
in time for second period.
S-So he can smile.
That was the first time
I've seen him do it.
Benio-sama!
Are you all right?!
Don't tell me you're not feeling well!
Are you ill?!
Thank you.
I'm fine.
...N-Not this again...
...I feel like puking...
This can only mean one thing:
a romcom scene!
Yeah, this is kind of its own disease.
Oh, did you find Hakuya?
H-He was over by the park.
Don't worry about school, by the way.
I pulled some strings and turned
first period into study hall.
Oh, that's a relief.
Wait, what do you mean by,
"pulled some strings"?
Oh, don't worry about it.
It's nothing important.
Anyway, I have to say,
you sure can run fast, Hakuya.
Yeah, that's right.
He's super fast.
He crossed mountains and valleys
to get to this town too.
Wait, I thought you came by train?
O-Of course we did!
W-We went on tons of buses
and trains to get here!
Do you even need to ask?
Are you feeling better, Kobeni-chan?
Yeah.
Sorry to worry you.
Your cheeks are still a bit red.
Are you sure you're feeling better?
Huh?
No, no!
I'm fine!
Sick bag
Did something happen?
Did they raise some flags or something?!
Benio-sama,
are you okay in the head?
Oh, so Hakuya-kun saved your life?
Yeah.
I don't really remember it, though.
Wow.
You know what this means, don't you?
It means you two must be soulmates!
Huh?
I mean, this doesn't happen all the time.
It'd actually be strange
if you weren't soulmates.
I bet you're made for each other!
It might just be my
sixth sense talking, though!
Sixth sense?!
Anyway, I've thought about this a lot,
and I think I should try to
get to know him a little better.
Really?
Well, good luck.
B-But I have no clue how to do it.
Huh?
I'll go ask for you, then.
Hakuya-kun, Hakuya-kun.
Um, what do you like?
Kobeni.
Oho?
Now wasn't that sweet.
Um, I'm glad you liked it.
D-Don't just blurt it out like that!
But she asked me what I liked.
Stop looking like an abandoned puppy!
Huh?
I can't really tell the difference
between his expressions.
It's pretty hard to tell, really.
To be honest, I don't
get around 80% of it either.
For his little sister,
that's a pretty terrible percentage.
But I'm surprised you can
read his expressions now.
You two sure are
getting closer, aren't you?
What?!
What the heck?!
That's too blunt!
That's not helping!
What is this, a two-man play?
I have no idea what you're doing.
No!
If you don't like it, I'll stop.
Please do!
Oh, come on!
What am I supposed to do?!
All I see is Hakuya-kun
spacing out like he always does.
What is this feeling?
...If I had to describe it...
Oh! It's like watching a dog
who was all excited to go outside,
but then got really depressed
when told to watch the house instead!
...I'm not too sure I understand...
Anyway, Hakuya can't
go on without you, Kobeni!
Is it because he feels
responsible for her getting hurt?
Well, I can't really say much right now,
but we were raised
deep in the mountains.
Kobeni was the first person
Hakuya met who was his age.
So he loves you!
What the heck is that? Imprinting?
Like I said, it's complicated!
But one thing's for sure:
it has to be you!
We've got plenty of
family issues to deal with too!
I don't know what I'd do
...if Hakuya didn't have you...
If the engagement were broken,
then he'd be single for the rest of his life!
He'll die alone!
Hey, don't cry!
Why are you threatening me?
Student Council Office
So yeah, he can run fast,
but can that alone really make
his movements look like that?
Well, I didn't have my
glasses on at the time either.
What's up?
I don't think asking you
would help me at all,
but do you think I look better
with or without glasses?
I honestly couldn't care less.
You probably shouldn't
interfere with Kobeni too much.
And why's that?
She's not a kid anymore,
so she'll just end up hating you
if you keep meddling in her affairs.
You know, kind of like how
girls tend to hate their fathers.
I'm a girl too, you know!
Besides, Kobeni wouldn't grow
to hate me over something like that.
I guess,
but it never hurts to be careful.
It has nothing to do with you!
Leave me alone!
I don't want my laundry done with yours!
Separate them!
No!
It might be a good thing in its own right!
You're rotten to the core.
That smells great.
Your cooking really is the best, Kobeni.
You're exaggerating.
Do you know what Hakuya
and Mashiro's hometown is like?
I hear it's pretty far up the mountains.
I don't know much.
I was pretty young back then too.
I wonder what the
Mitsumine house is like.
She found out about the injury,
but things haven't really gone downhill.
Isn't that great?
But... what about our family?
I don't know when to tell her
about the Mitsumine family.
You two need to get closer for that.
I don't think she'd
understand otherwise.
We're rather half-assed beings, after all.
It's another letter from home.
"We'll send someone over soon
...to see how it's going."
Oh?
Wait, what?
Yes, curry is my favorite
sou desu curry wa daikoubutsu desu
tada yoku wo iwasete moraereba
But if I may be a bit greedy
You prefer it mild, don't you?
amakuchi ga iindeshou
mou nebaneba nattou mo mochiron
Oh, but sticky natto is fine by me too
I can eat it, no problem
zenzen heiki de taberaremasu
nigate nan dana
You don't like it, do you?
Sure, I may look a bit on the smaller side
mou mitame wa chokotto chikkoi desu ga
kore demo shikkari kojuuto dattari shimasu
But I'm a proper sister-in-law
Look at you, pushing yourself (Yes!)
senobi shichatte (yes!)
You can handle cooking, cleaning, and laundry just fine
ryouri mo souji mo sentaku mo daijoubu desu
Plus you have some great child bearing hips
soreni anzangata desu
Hey, I'm conscious of that
ki ni shiteru noni
You're so crazy at home
ie de wa annani annan nanoni
ittai douiu sennoujutsu desu ka
Did you brainwash the people at school?
Aww, don't be jealous (Wow!)
shitto shichattemo (wow!)
shinpai da toka riyuu wo tsukete
We make excuses, saying we're worried about you
chakkari to ima senyuu seikou
And now we have exclusive possession of you
Once we get close to each other
And can't be frank anymore
mo
tte
ccha
Will we still be able to understand
What's left unsaid?
My love for snacks and other things
May make me seem childish
But will you still be my friend forever?
That way,
it'll put
a stop
to these
feelings.
I'll go
back in
time
and
punch
myself...
...I'll go back in time and punch myself...
That way, it'll put a stop to these feelings.
Ahhh!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's your Onee-tama, Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
It's
your
Onee-tama,
Kobeni!
Next Time
She's Given Birth
Next Time: She's Given Birth.