Oh, you put them on display.
Yeah. I haven't collected
them all, though.
You know how you guys
can transform at will?
Wouldn't that make you
some sort of UMA?
What?!
Don't lump us together.
Huh?
UMAs and UFOs are
unidentified and unconfirmed.
Unidentified
We're nothing like them.
How, exactly?
...Well, uh...
They're them, and we're us.
When I woke up this morning
asa me ga sametara mou
The everyday life I had was nowhere to be found
kinou mitai na nichijou wa nakute
Seriously, uh, what now?
honto ah mou etto dou shiyou
tameiki majiri ni neru
In the midst of all the sighing
I accidentally put in this recipe of sweets and delusions
okashi to mousou no recipe no naka ni
A dash of love
koigokoro haichatta
chiffon cake ni custard
Chiffon cakes and custard
scone ni clotted cream
Along with some scones and clotted cream
dakedo yappa korette okashii wa
But there really is something off about all this
Why does it have to be me?
doushite watashi nan daro
How could you spring this on me?
kyuu ni sonna koto iidashite
ah dou shiyou
What am I ever to do?
kimi wo suki ni nacchau ka nante wakaranai kedo
I don't know if I'll fall for you
taisetsu na hito da
But you'll still be precious to me
nante ah terekusai kana
Gosh, that's a little embarrassing
kimi wa majime na tone de suki tte nante iu desho
You say you love me in the most serious tone
chotto dokitto shichau jan
That makes my heart skip a beat
And sparks an extraordinary revolution within me
nante hinichijouteki na revolution
They're Them, and We're Us
All right.
Those in the back, please collect the
papers and bring them to my desk.
...We're finally done with finals...
They were a bit tough this time around.
Yeah. Hopefully I don't have to
take any make-up exams.
There, there.
Let's stop crying over spilled milk
and have a party today.
What a great idea!
Why don't you come to the student council's
office after school today to have some tea?
It's Benio-sama!
We have delicious tarts too.
Ta-Tarts?
Our secretary baked some.
President!
Oh, Suetsugi.
I've prepared the documents
you asked for the other day.
That was fast.
Thank you.
It must've been difficult having to
get them done during finals week.
No, it wasn't.
I'd do anything to help you.
Who's that?
Suetsugi Konoha-chan
from the class next door.
She's the student council secretary
that Benio-san was just talking about.
I hear she's a really nice and smart girl.
I see.
Wh-What was that?
Oh, wow.
All right, then, President.
I'm going to head back to class.
Okay.
Good work.
Bye-bye, Suetsugi-san.
Stop by any time!
I'm so pissed off!
It was back when I had just moved here.
What's wrong?
Do you need help with anything?
...Well, mah...
I mean, I'm new here,
so I kinda got lost.
Do you know where you're going?
If you have an address,
I could take you there.
That's when I decided to
go to the same school as her.
I used her uniform to identify it,
and after studying my hardest,
passed the entrance exams with flying colors.
...And yet...
I'm so happy that you're
attending the same school as me.
...And yet...
Nobody told me she had a little sister!
And what's with those breasts?!
I wanted to be Benio-sama's little sister!
...Well, I can accept her having a sister...
But who the heck's that pint-sized pipsqueak
and where did she come from?!
She's trying to steal Benio-sama from me!
Talk about an eyesore!
Eek!
Ko-Kobeni!
What?
Huh?
Th-There was something there!
W-Was it an alien?!
A spirit?
A ghost?!
Who're you calling a ghost?!
Konoha.
Niko-chan!
What's with that scary look?
Don't make me take a picture
and put it in the newspaper.
I'm serious!
There really was something there!
It's not fair that they get special treatment
just because they're related to Benio-sama.
Oh, Benio-sama's little sister
and her relative?
Especially that pipsqueak!
She gets fawned upon
because she's a child!
It's like a travesty!
Let me do some research on them.
You want to know
more about them, right?
It could make for an interesting article
in the school newspaper too.
...Y-You don't have to go that far...
I'm telling the truth!
There was something crazy there!
I bet it was a monster!
Maybe a demon!
Fine.
Get me something that I can
use to blackmail her with!
Gotcha!
I'll see if I can find something on the sly.
You're collecting data
for the school newspaper?
Yep!
I want to put together a
special edition on Benio-sama's sister.
N-No, don't do that!
Unlike Nee-sama, I'm a very boring person.
Don't say that!
You're sister to the Benio-sama!
...Everyone's interested—
No, really!
I-I'm not interested in that stuff.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Me too.
I didn't mean to be rude.
I'll just do a profile article, then.
Here's a questionnaire.
Fill it out for me, 'kay?
H-Hang on!
The student council president's sister, huh?
Do you hate being compared?
I-It's not like that.
I just don't like being
the center of attention.
I'd only end up
disappointing people, anyway.
What do you mean?
Oh, nothing.
This used to happen a lot,
so it doesn't bother me anymore.
"When bathing,
which body part do you wash first?"
"Where are you ticklish?"
What's with these questions?!
I can't believe I let myself get carried
away and make such a silly request.
I wonder if Niko-chan's going to be all right.
She said she'd try and
...find something on the sly...
Say cheese.
What was that for?!
...You seem to be close to Benio-sama...
What kind of relationship
do you two have?
Oh, and be sure to tell me
if you have any weaknesses.
Wh-What do you mean, "relationship"?
We don't have a relationship!
You two seem to
get along well, though.
No, we don't!
Things are really getting out of hand!
This was your doing?!
How dare you!
You're fired!
P-Please forgive me, Benio-sama!
...It's obvious that we don't—
Huh? Where'd Oono-san go?
Wh-What on Earth is up with her?
What's up, Konoha?
I-I'm sorry, Niko-chan.
I don't want you to
investigate them anymore.
Why?
You know I'll do a good job.
No, it's fine!
It's the thought that counts.
What? Why?
Because Benio-sama will get mad
if she finds out about this!
Don't worry.
Keeping secrets is also
part of a reporter's job.
Besides, if I just dropped this case,
then it'd disgrace my good name!
Wh-What's with that speed?
Y-You don't have to follow me!
Bathrooms are dangerous.
...Mashiro told me...
that someone named Hanako-san
frequently appears in school bathrooms.
She doesn't exist!
...Red hair, a pale face...
Stay!
Wow, it actually worked.
Uh, I-I'll be fine,
so just wait for me here.
Okay.
Thanks.
I'm getting information from her
directly and tailing her on top of it!
I've gotta get some natural shots of her!
N-Niko-chan!
Seriously, you can stop
investigating them now.
Why?
I told you I'd do a good job!
Thanks, but that's enough.
Please, stop!
Oh, right.
It didn't click until you told me,
but Mashiro-chan's just a kid, right?
A kid's attending high school,
and no one bats an eye.
It's a bit strange, isn't it?
This needs to be investigated too.
The reporter in me is getting
more and more excited!
I'll start writing tons of
articles as a first year,
ensuring that I, Oono Niko, will become the
newspaper club's editor-in-chief in the future!
Just you watch!
Uh, well... it's nice that
...you're ambitious, but...
Hey, what're you doing?
Give it back!
Stop causing trouble
for Kobeni and Mashiro.
Huh?
How did you know I'm
using those two to make it big?!
I'm deleting these.
What?!
H-Hey!
I went through a lot
of trouble to get those!
Wait, you don't know
how to delete them?
Whatever.
Anyway, just stop bothering Kobeni.
What's with that guy?
At least my photos are safe.
Wait, what? They're gone!
Why?
That pipsqueak's... brother?
Something wrong, Konoha?
N-Nothing, really.
Oh, was it love at first sight?
N-No way!
Benio-sama's the one I love!
Engaged to the
Unidentified
★
I have the results of your finals.
Anyone who scored less than a thirty
needs to take make-up exams.
Wh-What's wrong?
You passed, right?
Wait, what?!
Hakuya's good at memorizing things, but terrible
at subjects which require more brain power.
One extreme to the other, huh?
Eureka!
Kobeni, you should help Hakuya study.
What? But I'm not good at math either!
O-Oh, all right.
I-I'm having trouble keeping up
...with some parts too...
A-All right.
Let's study together.
Library
You use this formula for this problem.
And for this one, the five goes
over here and the seven over there.
Oh, I see!
What do I do if I run into
the slit-mouthed woman?!
Maybe give her some pomade.
That's Benio-sama's sister for you.
She seems very smart.
Benio-sama's as dreamy as ever today!
But she's been sighing for a while now.
Could she be tired?
I'm so worried.
Jeez, I really don't wanna do this.
I'm lacking in little sister vitamins.
I want my adorable little sister
to sit on my lap as I work!
Niko
A text from Niko-chan?
★
（＊＾３＾）/
Spying on them~
Subj:
From: Oono Niko
Spying on them~
Subj:
（＊＾３＾）/
★
I...
I need to use the restroom.
Okay.
...Hanako—
You don't need to worry about her.
The school's so scary in the evening.
It feels like something's
...gonna jump out at any moment...
She stepped out!
I'm just gonna close my eyes
and sprint all the way there!
Huh?
Whoa, she's coming after me!
I'll hide in the bathroom!
I-I'll be all right.
I'll be in and out in a flash.
I'm not a child anymore.
This'll be a walk in the park.
That was close.
Ouch, I started running too suddenly.
My sides hurt now.
A ghost!
Where are you, Niko-chan?
Oh no! A ghost!
A mo-monster!
...Wha—
A monster?
Who, me?
Shaddup, ya blubberin' fool!
How can ya have the gall
ta call some'un a monster?!
I can't believe ya call'd a
right hottie like me a monster!
O-Oh my.
Nobody saw that, right?
Oh.
...Uh...
...I-I'm sorry...
...O-Of all people...
School bathrooms really are dangerous.
They sure are!
School bathrooms are dangerous!
I knew it!
So from now on, just tell me
whenever you have to go.
I'll accompany you.
That's even more dangerous!
...Um, Nee-sama...
You know the student council secretary?
Oh, you mean Suetsugi?
What's she like?
The eldest daughter.
I kept thinking that she
wasn't very little sister-like,
but apparently she's the eldest daughter.
That's not what I want to know.
Well, let's see... What else is there?
She's an earnest and obedient kid.
And very girly, so to speak.
...Right...
She'll sometimes make
snacks and bring them to us.
But of course, she's
...no match for your breasts—
I mean, your skills!
...Uh... Uh-huh...
We've got make-up exams now, huh?
Good luck.
You can do it!
W-Will you be okay?
Probably.
...Because you taught me...
I think I'll probably be somewhat fine.
Pull yourself together!
Wait, how come Hakuya has to take
make-up exams while Mashiro passed?
Oh, well, those exams
were way too difficult for me,
so I cheated just enough to pass.
Cheated?
I just used a form of hypnosis.
The same kind that I used
to slip in unnoticed at school.
So that's why nobody finds it strange
that you're attending high school.
I can't believe you actually
have those sort of powers.
Can you do stuff like that too, Hakuya?
I can,
but I don't want to cheat.
Unlike Mashiro, I am
an actual high schooler.
I see.
Atta boy.
Student Council Room
...I don't even feel like going inside...
I couldn't believe she was
yelling in the hallway like that!
I don't want to breathe
the same air as her anymore.
Besides, she's a monster!
How can you deal with that?!
What if that's what happened?
How am I supposed to face Benio-sama?
Oh, Suetsugi.
What are you doing?
Oh, vice president!
...Oh, uh...
Where's the president?
I'm gonna go recharge
by touching my sister!
Fill 'er up nice and quick, please!
She'll be here eventually.
Spring's still a ways away, huh?
It'll get warmer once
March comes around.
...I-I have to use the restroom...
Oh, okay.
Shall we go, then?
Suetsugi.
Sorry to ask, but could
you go look for Benio?
Sure.
She's probably with
Kobeni and her friends.
Huh?
She's with her sister?
This sucks.
What if I run into her?
I'll accompany you to the bathroom!
You don't have to!
Why'd'ya hafta keep showin'
me stuff like that, huh?!
I'd kill ta hold hands wit her
and go ta the bathroom!
All right, the make-up exams are done.
I'm beat!
Let's go home.
Thank God we're done with that.
Where did Mashiro-tan go?
If I don't head back soon,
Nadeshiko will yell at me.
Look, it's Benio-sama!
Is she still here because
of her student council work?
...Benio-sama...
Goodbye, everyone.
Keep it together.
Is she emitting
poison gas or something?
Could it be nerve gas?
There's no doubt about it!
She's dangerous!
We need to quarantine Benio at once!
Quarantine me?
So you want to keep me
all to yourself?
Well, aren't you greedy?
How can you be so optimistic?!
Mashiro-tan complimented me!
Oh, come on!
I can't accept this.
There, there.
Nee-sama is very popular,
so some fanatics might end up
hating you if this keeps up.
What are you talking about?
There's no way that'd happen.
How could she behave
like that with Benio-sama?
Unforgivable!
Let's think about how to
achieve world peace.
No way!
Leave me alone!
How unfortunate!
...My wish is for every student—
No, for everyone in the world
to live in peace and harmony!
No!
Shiver me timbers! I'd be right chuffed
if the lady said somethin' like that ta me!
...Um...
Suetsugi-san, do you need something?
...Huh? Well, uh...
What do I do?
All right! That's it!
I-I need to talk to Mitsumine-san.
I can't believe I said it!
What is it?
Not you! I didn't even
know you were here!
M-Me?
What do you want?
...I-I even asked for her...
What do I do now?
Wait, could you be from the mountains?
Wh-Who cares about that?
I just got that kind of scent from you.
S-Scent?!
Do I reek of the sticks?!
So, what do you want?
...W-Well...
I just don't want you to act
rudely toward Benio-sama!
...Um...
...In other words, uh...
Just so you know,
Benio's the one being rude!
You're calling her by name?!
Sh-She buys me weird pajamas,
weird underwear,
wants to accompany me
to the bathroom,
tries to take baths with me,
and even buys extra-large
chocolate cakes on Valentine's Day!
A-Are you bragging?!
And you keep calling her "Benio"!
That's "Benio-sama" to you, you idiot!
Idio—?!
Only an idiot calls
someone else an idiot!
Only an idiot responds to being
called an idiot by calling them an idiot!
No, only an idiot calls
someone else an idiot!
How old are these two?
No, you're wrong!
Idiot!
I'm the one who should be crying!
...I didn't know Suetsugi-san was like that...
Looks like Benio's poison gas got to her.
I can't believe we're a
part of the same species.
Huh?
What?
She's the same as us.
She reeks of our species.
D-Does that mean
Suetsugi-san can transform too?
Probably.
I'd noticed it a while back.
Wh-Why didn't you say anything?
I didn't think it mattered.
Of course it does!
I don't really care, anyway.
Well, you should!
You're both the same!
That darn pipsqueak!
How dare she make a fool outta me!
Ya gotta problem with makin'
a fresh start in high school?
Konoha, your accent's showing through.
N-Niko-chan!
What are you doing?
I tried getting a
bird's eye view of a scoop,
but I couldn't find anything.
You fought with Mashiro-chan?
Over what?
She made fun of me and then bragged
about taking baths together with Benio-sama!
Oh, right.
You were asking why the pipsqueak
was in high school despite being a kid, right?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Wait, could you be
from the mountains?
Are we the same species?
Has she slipped into
the crowd at school?
...That means...
What is it?
Earth to Konoha!
You alive?
Hey!
What's her problem?
There, there. Calm down.
But she's so rude!
What did I do to deserve this?
sou desu curry wa daikoubutsu desu
Yes, curry is my favorite
But if I may be a bit greedy
tada yoku wo iwasete moraereba
You prefer it mild, don't you?
amakuchi ga iindeshou
Oh, but sticky food is fine by me too
mou nebaneba datte mo mochiron
I can eat it, no problem
zenzen heiki de taberaremasu
You don't like it, do you?
nigate nan dana
mou mitame wa chokotto chikkoi desu ga
Sure, I may look a bit on the smaller side
But I'm a proper sister-in-law
kore demo shikkari kojuuto datte shimasu
Look at you, pushing yourself (Yes!)
senobi shicchatte (yes!)
ryouri mo souji mo sentaku mo daijoubu desu
You can handle cooking, cleaning, and laundry just fine
And you've got great child-bearing hips
sore ni anzangata desushi
Hey, I'm conscious of that
ki ni shiteru noni
ie de wa annani annan nanoni
You're so crazy at home
Did you brainwash the people at school?
ittai douiu sennoujutsu desu ka
shitto shichatte mou (more!)
Aww, don't be jealous (More!)
We make excuses, saying we're worried about you
shinpai da toka riyuu wo tsukete
And now we've finally snuck into your heart
chakkari to ima sennyuu seikou
Once we get close to each other
nakayoku nattara
uchiakenakya demo
And we have to be frank
Will we still be able to understand
aimai na koto
What's left unsaid?
rikai dekiru kana
sorya maa oyatsu toka
My love for snacks and other things
kodomoppoi desu ga
May make me seem childish
sore demo zutto nakayokushite kuremasuka
But will you still be my friend forever?
Next Time
And now for
the preview for
next week's
"Engaged to the
Unidentified"!
Next Time
And now for the preview for next week's
"Engaged to the Unidentified"!
'Tis finally
mah time
to shine.
Konoha 'ere.
'Tis finally mah time to shine.
"Benio-sama's Morning"
Next
time
All three
of 'em
chapters.
And the
week afta
that...
"Benio-sama's Evening"
"Benio-sama's Afternoon"
"Benio-sama's Morning"
Next time, we have "Benio-sama's Morning,"
"Benio-sama's Afternoon,"
and "Benio-sama's Evening."
All three of 'em chapters.
...And the week afta that—
"Benio-sama's Afternoon"
All three
of 'em
chapters.
And the
week afta
that...
All three
of 'em
chapters.
And the
week afta
that...
Next time: Only a Sister can Cure a Sister's Sadness.
Next Time
Only a Sister can Cure a Sister's Sadness