Um, is something wrong?
Pissed
Nothing at all.
...A present for White Day...
Something white?
...White...
...Can you pass the milk...
Wh-What's wrong?
Nothing!
Oh, I get it!
Benio's jealous of you, Hakuya!
Jealous?
She doesn't like how you and
Kobeni are all lovey-dovey.
Isn't that right?
Even your face of satisfaction is cute.
That wasn't what
we were talking about!
I-It's not like we
actually are lovey-dovey!
And we're engaged, you know.
Don't you think the horse has bolted?
Yeah, perhaps it has.
...But...
After thinking about it for a bit,
I really don't like it.
A fiancé? To hell with that!
Kobeni's my sister!
I won't let anyone have her!
Are you a child?!
Through
Benio's Eyes
What's with that look?!
J-Just calm down!
I just don't like this at all!
Seriously, what's gotten into you now?
Hakuya, you should tell her off.
What... What am I, the father?
A straight man?!
Engaged to the Unidentified
asa me ga sametara mou
When I woke up this morning
kinou mitai na nichijou wa nakute
The everyday life I had was nowhere to be found
Seriously, uh, what now?
honto ah mou etto dou shiyou
In the midst of all the sighing
tameiki majiri ni neru
okashi to mousou no recipe no naka ni
I accidentally put in this recipe of sweets and delusions
A dash of love
koigokoro haichatta
chiffon cake ni custard
Chiffon cakes and custard
scone ni clotted cream
Along with some scones and clotted cream
dakedo yappa korette okashii wa
But there really is something off about all this
Why does it have to be me?
doushite watashi nan daro
kyuu ni sonna koto iidashite
How could you spring this on me?
What am I ever to do?
ah dou shiyou
kimi wo suki ni nacchau ka nante wakaranai kedo
I don't know if I'll fall for you
taisetsu na hito da
But you'll still be precious to me
Gosh, that's a little embarrassing
nante ah terekusai kana
kimi wa majime na tone de suki tte nante iu desho
You say you love me in the most serious tone
That makes my heart skip a beat
chotto dokitto shichau jan
And sparks an extraordinary revolution within me
nante hinichijouteki na revolution
Looking Up The Term "Lovey-Dovey Side"
I can't go so far as to say I won't stand for it.
You did save Kobeni's life, after all.
But I want you to know
just how mad I am!
...Also...
I think of you as my sister, Mashiro!
These are two separate matters. Got it?
What was that?!
How can she be so selfish?
Well, just don't let it get to you.
I won't!
I'd go insane if I let
everything she did get to me.
She's mad about it,
but she thinks of Mashiro as a sister?
...What the...
You don't have to take her seriously!
I wonder why she flipped, though.
Jeez, it's not like anything
happened between us.
What are you saying?
Benio's mad because you
told Hakuya you loved him!
Isn't that obvious?!
B-But I never said it!
It was implied!
All I said was I didn't mind
having him as a fiancé... right?
Wait, even that was crossing the line?!
That's what made her mad, I think.
Let's just ignore Benio.
Anyway, what are you
going to do for White Day?
That's the more pressing issue here.
H-He doesn't have to get me a present.
It's not like anything
happened between us.
Stop worrying about Benio!
All I said was I didn't mind
having him as a fiancé.
Here, you two should hold hands.
There. Just like that.
...Th-This is just like...
We've finally captured it
Photographic Proof of the Century
"M-Morning."
Or should I say "good morning"?
Please take care of her, Suetsugi.
...How am I supposed to talk to her...
...Th-That's just like...
Alien
Big news!!!
Invasion
...You pipsqueak...
Um, Suetsugi.
Can we talk later?
Cake? But why?
I wanted to apologize for the
trouble I caused you yesterday.
Th-Thank you.
...But I made her cry...
Unlike Sister, I don't really
like standing out much.
It'd be rough for me if this
whole fiancé thing spread.
So I'm not saying I don't
...want to be engaged, it's just...
Konoha!
What's up?
Woah, cake?
It looks delicious!
It's over before it even began?
Huh?
Sorry I'm late.
Cleaning took a little
longer than expected.
Huh?!
Snarl
What a great scent.
Um... what's wrong with the president?
Oh.
She's mad at how close her sister
and her fiancé are getting.
But I can't say that.
She's doing some soul searching.
Would you like some tea too, Suetsugi?
Yeah. Thank you very much.
Oh, right. I have cake.
Oh, is that the cake Kobeni baked?
Y-Yeah, it is.
I'm surprised you could tell.
She just gave it to me.
I see. You two sure are
getting along well.
Thank you.
N-No problem!
O-Oh, would you two like some?
I know it's not much!
It's not much?
Suetsugi, calm down.
I'm not saying I don't
...want to be engaged...
What the heck?
Why didn't you just
say that from the start?
...Now I look like an idiot...
She doesn't want it to spread?
Why would I go around telling people?
Konoha!
Gimme something to write about!
News! News!
Yeah. It's totally out of the question.
Can't tell one of Niko's
friends anything, can you?
Um, what happened, Hakuya?
Something great!
Something great?
I see. So that's what that expression is for.
His relationship with
Kobeni has leveled up!
Oh, really? Congratulations, Hakuya.
Um... does this make us officially coupled?
What's that supposed to mean?
I wonder if Suetsugi ate it yet.
No, I mean, is Kobeni mai waifu now?
Well, I guess so? You two are engaged.
What're you guys talking about?!
Lovey-dovey side
I found that phrase when I looked up the term "lovey-dovey side".
I told you, that's not it!
I just felt I was being a bit rude
...to you, so I wanted to apologize...
You sure are serious, Kobeni.
Hakuya doesn't care
about all that, though.
Rude?
What about?
...Well, um...
It's just a matter of
...sorting out my feelings...
Well, if you've hit your lovey-dovey
phase, then that's good news!
I'm telling you, that's not it!
We'll leave you two youngins alone.
The third and fourth wheels
will be taking their leave now.
Huh? Wait!
I can't believe I actually
said that clichéd line!
I've always wanted to say that once!
...Um...
...Well, for now...
Wh-What?
For now... let's go home.
Y-Yeah, let's.
Oh. Right.
Do you mind if I text you sometimes?
I don't.
Hakuya
Wait, right now?
Inbox
From: Hakuya
Wh-What are you two
walking home alone for?
Where the heck is Mashiro?
Well, where is she?
Wait, does that mean
Mashiro's... wide open?
She... She has to go home all alone?!
That's too dangerous!
Students need to go home in a group!
U-Um... are you okay?
You just jumped from the second floor.
I'm fine!
I'm good at sports, after all!
What sport involves
jumping off the second floor?!
It's dangerous to send
Mashiro home by herself!
...Um, that's...
What are you bothering them for?!
Oh, there you are, Mashiro.
You're a proper nuisance, Benio!
Get! Scram!
I haven't heard that word in ages!
So cute!
She's not even listening to me!
So you two were spying on us?
W-We're sorry.
I don't know why, but it's
all still weighing on my mind.
Konoha!
Oh, Niko.
Konoha, since you're
...in the student council...
have you heard anything about
Kobeni from Lady Benio?
Like, maybe something
I could write an article on.
Oh, is she still collecting data?
Though her subject said that she
...didn't want to stand out earlier...
Niko, there actually is
something I can tell you.
Really?!
...Well...
Engaged to the
Unidentified
★
Huh?
A new newspaper bulletin?
It mentions you, Kobeni.
Huh?
What's it say?
...Wait...
second
Lady Benio
gets another
perfect score
coming!
Today's
Lady Benio
is the
Another perfect score!
News on
Lady Benio
The sister of
80% of this is about Benio!
Thanks a bunch, Konoha!
This is the first article
I got an okay on!
I'm just glad I was of help to you.
Lady Benio's sister is a great cook
Yay!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
An article like this is fine, right?
Yay!
Yay! Yay!
Oh.
They published an article about your sister.
Huh?
Oh, wow. You're right!
I need to get a cutout!
Stop it.
Aw.
Is this fine, though?
Kobeni hates this sort of thing.
I thought that would be fine,
but could I have made
Lady Benio unhappy?!
You're right.
What if the entire world finds out
just how cute Kobeni is thanks to this article?
What if some nasty scumbags
start to take notice of her?
Though, well, I won't just
sit back and watch that happen.
You're too close.
Did I do something I shouldn't have?
Konoha!
Now that I think about it,
there's nothing newsworthy in this article!
She finally realized it.
...So, um...
Suetsugi told Hakuya to marry her,
so doesn't that mean she likes him?
Nah, that's not it.
It's just because
we're of the same species.
they're
the
same
Just
because
they're
the
same
Just
because
...Wait, that's all...
...there is to it....
Apparently her mom told her to call dibs
if she found a guy of the same species.
Dibs?
Well, it is rare to find our kind like that.
You don't have to worry about it, though,
since you're practically half-us too.
Wait, what?!
What, didn't you know?
Since Hakuya gave you half of his powers,
that makes you basically half-us.
So I have some mysterious power too?
Beats me. I don't think it
works like it does in a fantasy.
But if that's the case,
does that mean I don't
have to worry about Suetsugi?
Yeah, yeah.
We want nothing to do with
such a rude person either!
Grr!
So just forget about it and work
on your relationship with Hakuya!
You can even wear matching clothes!
No way!
Victory is mine!
...Sister... how long have you been there...
Huh? I just got here.
You were talking about
matching clothes, right?
Thank goodness.
She didn't overhear anything about
Suetsugi being one of Mashiro's kind.
I've already worn matching clothes
with Kobeni in the past,
so I win!
You mean from when we were kids?
You were so cute.
I forgot how many pairs we had,
...but my favorite one has to be...
I won't.
I'll have to buy matching clothes
for Mashiro and me next.
Could you stop messing around?
I kind of want
something
that
matches
with
Kobeni
too
Oh, that's it! That's what
you should get for White Day!
Get her something matching with you!
Does that mean you're going to
get me something too, Mashiro?!
For White Day!
No. These are two different subjects.
...A matching pair...
Maybe a sweater and scarf
with your initials on it.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
It's already spring!
It's getting hotter!
...I can't knit...
He was thinking handknit?!
Oh no! I can't knit either.
You don't need to
compete with him, Sister!
Just forget about matching
things and White Day, okay?
Besides, why does being on good terms
equate to having matching things?
I-I won't, okay?
Rather, it's out of the question.
Currently accepting replies for Q&A
What dish goes best with rice?
I'd like a matching pair
for boy and girl, but...
What dish goes best with rice?
Currently accepting replies for Q&A
I'd like a matching pair
for boy and girl, but...
Currently accepting replies for Q&A
What dish goes best with rice?
I'd like a matching pair
for boy and girl, but...
What dish goes best with rice?
Currently accepting replies for Q&A
I'd like a matching pair
for boy and girl, but...
Currently accepting replies for Q&A
What dish goes best with rice?
I'd like a matching pair
for boy and girl, but...
Currently accepting replies for Q&A
What dish goes best with rice?
I'd like a matching pair
for boy and girl, but...
Currently accepting replies for Q&A
What dish goes best with rice?
I'd like a matching pair
for boy and girl, but...
What dish goes best with rice?
Currently accepting replies for Q&A
I'd like a matching pair
for boy and girl, but...
What dish goes best with rice?
I'd like a matching pair
for boy and girl, but...
Currently accepting replies for Q&A
I'd like a matching pair
for boy and girl, but...
What dish goes best with rice?
Currently accepting replies for Q&A
I want a pair of matching things,
but I don't know what to get.
I don't want to get clothes or a scarf,
but something practical
where I don't have to worry
about the size or anything.
Good answer?
I want a pair of matching clothes,
but I don't know what to get.
I don't want to get clothes or a scarf,
but something practical
where I don't have to worry
about the size or anything.
I want a pair of matching clothes,
but I don't know what to get.
I don't want to get clothes or a scarf,
but something practical
where I don't have to worry
about the size or anything.
I want a pair of matching clothes,
but I don't know what to get.
I don't want to get clothes or a scarf,
but something practical
where I don't have to worry
about the size or anything.
I want a pair of matching clothes,
but I don't know what to get.
I don't want to get clothes or a scarf,
but something practical
where I don't have to worry
about the size or anything.
I want a pair of matching clothes,
but I don't know what to get.
I don't want to get clothes or a scarf,
but something practical
where I don't have to worry
about the size or anything.
Reply
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
From hjfhg4m
Reply
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
Reply
From hjfhg4m
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
From hjfhg4m
Reply
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
From hjfhg4m
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
Reply
From hjfhg4m
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
Reply
From hjfhg4m
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
Reply
From hjfhg4m
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
Reply
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
From hjfhg4m
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
From hjfhg4m
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
From hjfhg4m
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
You could always get them some sort of accessory.
Maybe casually measure their wrist for a watch.
Maybe something light like a notebook,
or even a pen would be nice too.
From hjfhg4m
What have you been looking up?
I have some business to
take care of on the way home.
Let's go home separately.
Business? That's odd.
Bye.
Okay.
I'm fine. I can get home on my own.
I wonder what sort of business
Hakuya has to take care of.
Isn't it obvious? He went
to go look for your present.
Is he that invested in finding
something that matches?
Benio stirred him up.
He wants something to
symbolize your relationship.
Oh, Hakuya?
Are you done with your business?
Is now fine?
It's a handkerchief.
They're technically different colors,
but they are matching ones.
A matching pair?
A halo?!
Oh, Hakuya, are you
done with your business?
Take a look at this!
It's the second installment of UMA series!
Oh, there's a new one?
Kusshie
Ooh, this one's Kusshie from Lake Kussharo.
They're getting into the
really niche characters now!
So, hey, keep this a
secret from everyone.
It's not that I don't like it. Just that it
might be problematic if Sister finds out.
Sister!
Why would it be
problematic if I found out?
What's that? A present?
I'm gonna throw up!
Sister!
What the heck?!
Are you okay?
...Oh, the stress...
So why would it be
problematic if I found out?
This is exactly what I'm talking about!
Hakuya, what is that?
It's a secret!
Huh? C'mon, what is it?
Tell me!
Oh, I was going to give these
...to you when we got home...
Here. I got a handkerchief
for you and Sister.
Huh?
Huh
The second installment of the
...UMA series and a handkerchief...
Today was a good day.
...But...
Kobeni stole the march
on you, didn't she?
Now you need to get her
an even better present!
That's easier said than done.
Stop being so timid.
You need to think of this as a battle
you need to win for Kobeni's love.
...That's a lot of pressure...
Good luck!
sou desu curry wa daikoubutsu desu
Yes, curry is my favorite
But if I may be a bit greedy
tada yoku wo iwasete moraereba
You prefer it mild, don't you?
amakuchi ga iindeshou
Oh, but sticky food is fine by me too
mou nebaneba datte mo mochiron
I can eat it, no problem
zenzen heiki de taberaremasu
nigate nan dana
You don't like it, do you?
mou mitame wa chokotto chikkoi desu ga
Sure, I may look a bit on the smaller side
kore demo shikkari kojuuto datte shimasu
But I'm a proper sister-in-law
Look at you, pushing yourself (Yes!)
senobi shicchatte (yes!)
ryouri mo souji mo sentaku mo daijoubu desu
You can handle cooking, cleaning, and laundry just fine
sore ni anzangata desushi
And you've got great child-bearing hips
ki ni shiteru noni
Hey, I'm conscious of that
You're so crazy at home
ie de wa annani annan nanoni
Did you brainwash the people at school?
ittai douiu sennoujutsu desu ka
Aww, don't be jealous (More!)
shitto shichatte mou (more!)
We make excuses, saying we're worried about you
shinpai da toka riyuu wo tsukete
And now we've finally snuck into your heart
chakkari to ima sennyuu seikou
nakayoku nattara
Once we get close to each other
And we have to be frank
uchiakenakya demo
aimai na koto
Will we still be able to understand
rikai dekiru kana
What's left unsaid?
sorya maa oyatsu toka
My love for snacks and other things
kodomoppoi desu ga
May make me seem childish
But will you still be my friend forever?
sore demo zutto nakayokushite kuremasuka
of
the
UMA
series
!
The
second
install-
ment
The second installment of the UMA series!
Asshie
Tosshie
Isshie
Asshie
I've also
got
Isshie
in Lake
Ikeda,
Asshie
in Lake
Ashino
and
Tosshie
in
Lake
Touya!
I've also got Isshie in Lake Ikeda, Asshie in Lake Ashino,
and Tosshie in Lake Touya!
Don't
forget
about
Bennie,
Mashiro!
She's
here
this
week
too?!
Don't forget about Bennie, Mashiro!
She's here this week too?!
S-So would that make me Kobennie?
S-So
would
that
make me
Kobennie
?
Enjoying The Handkerchief
Next Time
N-Next time: Enjoying The Handkerchief.