You there.
Marry me.
...Marry...
...I... I shouldn't have eavesdropped...
...That's when I remembered...
that I'm not athletic.
Kobeni?!
So I fall over if I suddenly try
to move? Just how clumsy am I?
Benio-sama's sister?!
...U-Um...
I didn't hear anything!
I didn't hear anything
about marriage or the likes!
She's amazingly terrible at lying!
Engaged to the Unidentified
When I woke up this morning
asa me ga sametara mou
kinou mitai na nichijou wa nakute
The everyday life I had was nowhere to be found
honto ah mou etto dou shiyou
Seriously, uh, what now?
tameiki majiri ni neru
In the midst of all the sighing
okashi to mousou no recipe no naka ni
I accidentally put in this recipe of sweets and delusions
koigokoro haichatta
A dash of love
chiffon cake ni custard
Chiffon cakes and custard
Along with some scones and clotted cream
scone ni clotted cream
dakedo yappa korette okashii wa
But there really is something off about all this
Why does it have to be me?
doushite watashi nan daro
kyuu ni sonna koto iidashite
How could you spring this on me?
ah dou shiyou
What am I ever to do?
kimi wo suki ni nacchau ka nante wakaranai kedo
I don't know if I'll fall for you
taisetsu na hito da
But you'll still be precious to me
nante ah terekusai kana
Gosh, that's a little embarrassing
You say you love me in the most serious tone
kimi wa majime na tone de suki tte nante iu desho
chotto dokitto shichau jan
That makes my heart skip a beat
And sparks an extraordinary revolution within me
nante hinichijouteki na revolution
It Was Humiliating! I've Been Shamed!
I'm sorry!
W-Wait!
...Kobeni...
...Sto—
Wait up.
Why?
Answer me in 100 words or less.
Huh? In 100 words?!
...Uh...
...We're... still... not... done... here...
Hey, what were you talking about?
Don't interrupt me!
Now I don't remember
what number I was on!
Hakuya and Kobeni
are engaged, you know.
Keep your nose out of their affairs.
Huh?!
Engaged?
Ha! Ha!
Serves you right!
What the heck?!
How was I supposed to know?!
Engaged? What's that
supposed to mean?
...Wait, could it be...
Is Benio-sama's sister
from the same species?
That means!
...Benio-sama and I...
are comrades?!
I knew it. She did get you
with some strange gas.
Well?
Is it true?
Is Benio-sama the same as us?
Neither one of them are.
Huh? They aren't?
That sucks.
So, what's up with that?
They're engaged even though
they're not of the same species?
...Th-That's...
We have our reasons.
So do I.
My mom told me to call dibs immediately
if I ever found a male from our species.
Your reasons don't concern me.
...Uh... uh... uh...
Suetsugi-san asked Hakuya to marry her.
So wait... that means she likes Hakuya?
Kobeni.
Oh, Hakuya.
Wh-What's wrong?
You tripped earlier, and I
wanted to see if you were okay.
O-Oh, that?
...Yeah, I'm fine, it's just...
Are you sure you
should've come after me?
It seemed like you three
were having an important talk.
An important talk?
...I mean, Suetsugi-san...
asked you to marry her.
Oh.
What's with that response?
But I'm already engaged to you.
N-No, I don't mean that.
Engaged?
Oono-san!
What's going on? Fill me in!
Engaged?!
Don't tell anyone
about this fiancé thing, okay?
I meant I was engaged
in mortal combat outside.
Mortal Combat
I smell a scoop!
You won't fool me so easily.
I heard you mention Konoha.
Suggestions
So, c'mon, tell me!
Oh, could it be that you
and Mitsumine-kun are dating?
...Th-That's...
No!
Oh, really?
I see.
So what was that about Konoha?
Why don't you ask her?
Oh, I see!
So, what was it?
I think you should just ask her yourself.
All right.
Konoha!
Where are you?!
She's fast.
No!
H-Huh... what's this feeling?
...I'm kinda hurt...
Was that good enough?
You said you didn't want me to
tell anyone about the fiancé thing.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
...It's just...
I'm sorry.
For what?
How could I tell him to keep it a secret,
and yet get hurt when he denies it?
That's way too selfish!
...And wait, the fact that it hurt means...
What's wrong?
Nothing!
Jeez, what was up with Suetsugi?
She was totally out of line!
Grr!
Hey.
Suetsugi-san originally called
you out to talk, right?
What was that about?
...It was...
about how she thinks I came
...here because I was after Benio...
Huh?
It was humiliating!
I've been shamed!
Shamed?
How?!
Wait, could it be?!
Suetsugi
x
Mashiro-tan?!
Suetsugi
x
Mashiro-tan?!
I can't believe it.
What's with that pipsqueak?!
I can't believe she doesn't understand
...how wonderful Benio-sama is...
And someone like her is
...staying at Benio-sama's house...
Oh, Konoha sighted!
Oh, Niko-chan.
Hey, hey, guess what?
Why were Kobeni and
Mitsumine-kun talking about you?
Wait, they were talking about me?
Could it be about
my outburst in the hallway?
Or that I fought with the pipsqueak?
Or maybe they were laughing about my asking him
to marry me without knowing they were engaged?
Konoha, keep it together!
Here! Look at Benio-sama's picture!
Benio-sama!
So then I asked if she
and Mitsumine-kun were dating,
and they said I was wrong.
They're always together, though.
Huh?
It would've made for a great article.
The headline would be:
"Benio-sama's sister has a boyfriend"!
Wait, aren't they engaged?
I get it.
Sure, they may be engaged,
but it must be one of those
arranged marriage thingies.
If those two are against it,
then I'll still have a chance!
Woohoo!
Konoha?
We got interrupted, so I still
have no idea what's going on.
You there.
Marry me.
So does that mean
Suetsugi-san likes Hakuya?
Yeah, it's way more believable
when there's photographical evidence.
Super secret zone!!
Uh, Mashiro-tan?
There's something I want to ask you.
What is it?
What happened between
you and Suetsugi yesterday?
...Suetsugi...
I was absolutely
humiliated because of you!
How are you going
to make it up to me?
I don't really understand,
but I'll take responsibility.
Let's get married.
It's utterly incomprehensible.
"Benio-sama", my foot.
Huh?
Aw, she's all bashful!
How cute!
So, what really happened?
You've gotta tell me this time.
...Uh...
Your popularity means that people get jealous
when you keep fawning over Mashiro.
So I think you should just leave her be.
No way!
But I can't believe people
are fighting over me. How sad.
Maybe I should have
a word with Suetsugi?
N-No, you'd just make things worse.
It's probably all good now.
It was just a misunderstanding.
Oh?
In truth, Mashiro's avoiding you.
Oh.
Wait, what?
So she's just jealous of
my relationship with Mashiro-tan.
Wait, are you jealous too?
Huh?
Oh, yeah!
That's right!
Wait... what?
Kobeni?
I'll pick up some eggs
on the way home,
and bake some chiffon cake later.
Yay! I can't wait!
I looked it up on the Internet.
I really want to try a
chocolate chiffon cake.
All right.
Nee-sama likes those too.
Guess I'll go with chocolate, then.
Oh, you don't like having
the same tastes as Nee-sama.
You may not like her, but Nee-sama
actually has a lot of good qualities.
It's amazing how she can do anything,
and it makes me happy
to see her so popular.
...I guess for me it's more...
sadness, than jealousy?
Even her sister is looking out for her?
How sad.
She randomly said how there
weren't many of our species out there,
and then she asked Hakuya
to marry her. Like, what?
Don't worry, though.
I already told her that
you and Hakuya are engaged.
Huh?
Yes?
You told her we were engaged?!
Yes!
Th-That's bad!
Why?
It's better this way.
Our parents approve, you know.
You shouldn't care
what anyone else thinks.
But if a rumor starts to
...spread, it'll be really bad...
...If Oono-san were to find out...
she might start questioning me again.
Oh.
Huh?
What now?
Have her not say anything.
...I wonder if she'll agree...
I'm not giving up!
Not giving up on... what?
...Not giving up...
Is it about Benio?!
No! That's scary!
Engaged to the
Unidentified
★
I guess Suetsugi-san really does like Hakuya.
What's wrong?
Are you worried about
this fiancé thing spreading?
...Oh, that too... just...
If asking her doesn't help, then you'll just
need to make her an offer she can't refuse:
a bribe.
Bribe?!
What about pictures?
I mean, didn't she have a
bunch of pictures of Benio?
I fail to understand why, though.
If we show her how
weird Benio can be,
then I'm sure she'll
awake from her spell.
...I'm starting to doubt your motives...
I'll take the pictures!
Benio at her weirdest!
I am great at concealing
my presence, after all!
A-Anyway, I'll go ask her
not to tell anyone about it.
Benio-sama!
Good morning!
Good luck with your
student council work!
Thank you.
I hope you all have a peaceful day today.
...She's like a queen...
I knew it. Mashiro-tan
...acts that way because...
She says "no", but she
actually means "yes"!
...The pipsqueak...
For someone who said she
wasn't interested in Benio-sama,
look at her go.
Well, it's not like I don't get it.
All said and done,
Benio-sama's charm
is out of this world!
...Still...
Ya gotta act accordin'ly, darn it!
...U-Um...
...I need to talk with you for a bit...
Is that okay?
Yes.
She doesn't let her
guard down in school.
What are you doing?
...Um, well, uh...
Nothing!
Does she hate me
because I'm Benio's friend?
What is it?
What's going on?
Do you need me, Mashiro-tan?
I'm coming!
What's with you?!
What's with you?
...U-Uh...
What is it?
...Well...
I wonder what it is.
Is this happening because I
said I wouldn't give up earlier?
...Um...
It's about this whole
engaged to Hakuya thing.
I wanted to ask you
to keep it a secret.
Oh, that.
19th
The Day's Food
Month
Every
of
The
So you really are against it.
Huh?
I wasn't going to spread it,
but, like, you told Niko-chan that you two
weren't dating despite being engaged.
On top of that,
you want to keep it a secret.
So basically, you're against it, right?
If you are, then why
don't you break it off?
I mean, you wouldn't be
doing right by him otherwise.
If they break it off, then I'll
be able to do as Mom told me.
I'll be able to marry
someone of the same species!
Was that good enough?
...I knew I wasn't doing right by him...
Wh-Why are you crying?
Are you not against it?
Huh?!
I-I'm sorry.
...It's...
It's not your fault, Suetsugi-san.
...Kobeni...
Are you... crying?
H-Huh?!
...No way...
She's gonna think I
made her cry, isn't she?!
...Wait...
Am I in big trouble here?
It's nothing.
Some dirt just got into my eye.
Dirt?!
Oh no!
Let's go to the nurse.
Or maybe an ophthalmologist?
I-It's fine.
Really, it is.
Oh, Suetsugi.
Y-Yes?
Oh, are you two friends?
...Uh, well...
Yeah!
We're in the same year,
and we've been talking a lot lately.
I see.
Please take care of her, Suetsugi.
Sure!
And since Mashiro-chan is like my beloved sister too,
I hope you'll play nice with her as well.
Sure!
Okay, then.
See you, Suetsugi-san.
I'll see you after school.
S-Sure!
Wait, what?
Kobeni, what happened?!
...No, nothi—
She got dirt in her eye.
There's dirt in her adorable eye!
Dirt in her eye?
I'm gonna kill it.
You're overreacting!
That means the school
isn't being kept clean enough.
Oh, I know.
We need to have cleanup
time once every hour.
Okay. I'll bring it up
during the next meeting.
Please don't abuse your powers.
Don't worry!
Ugh, Benio.
This will help the school
in the long run.
Here's my chance to
take a weird picture of her.
She really goes crazy
when she's with Kobeni.
Plus, we'd all feel a lot better
if the school was nice and tidy.
Here we go.
Don't you agree, Mashiro-tan?
She found me!
What's this?
Oh my.
Pictures of me?
N-No, that's not it!
Give it back!
What's with that look?!
I knew it. You meant "yes"
every time you said "no".
You've got it completely wrong!
Konoha!
Niko-chan.
Huh? What's wrong?
Benio-sama said to play nice
with her pipsqueak sister.
Right.
They do say that fighting
is a sign that you get along.
We don't get along!
That's not even the issue!
But why can't you all just get along?
You, Mashiro-chan, and Kobeni-chan.
...Her sister...
...I wonder why she started crying...
Here's your chiffon cake.
Thank you very much!
It's so light and fluffy!
We've got plenty.
Oh my, that looks delicious.
...Mashiro-tan...
Go away.
Oh, right.
Here you go.
You can have this.
What is it?
It looked like you wanted
pictures of me, so here you go.
I told you that you
...had the wrong idea...
Benio
Yonomori
Did she come up with
that autograph herself?
Like this, maybe?
I almost got Suetsugi-san
in trouble by crying.
I need to apologize.
I mean, you wouldn't be
doing right by him otherwise.
Oh, wh-what's up?
I was wondering if you
had any matchsticks.
Hey, I made some cake.
Do you want a slice?
It's not too sweet.
Um... how is it?
Oh, I guess if it's not
too sweet then it's good.
...Hey, about the whole fiancé thing...
I didn't want you to
tell anyone because
I didn't want any rumors spreading
...or people making fun of us...
...So, um...
It's not that I don't want
...to be engaged to you...
...Well, it's... um...
She's saying she loves you too.
You sure are slow.
Can I have another slice?
Isn't that nice?
It's finally here. Her lovey-dovey side.
Th-That's not it!
Congratulations!!
Lovey-dovey time
So, what happens now?
This is really good news.
It basically means you've leveled up.
Leveled up?
In what?
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're so big, I didn't see you.
She couldn't see me because I'm big?
What the heck's up with her?
Anyway, White Day's coming up.
Here's your chance to
show off the man that you are!
Kobeni gave you chocolate
on Valentine's day, right?
Now you need to get her something
that knocks it out of the park!
sou desu curry wa daikoubutsu desu
Yes, curry is my favorite
tada yoku wo iwasete moraereba
But if I may be a bit greedy
amakuchi ga iindeshou
You prefer it mild, don't you?
mou nebaneba datte mo mochiron
Oh, but sticky food is fine by me too
zenzen heiki de taberaremasu
I can eat it, no problem
You don't like it, do you?
nigate nan dana
mou mitame wa chokotto chikkoi desu ga
Sure, I may look a bit on the smaller side
But I'm a proper sister-in-law
kore demo shikkari kojuuto datte shimasu
Look at you, pushing yourself (Yes!)
senobi shicchatte (yes!)
You can handle cooking, cleaning, and laundry just fine
ryouri mo souji mo sentaku mo daijoubu desu
sore ni anzangata desushi
And you've got great child-bearing hips
ki ni shiteru noni
Hey, I'm conscious of that
ie de wa annani annan nanoni
You're so crazy at home
Did you brainwash the people at school?
ittai douiu sennoujutsu desu ka
shitto shichatte mou (more!)
Aww, don't be jealous (More!)
shinpai da toka riyuu wo tsukete
We make excuses, saying we're worried about you
And now we've finally snuck into your heart
chakkari to ima sennyuu seikou
Once we get close to each other
nakayoku nattara
And we have to be frank
uchiakenakya demo
Will we still be able to understand
aimai na koto
rikai dekiru kana
What's left unsaid?
sorya maa oyatsu toka
My love for snacks and other things
kodomoppoi desu ga
May make me seem childish
But will you still be my friend forever?
sore demo zutto nakayokushite kuremasuka
That's
when I
remem-
bered...
...That's when I remembered...
House-
wife
stuff?!
that
the milk
in the
fridge
expires
today!
that the milk in the fridge expires today!
Housewife stuff?!
...That's when I remembered...
Where'd
you
come
from?!
That's
when I
remem-
bered...
Where'd you come from?!
N
o
!!
that
Mashiro-tan's
panties have
two kitties
on them!
that Mashiro-tan's panties have two kitties on them!
Noooo!!
Next Time
Looking Up The Term "Lovey-Dovey Side"
Next Time: Looking Up The Term "Lovey-Dovey Side".