Mankanshoku?
Hey!
Why's the underachiever
wearing an Ultima Uniform?
What's the meaning of this, Iori?
Right now, our top priority is
to increase our combat potential.
Mankanshoku showed the greatest increase
in parameters compared to her base state.
It was the most logical conclusion.
Iori, I think you set a new
personal speed record on that one.
Yeah. This will be the last set
of Ultima Uniforms I ever make,
so I'm going to give it everything I have!
Anyway, we're busy. Talk to you later.
Hey!
Seven-Hundred-Plus-299-Strong
Super Suction Saver!
SEVEN-HUNDRED-PLUS-299-STRONG
SUPER SUCTION SAVER
Savor this severe savior!
Hey!
What are you dawdling for?
Haven't you guys
fought naked all this time?
And look at you now.
You call yourselves nudists?!
...I don't think we ever said we were...
...but we can't let Mankanshoku fight alone....
Let's go.
Eat this!
IN HEAVEN'S STEAD, WE SMITE CLOTHING
Don't you get full of yourselves now,
Honnouji Academy brats!
EPISODE 23
IMITATION GOLD
unmei no ito wo tachikitta sono saki ni
It all begins when we sever the threads of fate
senobi shiteitanda
I was trying to be someone I'm not
kutsuzure darake no
In a cramped world
With no breathing room
semai sekai de
runway wo aruku
As I walked down my runway
egao no uragawa
I thought I'd concealed it
kakushita tsumori de
Behind the smile that masked my face
dakedo itsumo kimi ni wa
But it doesn't work on you
minukarete shimatte ite
You always see through my facade
Nobody's ever unraveled me like this before
konna no wa hajimete de
tomadou kedo
I don't know what to do
hoka no dare ni mo kikonasenai
Nobody else can pull these outfits off
nandaka wakannai
A somewhat ambiguous fever
atsusa ga mune wo kogasu kara
Threatens to burn our hearts away
unmei no ito taguriyoseta sono saki ni
It all begins once we rein in the threads of fate
ima atarashii yoake ga kuru
A new day will dawn for us
We must be one in spirit
omoi wa kitto hitotsu
I figured out why Harime Nui
couldn't regenerate her arms.
The Sword Scissor and
Bakuzan can sever Life Fibers,
but the powerful kind begin regenerating
immediately after they're cut.
However, cutting them from
both sides at the same time
lets you sever the regenerating
Life Fibers in succession.
This is the true power of
Dr. Matoi's Sword Scissors.
SWORD
SCISSORS
Hang on.
...That means twin Bakuzans can...
...have the same effect, yes....
Thank Ragyou for
breaking Bakuzan in half.
No.
You're the ones who deserve the
gratitude for turning it into two blades.
Oh my.
Since when did you get into the
whole positive reinforcement thing?
Ryuuko.
Yeah.
I see it!
Detecting a high-energy response
from the original Life Fiber's core.
That must be where it's holding all the
people it took captive for their energy.
We can stop it in its tracks
if we take out that part.
But she'll be lying in wait for us, huh?
Ragyou!
How dare you force me into
an outfit I didn't want to wear!
Now it's my turn!
I'm gonna strip you of everything!
Dear me.
That's not how a
seventeen-year-old girl should be talking.
What?
I should reforge you two
from the ground up.
...Is that...
This sword is an ultra-hard Life Fiber.
It served as the basis for both
the Sword Scissors and Bakuzan.
The original Life Fiber
is everything in one.
The beginning and the end
both reside within it.
I will not let you place your
dirty feet upon this sacred being.
Let me show you what one can do
when they surrender themselves to clothing.
Blade Gale!
Whirlwind Edge!
She was never gonna go
down without a fight, huh?
But we can't fall here!
Then we should head
straight for that fatass!
Fool.
Ryuuko!
I bet the rest of you are planning to
destroy the transmitter at Honnouji Academy,
...but let me tell you...
It won't be that easy!
Here, Mako.
Thanks, Mom!
All right!
Croquette power: all charged up!
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
ON A FULL STOMACH
HEAD-ON BATTLE!
Is she eating while fighting?
Our croquettes can be
super effective, you know.
Guts, guts!
Now bring it on!
Stand back!
What's going on?!
It's headed this way.
It changed directions?
Don't tell me it wants to
swallow the Naked Sun whole!
Is it still not done consuming humans?
...Like I've been saying...
Try as you might,
you can't stop us!
Fire the Nudist Cannons!
Medics!
Right away!
Leave it to us! There!
All done!
That's too many bandages, dear.
Mako can't move now.
Oh my God!
You okay, Sis?
I'm fine.
You sure don't look it.
There are too many of them.
But we still have to fight!
You can't keep going!
But I can't fall here!
I have to keep this ship safe!
...Ryuuko said...
that this ship was her whole world!
She said nothing of the sort!
The Ryuuko in my heart said so!
Mako.
Even now, she's beckoning
to me from across the river!
Uh, I think you're in grave peril.
Your opinion is invalid!
Don't push yourself, Mankanshoku.
For an underachiever,
you sure did well.
But it's our job to take it from here.
Now, then.
Shall we debut Iori's
last ever Ultima Uniforms?
Three-Star Ultima Uniforms:
Final Form!
Blade Regalia:
BLADE
REGALIA
WONDROUS
ENLIGHTENMENT
Wondrous Enlightenment!
Symphony Regalia:
FINAL MOVEMENT
SYMPHONY
REGALIA
Final Movement!
Probe Regalia:
TRUTH DETERMINATION
PROBE
REGALIA
Truth Determination!
Shackle Regalia:
SHACKLE REGALIA
EGO
BURST
Ego Burst!
The Honnouji Four Devas'
Supreme War Regalia!
SUPREME
WAR
REGALIA
Snake!
Dog!
Monkey!
Toad!
Supreme Smackdown!
SUPREME
SMACKDOWN!
Amazing!
That's our Four Devas!
Showed up fashionably late, eh?
Sheesh. You girls are so dimwitted.
No matter how much they resist,
humans are meant to submit to Life Fibers.
Hell no!
The Life Fibers induced the evolution
of this planet's intelligent life.
Clothing made beasts
evolve into humans,
just like how people fatten livestock.
Did you just call us livestock?
And as people consume livestock,
Life Fibers consume humans.
As beings that stand
atop Earth's food chain,
they're only doing what's
expected of them, no?
That doesn't mean we should
let them do as they please!
People have wills of their own!
Big words from a pig in human clothing.
That "will" you mention
will soon be gone.
Your last bastion is almost within reach!
This is bad, Ryuuko!
The ship's in big trouble!
I know.
Satsuki!
You think we can't do anything?
We'll see about that!
Finishing Move:
Thread Stripper!
Perish.
Ryuuko!
Ryuuko! Ryuuko!
Curse you,
Ragyou!
Your resistance is futile.
It was only with Ryuuko's help,
and her Life Fiber Synchronization,
that you were able to
stand against me at all.
You and that imitation Godrobe
aren't even fit to tie my shoelaces.
You sad little bitch.
You should know your place.
The only thing you're good for is lending
your lonely little sister a shoulder to cry upon.
On your way to Hell together, that is.
Sure, I might be an imitation,
but looking down on imitations
can come back to bite you.
Ridiculous.
What can you do
this late in the game?
Right now? I can buy us some time.
I am but a decoy!
Blade Gale!
Ryuuko?
Back then... Don't tell me
she deflected my blade
and jumped into the ocean
before I cut her in half!
Exactly.
She'd let you think you killed her,
regenerate her injured
body parts while in the water,
and then take out
the original Life Fiber.
That was the idea she came up with.
I hope you regret wasting
precious time boasting to me, the decoy,
Kiryuuin Ragyou!
Impertinent wench!
...You...
My arm is every bit as hard as Bakuzan.
Know that I, Gamagoori Ira,
am Lady Satsuki's living shield!
Auntie Ragyou,
just look at how much
li'l Nonon has grown!
Enhance your Ultima Uniform all you want.
A blind man's sword
will never strike me.
I have to go all-out against you, Director.
My eyes have been opened!
That's where the
"enlightenment" comes from!
WONDROUS
ENLIGHTENMENT
Here you go, Lady Satsuki!
BAKUZAN-GAKO
BAKUZAN-KOURYU
Thanks, Inumuta.
We won't be able to
withstand one more!
Really?
I'm out of cards to play, but nudists always
have an ace or two up their non-existent sleeves.
I-It is as you say.
Batten down the hatches!
Hey, what's the big idea?
...Wait, you can't be...
That's exactly right.
I'm going to use the
Naked Sun's final trump card:
the Great Naked Blade!
So we're using this blade
to strip that gourd down?
Sounds good!
GREAT
NAKED
BLADE
We're here, Ryuuko!
This is the core!
Let's go.
Double-Edged Decapitation Mode!
DOUBLE-EDGED
DECAPITATION
MODE
DOUBLE-EDGED
DECAPITATION
MODE
DOUBLE-EDGED
DECAPITATION
MODE
DOUBLE-EDGED
DECAPITATION
MODE
Finishing Move:
Thread Stripper!
Status report!
Turbines One and Three
are out of commission!
Turbine Two is almost
out of energy as well!
Damn it.
Is this really all humanity can do?
Shit! This thing's too hard!
Ryuuko!
But I've still gotta do this!
I promised Mako!
This ship is Ryuuko's whole world.
That doesn't just go for
...the Ryuuko in my mind...
I'm sure the Ryuuko outside
feels the same way!
...I mean, each and every time...
she's always been there, waiting for me!
...So this ship...
Mr. Mikisugi!
The turbine's starting to move again!
In fact, it's rotating at incredible speed!
Just you wait, Ryuuko!
I'll catch up to you now!
Mako?
Is that you, Mako?
Ryuuko!
Mako! It's you, right?
...Everyone's...
Mako!
Everyone's here with me!
Ryuuko, I can feel your blood boiling!
It sure is!
Let's do this, Senketsu!
Sure!
...It can't be...
...The original Life Fiber couldn't have...
You look like you can't
comprehend what just happened.
That comes as no surprise.
After all, we are all
utterly incomprehensible!
You looked down on imitations,
but they've proved to be your downfall.
People do not live
for the sake of clothing!
Enough of your futile resistance!
Listen up, Honnouji Academy scum!
The show's not over yet!
Those Godrobes,
those silly Ultima Uniforms,
and you were all just the opening act.
The main event features the amazing
Grand Couturier and the most amazing supermodel
in an amazingly chic
and elegant fashion show!
Pay close attention!
Sorry to have kept
you waiting, Lady Ragyou.
Omnisilk Kouketsu is ready.
Well done, Nui.
It seems my foolish daughters
acted rather inappropriately with you.
Forgive me.
Ah, Lady Ragyou!
...Is this...
I can't replace the
Grand Couturier's delicate fingers,
but I can make you capable
of fighting some silly humans.
This planet will soon be
engulfed by Life Fibers,
so I don't need to
sew clothes anymore.
This is more than enough.
Your last ever design, eh?
I can't wait to find out
how it feels to wear.
Brilliantly done, Iori.
I'm amazed you managed to
recreate this many outfits.
I didn't just recreate them.
I powered them up!
I'd expect nothing less.
We've brought our latest
and greatest equipment as well.
We managed to take out
the original Life Fiber,
but Kiryuuin Ragyou's
still alive and kicking.
And now we're going to barge into
Honnouji Academy, destroy the transmitter,
and capture both
Ragyou and Harime Nui!
...Soroi...
Hot!
Your eyes are open now, but your
tongue still can't handle the heat, huh?
Oh, shut up!
Don't smash the cups.
We're not going off to die.
We're all coming back alive
to drink Soroi's tea again.
Isn't that right, Soroi?
I'll have the water
ready and boiled for you.
You don't need to come
if you don't want to, you know.
I've come too far for that.
...Sis...
Guts, guts!
Don't you worry.
If anything should happen to you,
I'll have the Kiryuuin Conglomerate
compensate us heavily.
Give it your all, but not your life.
Here you go. Croquettes.
Don't let your family's love go to waste.
Life a life happy enough
for the three of us.
You don't have to
worry about that, Satsuki.
This is the most incomprehensible
family in the entire world.
'Kay!
Mako's in your hands.
If anything goes wrong,
I'll wring every last penny out of you.
Got it?
I'll keep that in mind.
All right, then!
Let's go, Ryuuko, Lady Satsuki!
Yeah.
Life Fiber Synchronize:
Life Fiber Override:
Godrobe Senketsu!
Godrobe Junketsu!
GODROBE
JUNKETSU
ROBE
GOD
SENKETSU
It's time.
...We're going to take...
our academy back!
Yeah!
Guts!
dareka no sei ni shitara
I always took the easy way out
itsumo kantan dattanda
By pinning the blame on someone else
But a new day will never dawn on me that way
demo kitto sore ja zutto asu wa yattekonai
I was probably just really lazy
tabun tada no namakemono deshita
gomen ne
Sorry
Welcome to the runway of death,
Ryuuko.
This planet belongs to the Life Fibers.
You people cannot stop the genesis
of the Celestial Seed Cocoon Planet.
CELESTIAL SEED COCOON PLANET
We will stop it!
As Kiryuuin blood
courses through our veins,
it falls to us to overcome that destiny!
We already put the original
Life Fiber six feet under,
so quit trying to fight back.
Be careful, Ryuuko.
She's bad news.
This is on a whole different level
to what you've faced up to now.
There's nothing to be
afraid of, Senketsu.
Godrobes are so honest.
Behold!
Life Fiber Subjugate:
Omnisilk Kouketsu!
OMNISILK
KOUKETSU
Time for the finishing touches, Hououmaru.
Okay.
You shall know true fear,
my foolish girls!