Ryuuko!
Are you okay?!
This hurts like hell! It freakin' kills!
But it's just what I deserve for
acting like such a complete and utter fool!
I can't believe you're still alive
after severing your Life Fibers.
...However...
Nui's wounds healed!
So she's immortal too?
That's the power of the
Life Fibers within her body.
Throwing your Sword Scissor
at me was a mistake.
It wasn't enough to kill me,
and now they're both in my hands.
Go, Senketsu!
To Ryuuko!
Sure!
Too bad, Senketsu.
You're getting ripped to shreds again!
Not if I can help it!
Hey, I'm not your springboard!
Let's go, Ryuuko!
Life Fiber Synchronize!
EPISODE 22
TELL ME
HOW YOU FEEL
unmei no ito wo tachikitta sono saki ni
It all begins when we sever the threads of fate
I was trying to be someone I'm not
senobi shiteitanda
In a cramped world
kutsuzure darake no
semai sekai de
With no breathing room
runway wo aruku
As I walked down my runway
egao no uragawa
I thought I'd concealed it
Behind the smile that masked my face
kakushita tsumori de
But it doesn't work on you
dakedo itsumo kimi ni wa
minukarete shimatte ite
You always see through my facade
konna no wa hajimete de
Nobody's ever unraveled me like this before
tomadou kedo
I don't know what to do
hoka no dare ni mo kikonasenai
Nobody else can pull these outfits off
nandaka wakannai
A somewhat ambiguous fever
Threatens to burn our hearts away
atsusa ga mune wo kogasu kara
unmei no ito taguriyoseta sono saki ni
It all begins once we rein in the threads of fate
ima atarashii yoake ga kuru
A new day will dawn for us
We must be one in spirit
omoi wa kitto hitotsu
...Harime...
Oh? Did she just overwhelm
Harime with her spirit?
You can sit back and watch.
Aw, I went through all that trouble
fitting Junketsu to you,
but you're wearing
that lame outfit again?
I can't stand it!
Give it up.
I'm never gonna take
Senketsu off again.
Right now, Senketsu also has Satsuki
and Mako's blood flowing through him.
Compared to that monstrous
...Junketsu, he's much warmer...
and comfortable to wear!
Ryuuko!
Well said!
Hey, clothing isn't supposed to bawl!
I'd feel gross if you got all soggy!
You're letting all that
comfort go to waste!
Forgive me!
Why are you two playing friends?
It's so creepy I wanna hurl!
Don't you look down on us.
"Friends" is too limited a word.
The feelings I have for Mankanshoku Mako
and Senketsu aren't so easily described!
Who, me?
Yeah, that's right. A girl who's either weak
or really damn strong, but hell if I know which,
who barges into your damn mind
before you even know it,
and an outfit that laughs, cries,
and seriously worries about me.
These incomprehensible goofballs are
always giving everything they have to save me!
So I need to respond to their
incomprehensibility in kind!
You lot have only
one thing on your minds:
to turn this world
into one big Life Fiber.
Not on my watch, you won't.
The world's much better off being
full of these incomprehensible folk!
I have no idea what you're talking about,
but you're absolutely right!
Keep your mouth shut
if you don't have a clue.
Aw, jeez. This is why I hate humans.
Fine! Take your incomprehensibility
to Hell with you!
...Dad's Sword Scissors...
are finally back where they belong!
Hmph.
Maybe I should have
...the guys you're trying to protect...
attack you instead!
Have a taste of my mental refitting!
That's not gonna work!
Too bad!
That was a decoy!
This is the end, Ryuuko!
For you, maybe.
My arms!
Do you have any idea
how much my arms are worth?!
I'm the Grand Couturier, damn it!
That's exactly why I cut them off.
Just kidding!
Cut them off all you want!
They'll be back to normal in no time!
Take that.
And that.
They can prevent the
restoration of Life Fibers?
Those scissors are that powerful?
Give it up, Harime Nui!
This can't be happening.
You seriously piss me off.
Every last one of you!
You piss me off!
Hououmaru!
You're not getting away!
Senketsu Gale!
Huh?
What?
Knock it off, Ryuuko.
You've lost quite a lot of blood.
Chasing after them would be too risky.
...But these bastards are still...
Oh, Hououmaru.
She acted far too hastily
in rescuing Harime.
Exactly.
This is what you'd call
a golden opportunity.
They're offering our comrades and
Life Fibers to us on a silver platter!
That's right.
Now, stop dawdling.
Get to work, Four Devas!
Gimme those!
Seven-Plus-Two-Strong
Super Suction Saver!
SUPER
SUCTION
SAVER
SEVEN
PLUS TWO
STRONG
...You guys are...
the Tennis Club's Hakodate,
TENNIS CLUB
CAPTAIN
HAKODATE OMIKO
the Boxing Club's Fukuroda,
BOXING CLUB CAPTAIN
FUKURODA TAKAHARU
and so on and so forth!
YAGURUMA
KUSANOSUKE
OTTE TATAMU
FUGUHARA AIZENBOU
OKURAHAMA MAIMU
FORMER ACROBATICS CLUB
Medics!
At your service!
Tend to the people we rescued!
Roger that!
Come on, Mankanshoku family!
Let's actually help people for once!
Not like I can steal anything
from them when they're butt naked.
Cut it out, Matarou!
Aight, aight!
Guts, guts!
Sewing Club, collect all the stray Life Fibers
and get them to the lab at once!
Remaining:
4 hours
1 sec
0.5 sec
Complete
Collection complete.
Let me off!
I didn't ask for your help!
I haven't lost yet!
Calm down, Grand Couturier.
What can you do in that state?
Right now, you should be focusing on
completing the Shinra-Kouketsu.
And yet you shamefully lost your arms
in a battle you didn't have to take part in.
How are you going to
explain this to Lady Ragyou?
Explain this? Who, me?
You've gotta be kidding me.
Head to Honnouji Academy at once.
I shall complete the Shinra-Kouketsu.
Oh, and you're going to
pay for mouthing off at me.
Keep that in mind.
So long as the Shinra-Kouketsu is completed,
it matters not what happens to me.
What should we do with Junketsu?
Keep it locked up for now.
Are you sure we
shouldn't just get rid of it?
The battle is far from over.
You're planning to put it on again?
Do you really think
you can truly wear that monster?
I won't make the same mistake twice.
Big words from someone who
couldn't even synchronize with Senketsu.
Stop it, Ryuuko.
Satsuki put her life
on the line to stop you.
And what of it?
That's not enough to write off how
high-handed she's been up until now.
What do you want from me?
Let me punch you.
Ryuuko.
If you can take an all-out punch
from me and remain standing,
then I'll admit that you're
strong enough to fight by my side.
You're being unreasonable, Ryuuko!
Any normal human would die if you attacked
them seriously in your synchronized form.
But "Lady Kiryuuin Satsuki"
is no ordinary human, is she?
Very well. Hit me.
Our enemy is Kiryuuin Ragyou.
If I go down here, then I stand
no chance of winning this battle anyway.
I'll show you that I can
take that fist of yours.
Prove to me that you're
not all bark and no bite.
Here I come.
Gamagoori!
Stay out of this, dammit!
What is with you guys?!
You dare insult me, Matoi?
Say what?!
Is that an "all-out punch" to you?!
That's right!
Ridiculous!
Why are we still alive, then?
I thought no normal human could
survive if you attacked them seriously.
It's your damn fault for butting in!
That's outrageous!
You held back because
someone butted in?
A woman like you has absolutely
no right to hit Lady Satsuki!
Don't you snap back at me!
No, we're genuinely pissed off!
There's no way in hell we'd let such a
half-hearted punch hit Lady Satsuki!
What are you guys doing?
Our faces belong to Lady Satsuki.
Our limbs, too, belong to her.
If it's for her sake, we'll gladly be
smashed to bits or chopped to pieces!
But keep in mind that these limbs have a
mind of their own and can really take a beating.
We, the Four Devas of Honnouji,
are Lady Satsuki's greatest weapon
and her strongest shield!
If you wish to hit her,
you'll have to go through us first!
That said, it won't be easy
to bring us to our knees!
What is wrong with you guys?!
You're utterly incomprehensible!
So you have a bunch of incomprehensible
fools protecting you, just like me.
Sure looks like it.
In order to beat Ragyou, I have to use
...all humans as pawns to further my goals...
or so I used to think.
That went for you, too.
From the moment you
showed up dressed in Senketsu,
I tried to train you so you would
be of use against Ragyou's army.
By having you come after me,
your father's "killer",
I tested both Senketsu's
strength and your own.
If you could stay in control of yourself
without letting your Godrobe consume you,
then you would definitely prove
useful in my coup against Ragyou.
I thought I could lead you into helping the cause
against her without ever telling you the truth.
...You bitch...
But I was sorely mistaken.
At the end of the day, I was
doing the same thing as Ragyou.
Of course I couldn't defeat her that way.
...The biggest fool of all...
was me.
...Satsuki...
But now I know that the world
is not a piece of cloth.
It's filled to the brim with some
pretty incomprehensible things,
and that's what makes it beautiful.
Please, fight alongside me to
protect that beautiful world, Ryuuko!
Man, even your apologies are overblown.
I don't even feel like
hitting you anymore.
I have people I wanna protect, too,
so I agree it's high time
we stopped that mother of ours.
Now that you've made up,
let's eat!
Whoa! Mrs. Mankanshoku's croquettes!
Yep. They're packed with all kinds
of incomprehensible things!
Come now, dig in!
Yeah! If you want incomprehensible,
you've come to the right family!
Try some, Lady Satsuki!
...This...
Isn't it great?
It really is.
Please wash down
your meal with some tea.
Ryuuko.
That really moved you, didn't it?
I'm talking about what Satsuki said.
Man, you're one nosy outfit!
You should've just honestly said so.
Would you shut up already?
Sheesh. There's not a
cute bone in your body.
I see how it is, Senketsu.
You've been lonely 'cos you had
no one to talk to all this time, right?
That's why you're
running your mouth now.
Of course not!
I don't get lonely that easily!
All right, all right.
Run your mouth while you still can.
Soon enough, we won't
have any time for that.
She'll be here any moment now.
It's me.
Oh? Ryuuko did?
Yes. Have Nui hurry up with her work.
What troublesome girls.
Did I perhaps sew the
Marionette Threads all wrong?
Matoi Ryuuko!
Kiryuuin Satsuki!
...I swear... I swear...
You're gonna pay!
What I just shot into Junketsu was
Lady Satsuki's blood, Ryuuko's blood,
and a dash of Senketsu's Life Fibers.
So you're trying to forcibly dye Junketsu in
Lady Satsuki's colors by using Senketsu's powers?
Rather than force my arms through an outfit I can
never truly wear, it'd be better to just tailor it to my needs.
It's too late to care about
appearances now.
The only thing on your
mind is victory, huh?
Looks like you've shed
everything unnecessary.
You're a full-fledged
Nudist in spirit, too.
Iori, is there anything useful here?
You're ignoring me?!
Rest assured. Our collection of Life Fibers
went much better than expected.
I will now begin producing
Ultima Uniforms.
Will you be able to do it by yourself?
I'm all the help I need.
Three-Star Ultima Uniform:
ORDER
REGALIA
THREE-STAR ULTIMA UNIFORM
Order Regalia!
Kiryuuin Ragyou's ultimate objective
is to turn every last human into Life Fibers
and cover this planet with them.
It's called the "Celestial Seed
Cocoon Planet" plan.
CELESTIAL SEED
COCOON PLANET
Every REVOCS Inc. product
is fitted with Life Fibers.
Those Life Fibers will awaken
once the signal is sent out,
turning the helpless masses into energy sources
and transforming all clothes into COVERS.
Then seven billion COVERS will rise up into the
stratosphere and completely engulf this planet.
Is she trying to dress up the Earth?
That's absurd.
I'd heard that she was trying to
turn humanity into Life Fibers,
but I had no idea her plan
was so massive in scale.
But for what purpose?
Life Fibers are a lifeform
that wander across space.
When they reach a planet
inhabited by intelligent life,
they have it evolve to the point where
it's a suitable energy source for them.
After that, they turn them into
Fibers and cover up the planet,
and then turn the planet itself into an
energy source by causing it to explode,
using that momentum to
spray new seed across space.
That is how they have been able to
propagate throughout the universe.
Man, that sure is one bombastic plan.
Oh, man. He did it again.
How are you so nonchalant about blurting out
things that everyone else is trying not to say?
You Northern Kanto monkeys and your
lack of tact really drives me up the wall.
If you insult Northern Kanto
one more time, I'll turn you into soup!
Good grief. What is with
this incoherent prattle?
Knock it off, you two!
Do not forget that you are
in the presence of Lady Satsuki!
Let them be, Gamagoori.
When I hear you guys
mouth off at each other,
it makes me feel like
I'm finally back home.
Yes, ma'am!
All right.
I've managed to hack into
REVOCS' communications satellite.
Here comes some live footage
of the original Life Fiber.
Though, well, it's so heavily encrypted
that the only thing we can use is the camera.
Ragyou.
The original Life Fiber is headed
toward Honnouji Academy.
Our prediction was right on the money.
Honnouji Academy?
That's right.
Once the original Life Fiber is attached to the
massive transmitter installed at Honnouji Academy,
it'll send out the signal that will
turn all of mankind into Life Fibers.
You mean we need to destroy that
transmitter in order to put a stop to her plans?
Oh, there's just one thing
we weren't expecting.
What is it?
We've got incoming!
They're about to hit the ship!
Seriously, could you not report
these things at the last second?!
Mr. Mikisugi.
"Mr."?!
I'd like you to take charge
of our strategy from now on.
...What are you...
I will go with Ryuuko to stop Ragyou.
Someone who battles on the frontlines
is not fit to be a commander.
I see.
Did you get that, Four Devas?
Yes, ma'am!
All right!
We'll focus on destroying the
transmitter at Honnouji Academy.
Satsuki and Ryuuko will keep Kiryuuin Ragyou
and the original Life Fiber at bay.
This will be a two-pronged operation!
Battle stations, everyone!
There you go again,
ordering people around.
Aren't you going?
What about you?
I have no choice but to go.
Then hurry up and change.
Lady Ryuuko,
please take care of your sister.
Gotcha.
L-Let's go,
...S-S-Si...
You don't need to force yourself
to act like my sister.
Your blood's flowing through
Junketsu right now.
That's enough for me.
That so?
Yeah.
...You girls...
Save the waterworks for later.
Let's do this.
Life Fiber Override:
Life Fiber Synchronize:
Godrobe Junketsu!
Godrobe Senketsu!
GODROBE
JUNKETSU
ROBE
GOD
SENKETSU
Ryuuko.
Yeah.
Senketsu Gale!
SENKETSU
GALE
Grab on.
No need to help.
Junketsu Whirlwind!
JUNKETSU
WHIRLWIND
You gained my abilities as well?
Way to go!
Let's make haste.
Okay.
All right. Setting course
for Honnouji Academy!
Satsuki, the ship!
They were underwater too?
The hell is this?
Looks like it's a
combat-specialized COVERS.
This one's tough!
Honnouji Academy Fight Club Captain,
Mankanshoku Mako,
back in action!
ACTION
FIGHT CLUB-SPEC
TWO-STAR UNIFORM
MANKANSHOKU MAKO
CAPTAIN
BACK IN
Don't worry, Ryuuko.
I'll keep this ship safe!
My monotonous everyday life
kurikaesu mainichi ga
Took on a new hue
totsuzen iro wo kaeru
A part of me always wished for that to happen
sonna koto dokka nozonde itanda kedo ne
But when it actually did
iza to naru to
I was too scared to act
okubyoumono deshita
That's a secret, okay?
himitsu ne
Trembling alone
hitori furuete
I miss you so much
soshite kimi ni aitakute
zutto mikata da yo nante ieta nara
If only I could tell you that I'll always be on your side
muteki
We could be invincible
When we take flight, we'll do so together
sou sa tobitatsu toki wa futari de
tachimukai
We'll make a stand
I want to keep smiling
kakaekirenai okubyou ni
tsuppattatte waratte itai
Even when my cowardice freezes me in place
Every little thing will come together
hitori kiri zutsu ga awasatte
ookina chikara ni naru yo
To give us great strength
ima nee kanjita
That's how I feel right now