This Sword Scissor was left behind
by the person who killed my father!
Now, you'll tell me who
this scissor belongs to,
Kiryuuin Satsuki!
You said your name
is Matoi Ryuuko?
I see.
You're Matoi Isshin's daughter?
You know who my father is?!
You're bleeding too much, Ryuuko.
Isn't that what you want?
At this rate of blood loss,
you will lose consciousness
in five minutes.
Don't sound so calm about it!
We'll talk about this at length the
next time we meet, Kiryuuin Satsuki!
Don't let her escape! After her! After her!
Don't bother.
B-But, milady!
She'll be back.
Leave her be until then.
Lady Satsuki...
You're as dazzling as always.
Your tea, Miss.
A girl in a Godrobe, eh?
EPISODE 2
SWOONINGLY
SEXY
TLNOTE: MORE GOODER FONT COMING EVENTUALLY.
dareka ga katteni kimetara kimeru you na
This is a world that is at someone's beck and call
kyou wo nugisutete
I'll break free of its shackles
hadashi de hashitte iku
And sprint toward my goal
machigattatte
Even if I lose my way
korondatte
Or trip and fall
surimuita itami mo
Those wounds will still create
original na ashita ni naru
An original future for me
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
I hold my destiny in my own hands
chikai ga hikari ni natte
And it shines ever so brightly
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
So until the day I reach you
naiteru hima nante nai darou
I don't have the time to sit around crying
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
My burning passion pours out from within me
yozora de kagayaki dasu
And shines like a star in the night sky
umarete kita imi ga
I think I now understand
wakatta ki ga shita
Why I was born
negaigoto ga zenbu kono te de
I'll make all of my dreams come true
kanaeru
With my own hands
Oh, wow! It's a nearly naked chick!
You freakin' pervert!
You think you can make a move on Ryuuko, Kantou Vagabond and Guitar Case Drifter?
My scissor! My scissor's gone!
Ryuuko!
Thanks! Be careful, Mako!
This perv tried to—
Dad, what do you think you're doing?
"Dad"?
Dad?!
I'm so sorry!
Wow, I really felt that one!
You pack a mean punch, Miss!
Of course she does!
I owe her for saving my life!
MANKANSHOKU
BARAZOU
She looked like a total badass,
swinging that scissor around half-naked!
Nobody in their right mind
could dress like that, though!
MANKANSHOKU
MATAROU
Bite me! It's a long story, all right?
That hurt, damn it!
I was the one who carried you here!
If belting my husband or
Matarou makes you feel better,
then please, belt away!
MANKANSHOKU
SUKUYO
BACK-ALLEY DOCTOR
MANKANSHOKU
How did I—
Daddy treated you!
You'd never guess it,
but he's a back-alley doctor.
MANKANSHOKU
If you compare the number of people he's killed to those he's saved,
he's killed more!
That's not a good thing.
Don't worry about it.
The dead ones don't sue you.
Oh, right!
I know it's nothing fancy,
but eat all you like!
Go ahead, Ryuuko! Don't be shy!
It's unidentifiable stuff
made into croquettes
and unidentifiable
stuff in miso soup!
Oh, you! I'll have you know I use
only non-poisonous ingredients.
Better dig in before I eat it all!
Down, Guts! Your food is out there!
GUTS
We call him Guts 'cause
he's such a greedy guts!
You were suffering from a spot of anemia, little lady, so eat up!
Don't just sit there, eat!
The masses... Fools, all of them.
They're pigs in human clothing,
domesticated by the establishment.
They must be governed. By me,
Kiryuuin Satsuki, and Honnouji Academy.
It is we who shall pave
the way to humanity's future.
The Ultima Uniforms are
weapons to that end.
The uniforms that this country
makes its students wear
are based on military uniforms.
The raised collars on boys'
uniforms come from the army.
Girls' sailor uniforms are
just that—naval uniforms.
This country is a state that chose to make its youths wear military uniforms during their education.
In which case, we at Honnouji Academy
shall treat our uniforms as combat uniforms.
They shall be symbols of our control over the pigs in human clothing.
You of the Sewing Club are the chosen elite
of our Human Conquest and Liberation Project.
Carry out your work
with the utmost care.
Thank you for your kind words.
Tennis Club Captain, Hakodate Omiko,
Third Year Class D, reporting as ordered.
How are preparations proceeding
for the Hokkaido interleague match?
Milady. All club members are devoting themselves entirely to training.
Those ursine hicks from the north will
learn down to the marrow of their bones
the might of Honnouji Academy and Lady Kiryuuin Satsuki.
This is armed suppression in the guise of an interleague match.
If the Tennis Club succeeds, our dominance of northern Japan will be complete.
Don't fail us.
I understand.
This is a Tennis-Spec Athleticism-
Augmenting Two-Star Ultima Uniform.
A gift from Lady Satsuki.
At last, a Two-Star
Ultima Uniform of my very own!
Thank you, milady!
Carry out your mission.
Without fail, milady!
The entire Tennis Club shall
pull together, redouble its efforts,
and train even harder
for the interleague match!
Why do you not wear
an Ultima Uniform, Miss?
This sword is more
than sufficient for me.
Are you saying no uniform
is worthy of you?
Hey, are you awake?
What the hell are you, Senketsu?
Quit your quibbling!
Fine. I'll make you wear me by force!
Wh-What kind of kinky outfit is this?!
This is me.
Don't be so matter-of-fact about it!
Get off me! Come off, damn it!
Anyway, just get away from me,
you perverted sailor uniform!
Where'd that power come from?
This power is yours and mine.
I drank your blood and awakened.
Whenever you put me on—
whenever I am worn by you—
that power will be manifested.
What are you?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You just finished calmly
explaining how you worked!
I am able to explain phenomena that are occurring right now.
However, there is much
that I do not know.
My memory...
Yes, in your language, you would say that there are gaps in my memory.
Don't you remember anything?
I do know that the man
who constructed me
had a beard, an eye patch,
and wore a white lab coat.
He was stooped, wore sandals,
held a cane in one hand, and had a mouse.
That could be only
one man—my father!
Father?
Yeah, Matoi Isshin. He's my father.
I'm Ryuuko.
My father made you?
But if I have you,
I might be able to beat them!
You're coming with me
for a while, Senketsu.
"Senketsu"?
It'll be a pain if I don't
have anything to call you.
And since my blood awakened you,
your name can be Senketsu—"fresh blood".
SENKETSU
"FRESH BLOOD"
Just you wait, Kiryuuin Satsuki!
Ryuuko! Wake up!
We have to hurry and eat breakfast!
If I'm late for school again,
I'll be expelled!
There's a pretty dramatic difference between the rich and poor here.
Well, this city is ruled
by Lady Satsuki.
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
Top-tier students get placed in the exclusive residential areas,
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
ONE-STAR
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
while lower-tier students
like us get the slums.
TWO-STAR
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
THREE-STAR
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
Your position at school also
determines where you live?
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
HONNOUJI ACADEMY
Yep! Pretty straightforward, huh?
Oh, that reminds me.
Ryuuko, Mom said that
—if you need a place to—
Mom said that—
if you don't have a place to stay—
you can stay—
with us—
She's already filed the paperwork!
Is this really the time
for living arrangements?!
Hey, what's the big idea?!
Ah, you're the transfer student
who was rude to Lady Satsuki, as I recall.
Stay out of this.
I'm Hakodate Omiko,
captain of the Girls' Tennis Club.
GIRLS' TENNIS CLUB
CAPTAIN
HAKODATE
OMIKO
Club member Mankanshoku Mako
has failed to fulfill her club obligations,
and as such, is now being purged.
What did Mako do wrong?
She skipped yesterday's club practice.
Our rule is that anyone who fails to come to practice must suffer the 110 Million Cannonball Serve.
An outsider has no right to
complain about internal club policies.
Yesterday? Mako was being
held hostage yesterday!
Of course she didn't come
to your stupid practice!
The issue is that she got herself
taken hostage without permission.
Begin.
Cut that out, damn it!
Go on ahead, Mako!
You'll be expelled if you're late, right?
Yeah!
Thanks a bunch!
I'll see you later, 'kay?
Yup!
So, you're saying that
you will take us on?
I owe her for a meal
and a night's lodging.
How amusing.
Don't get too full of yourself just because
you defeated Fukuroda from the Boxing Club.
I'm gonna make quick work of
those Ultima Uniforms of yours!
Let's do it, Senketsu!
Hey! Hey, let's do this, Senketsu!
Hey, what's wrong with you?!
Are you kidding me?!
She's talking to her clothes...
How utterly pathetic.
Wake up, damn it! Hey!
What's your problem?!
Die!
Screw you! There's a reason—
What, a total shutout?
No challenge whatsoever.
Oh, dear...
You awake, Ryuuko?
Wait, aren't you a teacher?
That's right.
I'm your homeroom teacher,
Mikisugi Aikurou.
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
Talk about your crazy
extracurricular lessons.
Hang on, you didn't
undress me, did you?!
That's right. I thought I would
...teach you a few things...
straight to your body.
You perverted son of a bitch!
Wait, what?! My body won't move!
Calm yourself.
What did you do?!
Anesthetic acupuncture.
You seem a little
hot-blooded at the moment,
so I thought I might
draw some of it for you.
No, don't! I hate needles!
Allow me to tell you why your
Godrobe didn't activate earlier.
More! Feed me more!
Feed me more blood!
You're awake, Senketsu?
Ryuuko?
Why didn't you wake up when I needed you, you dumbass?!
Now, now, calm down.
You understand now, right?
Understand what?
This Godrobe is
awakened by your blood.
What's this "Godrobe" thing
you keep talking about?
You mean this sailor uniform?
That's right.
It's a uniform constructed by your father,
Matoi Isshin, and its power surpasses that of the Ultima Uniforms.
Only someone who can master wearing this can fight against Kiryuuin Satsuki.
Who the hell are you?
You must prove to me that
you are worthy of that answer.
Come again?
The first order of business is the
Tennis Club Captain, Hakodate Omiko.
If you can't master this
Godrobe and defeat her,
you don't stand a chance
against Kiryuuin Satsuki.
Better get a move on.
It's almost time for afternoon classes.
Use this Crimson Glove from now on.
It will make it easier for
you to provide it with blood.
CRIMSON
GLOVE
Fine. I'll pound that tennis
club president into the dirt,
and then you're gonna tell me everything I want to know.
Looking good, Hakodate.
Thank you. It is all thanks to this Tennis-Spec Ultima Uniform I received from Lady Satsuki.
The Tennis Club shall
subjugate Hokkaido without fail.
What's that about?
We have an unmotivated club
member, so we are purging her.
Not so fast, people!
Ryuuko!
The transfer student...
You've come for another beating?
As if!
This time, I'm gonna
knock you all on your asses!
Let's do it, Senketsu!
That looks both painful and embarrassing, you masochistic exhibitionist!
Bite me! I'm not an exhibitionist!
Quit splitting hairs.
Let's begin! 110 Million Serve!
Fault! You're disqualified,
transfer student!
What?!
True, you evaded Hakodate's attack,
but slicing balls in half
is against the rules!
In other words, you've won
the fight but lost the match!
Listen up! What you're
standing on is a tennis court!
That means you can't say you've won
unless you win according to the rules of tennis!
Hey! Why are you
getting all picky now?
What about yesterday?
That was yesterday!
This is crazy!
—When we were boxing, we—
Doesn't matter! You're disqualified!
No, she won!
Ryuuko won! She won!
What?
Ryuuko rescued me!
She may have lost the match,
but she won at friendship!
Winning at friendship
means winning at life!
Listen...
If you're going to be like that,
you leave her no choice!
Ryuuko will win.
Even in tennis, even in tennis,
even in tennis, she'll win!
So, you're saying that
you want to face me,
Tennis Club Captain
Hakodate Omiko, in a tennis match?
Here! Do your best, Ryuuko!
All right, all right...
Let's do this!
Special rules!
The match is one game!
Decide who serves first!
I'm watching, Ryuuko!
She's a rookie. I'll let her serve.
I'll take you up on that, then!
I won't hold back!
Too weak!
She's fast!
Ryuuko, that was awesome!
Love-fifteen!
Not bad.
I'm just getting warmed up.
You're only just beginning to learn the might of the Tennis-Spec Athleticism-Augmenting
Two-Star Ultima Uniform
I received from Lady Satsuki!
Interesting!
That won't work this time!
Nice!
Love-thirty!
I knew you'd try that.
That's why I put a
special spin on my serve.
Ryuuko, you naughty girl!
Then I'll do the same!
Here we go!
Fault!
Oh, come on!
Double fault! Love-forty!
Ryuuko, this is your last shot!
What's the matter, transfer student?
Hurry up and serve!
Ryuuko, use the Sword Scissor!
Only the Sword Scissor
can withstand our strength!
SWORD
SCISSOR
Got it!
Mako! My scissor!
Catch!
...Right, then...
This should do it!
You can't be serious!
Faul—
It's all right.
Play along, Hakodate.
Show us all the power
of your Two-Star.
Yes, Milady!
As you wish!
Kiryuuin Satsuki, you're looking down on people and barking out orders, same as always.
It's creepy.
You're going to show me
just how much of that
Godrobe's power you can tap into.
...You bitch...
You know that this thing
is called a Godrobe?
Not so fast. Your opponent is over there.
I'm gonna use you as a live-fire exercise
to loosen up for the Hokkaido away series!
Let's do this, then!
On the court, you can
only count on yourself!
Nobody gets it!
"STRIPPED"
"Stripped" of the will to fight!
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
You did it, Ryuuko!
Oh, dear. It looks like
the match can't go on.
Don't get too full of yourself, bitch.
Wait, Sanageyama.
The winner of the match is that girl.
Lady Satsuki!
So, are you going to tell me?
Are you the woman with
the other Sword Scissor?
What?!
If you wish to know the answer,
you'll need to prove yourself!
Ryuuko, if you're going to fight,
you must win within two minutes.
Otherwise, you're going
to pass out again.
That's because you
drank too much blood!
SECRET
SWORD
Secret Sword Bakuzan.
BAKUZAN
This blade can cut even a Godrobe.
Its edge is even keener
than that scissor's.
...The pressure's incredible...
Her fighting spirit is amazing!
Mark my words!
Next time, I'll finish
this once and for all!
Let's go, Mako!
'Kay!
Forgive me, Milady.
I underestimated the transfer student.
Hakodate is demoted to a No-Star.
As for Hokkaido, set up an
interleague match with the Sumo Club.
As I expected, a Godrobe
is most formidable.
To think it could
...turn away my blade...
I shall remember this, Matoi Ryuuko.
chime ga naru mae ni
Before the bell rings
kokuu ni muketa
The adults' vacant stares
otonatachi no haiiro no me
Drift into empty space
tawai no nai kaiwa
The pointless conversations
togirenu no mama
Keep going on and on
sakamichi wo kudatteku
As I walk down the slope
nani wo suru demo naku
I have nothing to do
yuku ate sae mo naku
And nowhere to go
tada atashi ima wa ne
Right now, all I do
donna chuukoku mo mimi wo surinukeru
Is ignore any and all warnings
mada mada suki ni sasete
Because I still want to be free
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
To be an exemplary student
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
rojiura no nukemichi
And take the back alley
amai yuuwaku na michi
A path of sweet temptation
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you
PREVIEW
Kiryuuin Satsuki...
KIRYUUIN SATSUKI
Another owner of a Godrobe.
ANOTHER
GODROBE
Ryuuko and I are helpless
before that overwhelming power.
OVERWHELMING
RYUUKO AND I
HELPLESS
Can we win, Ryuuko?
MATOI RYUUKO
Next time on KILL la KILL, "Purity."
EPISODE 3 PURITY