Hey there, everyone!
Thanks for watching
KILL la KILL every week!
I'm Godrobe Senketsu,
a living sailor uniform that
loves ironing—no, being ironed.
Now, here's something that I'm sure
you've all been expecting for quite some time.
It's time for a recap episode!
RECAP
Matoi Ryuuko, a girl looking for the woman
with the Sword Scissor who killed her father,
KILLED HER FATHER
runs into Kiryuuin Satsuki,
the student council president at Honnouji Academy.
KIRYUUIN SATSUKI
Satsuki was planning to take over all of the nation's
schools using Ultima Uniforms fitted with Life Fibers
that awakened special powers within humans,
but Ryuuko gained the power to oppose Satsuki
and her cronies by meeting me, Godrobe Senketsu.
GODROBE SENKETSU
The Boxing Club, the Tennis Club,
the traps devised by the Disciplinary Committee,
the Gardening Club, the Rakugo Club,
the 100 Poets Club, the Knife Throwing Club,
and so on and so forth.
After the defeat of all these clubs
came the Naturals Election.
The time had come to
take on the Four Devas.
Against all odds, Ryuuko defeated
Gamagoori Ira, Inumuta Houka, and Jakuzure Nonon,
only to be suddenly faced
by a girl called Harime Nui.
She was the woman with the Sword Scissor
that Ryuuko was looking for.
Then came the appearance of Satsuki's mother,
the head of the Kiryuuin conglomerate, Kiryuuin Ragyou.
To complete her takeover
of schools across the country,
Satsuki ordered a Battlefield Trip
to the Big Three Kansai-area cities.
But schools weren't the
only thing she was after.
She also wanted to take out Nudist Beach, the anti-uniform
organization that opposed the Kiryuuin family.
In order to put my pieces back together,
Ryuuko headed to Kansai too.
In the city of wealth, Osaka,
Ryuuko and Satsuki engaged in mortal combat.
And today, the secret behind the
Life Fibers will finally be revealed!
Fret not, all of you that were
disappointed to hear this was a recap.
Breakneck pacing is a
hallmark of KILL la KILL.
Even the recap episode
only lasts as long as an intro!
The actual story continues now!
The tides of war will change drastically!
Ignorant as you are,
you stand no chance of victory!
That's exactly why I keep asking
you to tell me, dammit!
All you've ever done is beat around
the bush! Get off your high horse!
Screw you, Ms. Bigmouth Eyebrows!
EPISODE 16
THE GIRL CAN'T HELP IT
unmei no ito wo tachikitta sono saki ni
It all begins when we sever the threads of fate
senobi shiteitanda
I was trying to be someone I'm not
kutsuzure darake no
In a cramped world
semai sekai de
With no breathing room
runway wo aruku
As I walked down my runway
egao no uragawa
I thought I'd concealed it
kakushita tsumori de
Behind the smile that masked my face
dakedo itsumo kimi ni wa
But it doesn't work on you
minukarete shimatte ite
You always see through my facade
konna no wa hajimete de
Nobody's ever unraveled me like this before
tomadou kedo
I don't know what to do
hoka no dare ni mo kikonasenai
Nobody else can pull these outfits off
nandaka wakannai
A somewhat ambiguous fever
atsusa ga mune wo kogasu kara
Threatens to burn our hearts away
unmei no ito taguriyoseta sono saki ni
It all begins once we rein in the threads of fate
ima atarashii yoake ga kuru
A new day will dawn for us
omoi wa kitto hitotsu
We must be one in spirit
Milady!
Shirou!
Right away!
It's a tranquilizing coagulant.
Please take this opportunity
to change out of your Godrobe.
Thanks.
Your fights seem to be taking a
greater toll on your body than before.
It's too risky to activate Life Fiber Override
for as long as you have been.
I'm aware of the risk.
But so long as Matoi
continues to wear her Godrobe,
I have no choice but to
don Junketsu to fight her.
It is as you say, Milady.
Are you sure, Uncle?
Shirou.
As my nephew,
it is about time you realized
that once Lady Satsuki has her heart
set on something, she never backs down.
The only thing we can do is
support her and her decisions.
Soroi, Iori.
I've made many
selfish demands of you two.
But please allow me
to do so for just a little longer.
Oh?
So you were pushing yourself,
Lady Satsuki?
Who are you?!
...That voice...
Is that you, Harime?
Sure is!
The Grand Couturier?
When did you get here?!
I go wherever I want to go,
and no one can stop me.
What do you want?
Don't get all, "What do you want?" with me.
It was Lady Ragyou.
She said she wanted to hear the
results of the Battlefield Trip in person.
And since I had time to kill because a certain
someone barred me from Honnouji Academy,
I came all the way to pick you up!
I bet you just wanted to see
Senketsu and Junketsu square off.
Bingo, Lady Satsuki!
You're the only one who
truly understands me!
That's rich, coming from someone who
refuses to let anyone understand her.
Well then, shall we make
our way to the mansion?
Iori.
Pass on a message to the Four Devas:
"I'll be returning late.
You must all remain vigilant
until you reach Honnouji Academy.
Remember, the Battlefield Trip
isn't over until you get home."
Yes, ma'am!
Shall I pour you another
cup of tea in the meantime?
Please.
She got us.
But we still escaped with our lives.
As long as we're alive, we can fight.
You're right.
Ryuuko, I'm amazed you fought
Kiryuuin Satsuki to a draw.
Well done.
Come.
Hey, Mikisugi!
Where are you going?
Kiryuuin Satsuki hit the nail on the head.
The tides have turned.
There is no reason to
keep secrets any longer.
It's time I exposed everything to you.
What?!
...Were you really...
Mr. Mikisugi all along?!
That's right.
You've never seen me like this before.
I never knew you were an exhibitionist!
You've found a comrade-in-arms, Ryuuko!
...We are Nu—
Don't lump us together!
Mako, you go home for now.
Huh?
Mankanshoku,
if you come with us, you will need to
hurl yourself into the maelstrom of battle.
Do you have that resolve?
I do not!
Figures.
Go home, then.
I don't have the
resolve to go nude yet.
That's what you're talking about?!
...But what I do have...
is the desire to be
Ryuuko's friend forever!
So I'll go with you!
...Mako...
Very well.
Follow us!
Okay!
Huh?
Woo!
What?
...Hey—
Hoo!
Mako!
...Hang on...
Why are you diving in?
Ryuuko.
Beyond here lies the truth you must learn.
Let's do this.
It's skinny diving time!
Huh?
What?
Wait!
Take off Junketsu, please.
We'll hold on to it for you.
The CEO left a message for you.
She wants you to wait for her
at the grand bathhouse.
KIRYUUIN
RESIDENCE
GRAND
BATHHOUSE
You're pulling off that
Godrobe quite well,
but it would appear
you're pushing yourself.
Mother.
This herbal extract will increase
your affinity with Life Fibers.
Be sure to soak yourself well.
I will.
My, such nice skin you have.
Entrust your heart to me.
I shall purify you.
Humans are such fragile beings.
When we're naked like this,
anxiety overcomes us.
It makes us want to hurry up and cover our
bodies in the wonders known as "clothes".
That is our instinct.
...And species that defy their instincts...
...will eventually...
fall into ruin.
You can get out now.
There is somewhere we need to be.
...Does that mean...
Yes.
You did well, Satsuki.
As a Kiryuuin,
and as my successor,
it is now time for you to
learn where all this began.
There was a place like this
underneath Osaka?
It's in pretty bad shape, though.
Jakuzure sure did a number on us.
However, there is more to
this place than meets the eye.
Mikisugi! Kinagase!
I see this place was spared.
We were right to follow
your orders and take refuge here.
I guess being a worrywart
pays off from time to time.
I see Nudist Beach has had
quite a bit of money poured into it.
It's all thanks to your father.
Dad?
He was an amazing scientist.
Using the patents he held, he collected money
from corporations worldwide.
And with those funds,
he created this organization.
...Then...
Indeed!
...Nudist Beach was founded...
by Dr. Matoi Isshin!
What?!
I don't think it happened like that.
How did you know what was
going through my mind?
You two are on the same
wavelength now, huh, Ryuuko?
I can't say I'm too happy about that.
Wow, Ryuuko!
Now I've got a friend who's
both outside and inside my mind!
...Er...
Clothes
Now, Ryuuko,
how many organisms on this planet
do you know of that wear clothes?
Just us humans, obviously.
Correct.
Out of the countless species on Earth,
the only one to wear
clothes is homo sapiens.
And why do you think that is?
It is not that only humans wear clothing,
but rather that the creatures who wore clothes
became mankind as we know it today!
Life Fibers caused homo sapiens, previously
just one of many anthropoids, to evolve this far.
That's right.
Mankind was chosen by clothing!
KIRYUUIN
RESIDENCE
FIBER
PALACE
FORBIDDEN
ROOM
This is where it all began?
Correct.
The source of everything:
the original Life Fiber.
ORIGINAL
LIFE FIBER
The moment this shining ball of thread that had
wandered across space touched down on Earth,
humans were fated to become
beings that served clothes.
Life Fibers will become clothes
and cover up the planet.
That is COVERS.
Nobody in this world
can stop it from happening.
We, the Kiryuuin family,
are the mouthpiece for COVERS' will.
Do you understand that?
Yes, Mother.
Clothing chose mankind?
What do you mean?
Life Fibers are an
extraterrestrial lifeform!
Antiquity
They came to Earth in ancient times
and induced human evolution!
What?!
Does that mean Senketsu's
an extraterrestrial being?
Mako
He's not only a sailor uniform,
but also an alien?!
So that's how it is.
Don't just accept it!
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?!
Could you pipe down and hear me out?
I'll explain it from the ground up.
Life Fibers are a
lifeform from outer space.
Like parasites, they use
native lifeforms as their hosts
and breed by feeding off
their nerve pulses.
However,
when they directly inhabit a body,
they place too much strain on
the nervous system, destroying it.
That is why they decided to cover
the creatures' bodies instead.
They can only obtain a miniscule amount
of energy from the skin's nerve endings,
but this way,
they keep their hosts alive.
They chose the species with the furthest-developed
cerebrums at the time, homo sapiens,
to be their hosts and artificially
sped up their evolution.
And thus, mankind evolved.
We developed brains that far
outclassed any other creature on Earth,
proliferated throughout the world,
and climbed to the
apex of the food chain.
However, this was all
under the Life Fibers' guidance.
It is but a transient peak.
Ultimately, we humans are
just food for the Life Fibers.
It can't be!
...Have I been feeding off Ryuuko—
Calm down, Senketsu.
We haven't heard the whole story yet.
Why don't all clothes have
Life Fibers in them, then?
Right now, most of us wear clothes
normally and lead normal lives.
Honnouji Academy students are pretty much
the only ones who wear such strange outfits!
You're right.
The only possible conclusion is that,
having induced mankind's evolution,
the Life Fibers left us with only
the habit of clothing ourselves
and entered a long period of dormancy.
It was around two hundred years ago
that they came out of their dormant state.
Kiryuuin Ragyou made contact
with the original Life Fiber,
which led to their reawakening.
Or so I heard from Dr. Matoi.
They were waiting
for the opportune time.
Don't people wait until cattle
are nice and plump, too?
...Was I...
waiting for Ryuuko to grow up?
Is that why I need her blood?!
Like I said, calm down!
You're not like that, Senketsu!
Is Senketsu panicking?
...If so, tell him...
that the two of you represent our hope.
Hope?
That's right.
Godrobe Senketsu was created by
Dr. Matoi to fight against the Life Fibers.
And you're the only one
who can pull off that Godrobe, Ryuuko!
I'm the only one?
But why?
You are extraordinarily
resistant to Life Fibers.
Dr. Matoi probably knew that.
That is why he crafted
...Senketsu to suit you—
to put an end to the
Kiryuuins' ambitions!
The Doctor once researched Life Fibers
under orders from Kiryuuin Ragyou.
But once he learned the
terrifying truth, he fled from her
and secretly formed
a counter-organization.
...That is...
who we are: Nudist Beach!
I see.
So that is why Dr. Matoi created me.
Yes.
I remember it now.
I was born in that
underground laboratory,
but I was immediately put to sleep.
Until Ryuuko came to me,
six months later.
I'm sorry for keeping
all this a secret until now.
But the Kiryuuins' might
knows no bounds.
Until you got to the point where you
could freely call upon Senketsu's powers,
I couldn't tell you the whole story.
Yeah, you even planned on eliminating me
if I were ever consumed
by the Life Fibers.
Exactly.
That plan hasn't changed.
Tsumugu!
...Yeah, this story...
is a bit hard to believe.
But it is the truth.
The clothes produced by REVOCS,
the company Kiryuuin Ragyou leads,
are worn more or less across the globe.
Each one of those outfits
contains Life Fibers.
At the moment, they still lie dormant,
but if they ever were to awaken,
Hououmaru Rei
Harime Nui
Kiryuuin
Satsuki
Ragyou
there's no telling what will happen.
But one thing is for sure:
they will be a massive threat to mankind.
So you succeeded in taking over all the schools
in the country and suppressing Nudist Beach?
Yes.
That means we can advance the
Honnouji Academy experiment to the next stage.
We've also completed construction
of the Ragyou Stadium.
The festival is all set to go.
Very well.
Let us move to the
final stage of the plan:
the Great Culture and Sports Festival.
As you wish.
What will you do?
I haven't been home in a while,
so I'll stay the night.
Is that so?
Take care of her needs, Kuroido.
Honnouji Academy is your creation.
I'm looking forward to
seeing just what it's made of.
We shall welcome you
with open arms, Mother.
Now I get it.
So you're telling Senketsu and I to fight
hand-in-hand for the sake of mankind, huh?
To hell with that!
Ryuuko?
You mean to say
Senketsu's just a weapon?
A combat outfit
made purely for battle?
You've gotta be kidding me.
He's got a mind of his own!
Now you're telling me
he was born to kill his brethren?
I feel so damn sorry for him!
What are you doing?
This is Nudist Beach, right?
What's wrong with me stripping off?
...Ryuuko...
I can't fight while wearing you!
You don't need to fight either!
Let me tell you two
useful pieces of information.
One: there's no reason for a
Godrobe that doesn't fight to exist.
Two: I won't hesitate to
dispose of any such Godrobes.
You'll have to do it over my dead body.
Fine by me.
I'll grant that wish of yours.
You're all scaring me!
This is bad!
Why don't we have
some snacks and calm down?
Let's see.
I'll borrow some souvenirs.
This sucks!
This whole thing sucks!
kurikaesu mainichi ga
My monotonous everyday life
totsuzen iro wo kaeru
Took on a new hue
sonna koto dokka nozonde itanda kedo ne
A part of me always wished for that to happen
iza to naru to
But when it actually did
okubyoumono deshita
I was too scared to act
himitsu ne
That's a secret, okay?
hitori furuete
Trembling alone
soshite kimi ni aitakute
I miss you so much
zutto mikata da yo nante ieta nara
If only I could tell you that I'll always be on your side
muteki
We could be invincible
sou sa tobidatsu toki wa futari de
When we take flight, we'll do so together
tachimukai
We'll make a stand
kakaekirenai okubyou ni
I don't want to go back
zutto hitatte waratte ita
To being the bumbling coward I was
hitori kiri zutsu ga awasatte
Every little thing will come together
ookina chikara ni naru yo
To give us great strength
ima nee kanjita
That's how I feel right now
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Ryuuko has found out
about her father's desire.
Don't hesitate, Ryuuko.
You and I don't wear on each other.
YOU AND I
The Great Culture and Sports Festival!
THE GREAT CULTURE
AND
SPORTS FESTIVAL
It's the Kiryuuins' declaration of victory.
DECLARATION OF VICTORY
Only we can stop them.
ONLY WE
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"Why Do You".
EPISODE 17
WHY DO YOU