I'm done with you.
I'm never putting you on again.
Ryuuko!
Just looking at you pisses me off!
'Cause we're both the
same breed of monster!
That's right! I'm not human!
I'm a Life Fiber monster!
That's not right, Ryuuko!
Isn't Senketsu your friend?
This isn't like you at all!
At all!
At all! At all! At all! At all!
Well, yeah. I'm not my usual self.
Turns out my whole life
until now was a lie,
and I'm actually a monster.
Not a human.
I'm some unkillable freak,
just like Ragyou.
...No...
Hmm. You're looking
awfully grumpy today, Ryuuko.
Harime Nui!
EPISODE 20
FAR FROM THE MADDENING CROWDS
unmei no ito wo tachikitta sono saki ni
It all begins when we sever the threads of fate
senobi shiteitanda
I was trying to be someone I'm not
kutsuzure darake no
In a cramped world
semai sekai de
With no breathing room
runway wo aruku
As I walked down my runway
egao no uragawa
I thought I'd concealed it
kakushita tsumori de
Behind the smile that masked my face
dakedo itsumo kimi ni wa
But it doesn't work on you
minukarete shimatte ite
You always see through my facade
konna no wa hajimete de
Nobody's ever unraveled me like this before
tomadou kedo
I don't know what to do
hoka no dare ni mo kikonasenai
Nobody else can pull these outfits off
nandaka wakannai
A somewhat ambiguous fever
atsusa ga mune wo kogasu kara
Threatens to burn our hearts away
unmei no ito taguriyoseta sono saki ni
It all begins once we rein in the threads of fate
ima atarashii yoake ga kuru
A new day will dawn for us
omoi wa kitto hitotsu
We must be one in spirit
But I think you're getting mad
at the wrong person.
I seem to remember you
wanting to avenge your father.
And yet you're ignoring me, his killer,
and playing with a
bunch of weaklings instead.
You're making me sad!
Screw you!
That's the spirit, daughter of mine!
Don't call me your daughter!
I can understand your turmoil.
Kiryuuin Souichirou—no, I suppose
I should call him "Matoi Isshin" instead.
This was a dastardly scheme
concocted by that foolish man.
He treated his own daughter
as but a mere tool.
As your mother, I understand
your rage so much it hurts.
Enough of your barefaced tripe!
Marvelous. Your unyielding
spirit is a sight to behold.
Watching you excites me far more
than that worthless firstborn of mine!
You wretch!
Don't you dare insult Lady Satsuki!
What exactly do I owe a girl who
stabbed her own mother in the back?
Do you hate your mother?
Do you resent me, Ragyou?
I'm gonna kick your ass all the way to Hell.
Then come to me!
Honnouji Academy shall be the stage where you and I,
mother and daughter, settle things once and for all!
Fine by me.
I'm coming for your head.
I can't wait.
Adieu, mon amie!
Wait, Ryuuko!
Don't try to stop me.
This is a trap.
Barging in in a fit of rage
would put you in too much danger.
Quit acting like you're
my goddamn teacher!
This is all your fault in the first place.
You played dumb,
despite knowing everything.
Deep down, I bet you were
laughing at this freak of a girl!
Of course not.
Shut up.
I've had enough of your excuses!
Looks like humans and clothing
really can't see eye to eye.
The hell are you talking about?
I've never been human to begin with!
Step aside!
I'll crush anyone who gets in my way!
She felled two buildings with one strike?
What terrifying fury.
Ryuuko.
See that? That's who I am right now.
All you guys have to do is
cast off your Ultima Uniforms.
But I'm gonna have to live
with Life Fibers until I die!
Senketsu wasn't the weapon
created to kill his brethren!
It was me!
...No...
Just looking at you pisses me off!
You remind me of my own stupidity!
...Ryuuko...
If you got that, then don't
come clinging to me again.
Oh, but he will!
I mean, Senketsu's both your
best outfit and your best friend!
Just like a western outfit that screams "youth",
he'll cling to your body always and forever!
Whoa!
I felt a spark run through my body!
Ryuuko?
...Ryuuko...
There are no signs of
any COVERS reinforcements.
So they were after
Matoi Ryuuko, and her alone?
If only I'd realized the truth
...about Ryuuko earlier...
..."I could've done something"?...
Talk about conceited.
We can't count on Matoi Ryuuko
to fight for us anymore.
The only thing we should be thinking
about is what we can do right now.
There's no time for regrets.
For high schoolers, you guys sure
have good heads on your shoulders.
Lady Satsuki did train us well, you know.
We can't sit here moping
over something like this.
What exactly do they plan to achieve by provoking
Matoi Ryuuko into storming Honnouji Academy?
If she takes out Ragyou and Harime Nui,
that would save us a lot of trouble.
This is the Kiryuuin Ragyou we're
talking about. It won't be that easy.
Ryuuko was crying.
Filled with suffering and resentment,
it was she who was
shedding bitter tears this time.
I shall head for Honnouji Academy.
I can't leave Ryuuko on her own!
That said, I'm sure my words
won't reach anyone.
Senketsu, you want to
go after Ryuuko, right?
You want to go after her, right?
Y-Yes. You can understand
what I'm saying?
All right, I get it.
There, there.
Mankanshoku!
Can you hear Senketsu's voice?
Not at all.
Figures.
But I can understand how he feels.
After all, I feel the same way.
Uh... I think we're all going to
want to go after Matoi Ryuuko now.
What do you mean?
I finally managed to infiltrate
the academy's system.
They seem to be building something.
That bothers me too, but there are
more pressing concerns right now.
Lady Satsuki!
Lady Satsuki, you say?
Is she alive?
How cruel.
Don't look, you fiends!
You must not lay eyes on this!
My Mind's Eye doesn't work on screens!
Someone tell me what's going on!
She's hanging by chains.
Stark naked, too.
Chains? Stark naked?!
What's the meaning of this?!
Nothing!
Settle down, would you?
We haven't gotten to the real issue yet.
I'm raising the volume.
...She's sharpening...
Lady Satsuki's sharpening
the fangs of rebellion!
Nails, to be more precise.
Milady!
Sheesh. How roundabout can she be?
If she was alive, then she
should've just said so already.
Yeah. Looks like we know where to go.
Indeed.
Our goal is to rescue Lady Satsuki!
The enemy awaits at Honnouji!
Oh man. He went and said it.
And here we were
all trying to hold it in.
Man, that sorta stuff is
seriously embarrassing, you know?
This is why I can't stand dumb monkeys
from Northern Kanto. No tact at all!
Oh dear.
If you guys are so up for it,
I'll have to take off my underwear too.
Don't you dare, pervert.
So long as we can't rely on Ryuuko,
mankind cannot prevail
without Kiryuuin Satsuki.
Nudist Beach shall offer up all of its
manpower to Operation Rescue Satsuki.
Wait, are you going to use the Naked Sun?!
Naked?
That's right! We're all set to go.
Behold!
This is our very last piece!
The S.S. Naked Sun!
Set sail!
All hands, get ready to sail!
Have all non-combatants
disembark the ship!
All right! It's about freakin' time!
Go break a leg, you guys.
Open the Doutonbori Gate!
Opening the Doutonbori Gate!
Quick!
The underground base was a ship?
It took every last penny of the
Takarada Conglomerate to finish this,
Nudist Beach's final trump card:
The S.S. Naked Sun!
S.S. NAKED SUN
Mako!
Oh, Dad! Mom!
...You guys...
We're coming with you!
It'd help you to have a doctor on board.
BACK-ALLEY MEDICAL CORPS
THE MANKANSHOKU FAMILY
Honnou Town is our hometown, after all,
and I've been wanting
to pick up some frying oil.
Plus, this seems like fun.
Guts, guts!
Yup! Let's go together!
Now hang on just a second.
We never said anything about taking
the underachiever along to begin with.
Give it up, Jakuzure.
Mankanshoku's the most
stubborn person in Honnouji.
Not even you can pull out the earplugs
she wears, for they are earplugs of the heart.
Uh, I'm not sure I follow.
Well, too late for that now.
The ship has sailed.
I got a lotta money ridin' on that thing!
Go give 'em threaded freaks
a beatin' they'll never forget!
I'm countin' on ya.
Ragyou!
Nui!
Where are you?!
I've come, just as I said I would!
Amazing!
You're just so wild
and cool today, Ryuuko!
Spare me the small talk.
I'm here to kill you and Ragyou.
And what will that achieve?
You can no longer go back to
the life you used to have, you know.
Like I said, spare me the small talk.
Hup!
Wow, so fast!
So it begins.
Have some more!
Missile confirmed to have hit target.
How easy it'd be if
this was enough to kill her.
Sure, we may have seen it coming,
but it's really annoying to
see her act like it was nothing.
What an ugly lump of steel.
I'll let you have all the
fun you want for now.
What a flashy ride.
My fake toenail's made from
the same material as Bakuzan.
It should be more than enough
for you scraps of cloth.
I get it, Ryuuko.
You're lonely, aren't you?
You believed you were human,
but you were being kept alive by the
same Life Fibers you considered your enemy.
In that case,
who exactly are your allies?
Who exactly are your enemies?
There's no human out there
who can understand you.
Quit running your mouth and fight me!
But you know what, Ryuuko?
You mustn't despair!
You still have me!
I'm the only one
who can understand you!
Say what you want!
But save the rest
for when you're in Hell!
Just kidding!
Lookie, look! This is my heart.
Just watch it pulsate
and sparkle with Life Fibers.
Isn't it oh-so-pretty?
...Are you...
Yup.
I'm just like you.
The only difference between us
is that you grew within
Lady Ragyou's belly,
whereas I grew within an
artificial womb made of Life Fibers.
That makes the two of us soul sisters.
Screw that!
My family's big enough already!
But you can't go against
the threads of fate!
Shut your mouth!
...That's...
Junketsu!
What?!
This is a heartfelt gift
from the Grand Couturier.
Ragyou, you bitch!
When did these threads get here?
While we were fighting, I stuck these
Marionette Threads in you for her.
You're my precious daughter.
I can't have you wearing a
cheap outfit like that Senketsu.
If you're going to wear clothes,
you should make them the very best.
Stop it!
Godrobe Junketsu!
That is the garment that best suits you.
Is that Junketsu?
Matoi?
So that is what's happening.
I have no means to
stop them right now.
Damn mass-produced trash.
Jump!
Lady Satsuki!
Let us help. Here.
Sorry we're late.
Don't be. You Four Devas always
show up at the perfect time.
Entrust your heart
to Junketsu, Ryuuko.
Knock it off!
Stop!
...Yes. That is your happiness—
the good fortune of being worn by clothing.
You understand, don't you, Ryuuko?
Yes, Mother!
I see.
Nudist Beach's flagship, huh?
Come to think of it, the Takarada
Conglomerate did begin as a shipyard.
Right this way, Lady Satsuki.
Milady.
While this may be
...too filthy a place for you...
Just being able to drink your tea
makes coming back worth it, Soroi.
Now that we've successfully rescued you,
it wouldn't be safe to
stick around in this area.
Shall we head back to Osaka for now?
I doubt we'll be able to.
Soon, we'll have to face
our worst possible enemy.
Bad news.
Something's heading
straight for this ship, and fast.
What?!
I'm gonna destroy it all!
Every last thing!
Yeah, this certainly is
the worst case scenario.
Things aren't looking good.
Unless we do something, this ship
will be sunk by a lone high school girl.
That idiot!
Tsumugu!
You'll die, you know.
I'll use that secret DTR
that was personalized for me.
...But that's still not...
It's got stronger armor than yours.
It's worth a shot!
Here, Lady Satsuki.
They're better off in
your hands than in ours.
What?!
Why's Ryuuko wearing Junketsu?
This can't be!
How could Ryuuko
wear another Godrobe?
I'm coming in.
Lady Satsuki!
Oh, look. It's a guy with a mohawk riding a mech
that exposes his ass to the entire world.
Die.
Wow.
So that's your game.
...The two of you...
joined hands, eh?
Hate me as you may,
you and I are the only ones
who can stop her right now.
Please lend me your strength,
Senketsu!
kurikaesu mainichi ga
My monotonous everyday life
totsuzen iro wo kaeru
Took on a new hue
sonna koto dokka nozonde itanda kedo ne
A part of me always wished for that to happen
iza to naru to
But when it actually did
okubyoumono deshita
I was too scared to act
himitsu ne
That's a secret, okay?
hitori furuete
Trembling alone
soshite kimi ni aitakute
I miss you so much
zutto mikata da yo nante ieta nara
If only I could tell you that I'll always be on your side
muteki
We could be invincible
sou sa tobidatsu toki wa futari de
When we take flight, we'll do so together
tachimukai
We'll make a stand
kakaekirenai okubyou ni
I don't want to go back
zutto hitatte waratte ita
To being the bumbling coward I was
hitori kiri zutsu ga awasatte
Every little thing will come together
ookina chikara ni naru yo
To give us great strength
ima nee kanjita
That's how I feel right now