FIVE
YEARS
AGO
Revocs Corporation Business Strategy Workframe
The Revocs Corporation.
They hold 70% market share
in the global apparel industry.
Rating
Stock
That's amazing.
Ah, they belong to the
Kiryuuin conglomerate.
Now I get it. That's interesting.
But one genius is about to single-handedly alter the destiny of that company.
MIDDLE SCHOOL THIRD YEAR STUDENT
INUMUTA HOUKA
Uh-oh, their stocks
are in free fall! How terrible!
Crap! I've been found out?!
How'd they manage to
pinpoint my location so quickly?!
Shoot first, ask questions later?!
I'm sorry! What I did was wrong!
It was a middle-school
scamp's harmless prank!
Please forgive me!
No mercy? Dude, seriously?
A middle-schooler you may be,
but you have trespassed into territory you shouldn't have.
A girl?
Then again, you are a man capable of breaching the
tightest security in the world to break into the Revocs site.
Calling yourself a middle-school
scamp at this point is pushing it.
So you're the big boss, huh?
Why did you do this?
The fact that it's the tightest security in the world is why it's such an attractive challenge.
How petty-minded.
What?
If you want to
challenge the system,
shouldn't you aim to change
the real world and not a virtual one?
Admission Permit
Honnouji Academy
High School
Admission Permit
Honnouji Academy
High School
Admission Permit
Honnouji Academy
High School
Admission Permit
Honnouji Academy
High School
Admission Permit
Honnouji Academy
High School
Admission Permit
Honnouji Academy
High School
Admission Permit
Honnouji Academy
High School
Admission Permit
Honnouji Academy
High School
Admission Permit
Honnouji Academy
High School
Admission Permit
Honnouji Academy
High School
Honnouji Academy High School?
That is the place where you will
change the world, Inumuta Houka.
EPISODE 10
I WANT TO KNOW MORE ABOUT YOU
dareka ga katteni kimetara readymade na
This is a readymade world that is at someone's beck and call
kyou wo nugisutete
I'll break free of its shackles
RYUUKO
MATOI
hadashi de hashitte iku
And sprint toward my goal
GAMAGOORI IRA
machigattatte
Even if I lose my way
GAMAGOORI IRA
SANAGEYAMA UZU
JAKUZURE NONON
INUMUTA HOUKA
korondatte
Or trip and fall
INUMUTA HOUKA
MANKANSHOKU FAMILY
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
surimuita itami mo
Those wounds will still create
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
KINAGASE
TSUMUGU
original na ashita ni naru
An original future for me
KIRYUUIN
SATSUKI
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
I hold my destiny in my own hands
chikai ga hikari ni natte
And it shines ever so brightly
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
So until the day I reach you
naiteru hima nante nai kara
I don't have the time to sit around crying
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
My burning passion pours out from within me
yozora de kagayaki dasu
And shines like a star in the night sky
umarete kita imi ga
I think I now understand
wakatta ki ga shita
Why I was born
negaigoto wa zenbu kono te de
I'll make all of my dreams come true
kanaeru
With my own hands
...The second of the Four Devas...
Quit pushing!
Quit your damn pushing!
Sheesh, whose TV
do you think this is?!
Look at this crowd!
Nobody'd notice if
I walked off with a nice set!
Matarou, I will end you.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Is Ryuuko gonna be okay?
If I was allowed to be her second,
I'd be right there looking after her!
G-Gamagoori!
And you're half-naked!
Don't be afraid, Mankanshoku.
I am now a No-Star,
the same rank as you.
It's only fitting that I
should observe this battle
from the same bleachers where
the other No-Stars are gathered.
Lady Satsuki, I, Gamagoori Ira,
will work my way back up
from this shame without fail!
I won't allow your kindness
toward me to be in vain!
Oh, I get it!
You want to fight me
right here and now, right?
I'm cheering on Ryuuko with all I've got,
so I won't let anyone
interfere, not even you!
How amusing!
Even with your encouragement,
Lady Satsuki's stronghold
won't budge one iota!
But it did budge!
You lost, remember?
Inumuta, win!
Trounce her thoroughly and utterly!
Ryuuko, take him out!
You can do it!
You hear me, Inumuta?!
Time to hit the noise canceller.
I'm not interested in hearing
a beaten dog yap away.
Now she's showing
mercy to the vanquished.
What could our
mighty queen be up to?
You have doubts
about Lady Satsuki?
Honestly, that obnoxious intuition of yours has gotten
even sharper since you lost your sight, Mr. Wild Monkey.
If your faith in her falters, you may
find your own footing grows unsteady.
I hate to break it to you,
but I have a different relationship to her than the rest of you.
That Godrobe transformation
was most fascinating,
but you overexerted yourself in your
fight against Gamagoori, don't you think?
You're breathing heavily,
and your heart rate is elevated.
Don't you worry about me.
Let's get this started!
...Round Two...
Begin.
King Of
The Hill
Round 1
Matoi Ryuuko
vs .
Inumuta
Houka
Round 1
Matoi Ryuuko
vs .
Inumuta
Houka
King Of
The Hill
Matoi Ryuuko
vs .
Inumuta
Houka
The Hill
Begin
Fighting
Understood.
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
PROBE REGALIA
Three-Star Ultima Uniform:
Probe Regalia.
"Probe Regalia", huh?
Seems more subdued than the others.
And yet, it makes me uneasy.
It's as though we're being stripped bare.
Figures. He is their intel chief.
We don't know what his
deal is, so let's be careful.
Life Fiber Synchronize,
Godrobe Senketsu!
So, she's starting off with Stage 1, her standard combat mode, eh?
Ah, I see.
She's even faster than I predicted?
I know your type.
You guys are always spouting crap like
"I've analyzed all your capabilities" or
"I can anticipate every one of your moves!"
There's only one way to
beat somebody like you:
by being reckless!
I see.
That's why you exerted yourself right away and
boosted your reaction speed higher than I predicted.
Boosting your Life Fiber link
through force of will, eh?
It's the same general principle
as the Ultima Uniforms,
but given that yours is 100% Life Fiber, its effect is that much greater.
But I wonder: how long
can your body keep this up?
It's not about if I can or not.
I will make it happen!
I'd expect nothing less
from Matoi Ryuuko!
How can a human body
move like that
when it's clad in
nothing but Life Fibers?
Show me with your actions!
...What the...
He vanished?!
He disappeared!
When Inumuta Houka's
Ultima Uniform shines,
white butterflies flutter
and come to rest on a snowman.
He did not vanish!
OPTICAL
CAMOUFLAGE
This is optical camouflage!
Nuh-uh! There are
no butterflies in winter!
They die when it snows!
I should have known, Mankanshoku.
You totally missed the point.
When it comes to haphazard attacks,
the most effective countermeasure
is to dodge them.
What's more, if you're able to retaliate,
the psychological damage
is all the greater.
There's nowhere to run!
If all I can gather is
obvious data like this,
I'll be very disappointed!
Senketsu, time for Plan B:
Get Really Reckless!
Understood!
Eat this!
What?
That eye is totally huge!
If I can't see where you are,
I'll just have to attack
the whole field at once!
...E-Evasion...
EVASION
IMPOSSIBLE
...impossible!...
I can see him!
Oh, dear. It looks like the shock of that attack wrecked that hide-and-seek ability of his.
That's what happens
when you rely on your eyes.
Yeah, just like a certain somebody!
See that?
Make a crazy attack
even crazier, and it'll hit.
Let's do it, Senketsu!
Your blood is boiling
even hotter than usual.
Yeah, 'cause I can't stop here!
DOES NOT COMPUTE
I'm at the limits of
my processing capacity?
DOES NOT COMPUTE
Inumuta Houka
hereby forfeits this battle!
FORFEIT
What are you up to?
If I continue fighting, the data
I've gathered so far will be damaged.
Say what?
All I want is data.
I care not for victory.
That data-lover is
grandstanding again.
Still, Lady Satsuki is allowing it.
Jakuzure. Prepare for battle.
What's the matter?
What are you so flustered about?
I thought you two went back
further than any of us.
Oh, shut up!
Hey! I'm the one who's up next!
I know that.
But I need to prepare my Three-Star Ultima Uniform: Blade Regalia Mk 2.
What are you saying?!
You're just assuming I'm gonna lose?!
Nobody mocks me!
She's cleared the second one, too.
That's way better
...than I expected, but still...
10 Minutes
¥100
A hundred yen per ten minutes?!
Where do you get off, gramps?!
The electricity to run those
TV's ain't free, you know!
You're gonna pay for it!
You greedy old fart!
What the hell, man?!
Yes, yes!
If you don't like it,
go somewhere else.
Don't mess with us,
you senile old fart!
Son! Come here, boy!
We'll pay, we'll pay!
10 Minutes
¥100
You're here too, Inumuta?!
I'm just like you.
I'm going to observe the fight from here.
I won't bring up the fact that you forfeit.
The way each man fights
is his own path to choose.
But, Inumuta, why are you wearing a tracksuit?! Have you no shame?!
The loser is stripped
of his Ultima Uniform.
I don't recall there being a rule
about having to go naked, though.
Surely it's more important to know the rules than it is to know shame, Mr. Disciplinary Bureau Chairman.
Oh, my apologies!
Former Disciplinary Bureau Chairman!
Thank you for your kind advice,
Former Intelligence and Tactics Officer.
What's with all this tension?
Even the spectator seats
have turned into a battleground!
Fine! I'm not gonna lose either!
Go for it, Mako!
Stand strong, Mankanshoku Mako!
Hooray! Hooray!
Go for it, Mako!
Your friend has finally
started cheering for herself.
It sure looks that way.
Still, that's classic Mako.
Your pulse and respiration
have returned to normal.
So she's the key to getting you to relax?
Entrance march!
Under the Double Eagle!
What the hell?
She certainly knows
how to make a cheery entrance.
Sorry for the wait, transfer student.
This won't be like those boorish fights you've had with the boys.
Prepare to be pummeled cheerfully, jauntily, and utterly one-sidedly!
Three-Star Ultima Uniform:
Symphony Regalia Grave!
THREE-STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA
GRAVE
That's huge! On what planet
is that a uniform?!
I can get better acoustics this way.
Okay, for my first song,
Light Cavalry Overture!
She's gonna fight while playing music?
It's so loud I can barely think.
Now's not the time for complaints.
Let's do it! Life Fiber Synchronize,
Godrobe Senketsu!
Her attack sure packs a punch.
The bass really reverberates, doesn't it?
Next up is a really sharp performance!
Ow!
Dance harder!
The music's lacking a
certain something, you know?
Oh, I know!
It's missing your screams,
transfer student!
In that case, I'm gonna wring
a better performance out of you!
SYMPHONY
REGALIA
PRESTO
Symphony Regalia Presto!
That huge thing can fly?!
Yes indeed, this huge thing can fly!
That's my power!
The other three Devas
could never do this!
I'm the one who can best
...use this Ultima Uniform—
the power you got your hands on!
Isn't that right, Satsuki?!
HIGH-HANDED
KINDERGARTEN
You know, I sure would like a castle.
This sandbox belongs to me!
I won't let the other kids use it!
Except for you, Satsuki!
We've been best friends since forever!
I'll make a castle for you too!
No.
My sand is right here.
Is that all?
This sand is what's left over from that.
The rest of my sand became concrete
and was transformed into that skyscraper.
From the top, even a child
can look down on any adult.
A castle that blows away with
the first gust of wind is worthless.
Don't you agree, Nonon?
But all buildings fall down eventually!
Then you should
build it inside your mind!
A skyscraper built
...within your mind...
will never fall down.
You don't need any dumb sand!
I'll hold your hand!
For ever and ever!
Ever since that day,
I promised myself that
I would always be with you.
That I would always look out
from the same height as you!
Actually, I guess my view
is even higher right now.
Now, listen to this!
The William Tell Overture finale!
Hey! I thought you were disqualified if you left the battle area!
Not if you leave it;
only if you fall out of it.
I'm flying, so it's all good!
You weasels are always
making up rules on the spot!
Goodness, it seems like you
have time to complain, at least.
Let's give you a taste
of something bigger.
Dodge as jauntily
as you can! If you can!
Like I said, on what planet
is that a uniform?!
A flying weapon fired a flying weapon!
Damn it, how is that fair?!
Chew on this!
In that case,
I'll just have to
bring you down to my level!
...I'll cut those...
flimsy ropes of yours!
Every part of Senketsu's body
is a bundle of Life Fibers!
You think you can
cut him that easily?
Attagirl, Ryuuko!
Certainly, cutting Life Fibers is difficult.
But what about the ground?
Right! So let's see how you like this!
I can withstand an explosion or two!
It's no use! The ground's
giving out beneath us!
Oh dear. She's fallen.
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
Locator
No Response
Communications Ok
The communications
search system is online, huh?
I think I could get used to
this Naturals Election thing.
You're the last person
I expected a call from.
Is this about the girl in the Godrobe?
Yeah, I guess you could say that.
Ryuuko is trying really hard, but...
Senketsu, can you do something that's really, really reckless?
I'll do my best!
You're finished!
It evolved into a flying configuration
in so short a time?
That's my Senketsu!
He can do anything if he tries!
Did you see that?! Senketsu Gale!
SENKETSU
GALE
She's trying a little too hard, you see.
SENKETSU
It's evolving too quickly.
You're telling me to
prepare for the worst, are you?
I suppose I am.
Understood.
...The sky is my world...
The kid gloves are off,
you stinking bitch!
chime ga naru mae ni
Before the bell rings
kugurinuketa
I sneak out of school
otonatachi no haiiro no me
Avoiding the adults' vacant stares
tawai no nai kaiwa
The pointless conversations
togirenu mama
Keep going on and on
sakamichi wo kudatteku
As I walk down the slope
nani wo suru demo naku
I have nothing to do
yuku ate sae mo naku
And nowhere to go
tada atashi ima wa ne
Right now, all I do
donna chuukoku mo mimi wo surinukeru
Is ignore any and all warnings
mada mada suki ni sasete
Because I still want to be free
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
To be an exemplary student
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
rojiura no nukemichi
And take the back alley
amai yuuwaku wa michi
A path of mysterious sweet temptation
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
As the battle against
Jakuzure Nonon reaches its climax,
a girl appears at Honnouji Academy!
HONNOUJI ACADEMY
GIRL
Her name is Harime Nui!
HARIME NUI
Be careful, Ryuuko! A girl who uses her own name as an eyepatch must be crazy! Watch out!
EYEPATCH
GIRL
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"I'm Not Your Cute Woman"!
EPISODE 11
I'M NOT YOUR CUTE WOMAN