Eat this!
Finishing Move: All-Out Blade Strike!
Hup!
Go right back to being a naked ape!
Impossible!
Hup!
Here we go!
Ta-dah!
...That's...
Yep! It's the other half
of your Sword Scissor!
Fresh from your dad's corpse!
Wait... It was you?
Sure was!
I was the one who killed your father!
Bitch!
Tell me!
Why did you kill my dad?!
EPISODE 12
SPIT YOUR
SADNESS AWAY
dareka ga katteni kimetara readymade na
This is a readymade world that is at someone's beck and call
kyou wo nugisutete
I'll break free of its shackles
RYUUKO
MATOI
hadashi de hashitte iku
And sprint toward my goal
GAMAGOORI IRA
machigattatte
Even if I lose my way
GAMAGOORI IRA
SANAGEYAMA UZU
JAKUZURE NONON
INUMUTA HOUKA
korondatte
Or trip and fall
INUMUTA HOUKA
MANKANSHOKU FAMILY
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
surimuita itami mo
Those wounds will still create
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
KINAGASE
TSUMUGU
original na ashita ni naru
An original future for me
KIRYUUIN
SATSUKI
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
I hold my destiny in my own hands
chikai ga hikari ni natte
And it shines ever so brightly
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
So until the day I reach you
naiteru hima nante nai kara
I don't have the time to sit around crying
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
My burning passion pours out from within me
yozora de kagayaki dasu
And shines like a star in the night sky
umarete kita imi ga
I think I now understand
wakatta ki ga shita
Why I was born
negaigoto wa zenbu kono te de
I'll make all of my dreams come true
kanaeru
With my own hands
My dad told me that if I took this scissor,
I'd be sure to find the person who killed him!
What do you know, he was right!
You were the one in my house
that day, weren't you?!
Yup, I sure was!
Why?
Why did you kill him?
You know the answer
to that question already.
Who, me? Don't give me that crap!
I don't know anything about my dad!
Your outfit says otherwise, though.
Outfit?
You mean Senketsu?
Yup. Your dad crossed a line
mankind was never meant to cross.
He committed a taboo.
But taboos sure feel nice, don't they?
What's with her hand?
It's freezing!
Wow, it's silky-smooth!
You can tell it's 100% genuine Life Fiber.
Don't dodge the issue!
Please. I'm doing nothing of the sort.
But now that we've met here,
I want us to have lots of fun!
Screw you!
Why would I play friends
with my dad's killer?!
You're so narrow-minded.
Love and hate are two sides
of the same coin, you know.
The better an outfit's lining,
the better its stitching is too.
That is to say, the more you hate someone,
the more you can love them in turn.
My ass, you can!
There, there.
You look wonderful
even when you're mad, Ryuuko.
Calm down, Ryuuko.
Your blood's boiling.
You're too agitated!
Hey!
It's another red thread!
Is that the Nexus Thread?
This is trouble!
Makes me want to see you...
naked!
What?
...Oh—
Now!
That Godrobe's something else!
It has more than one Nexus Thread, huh?
That's right.
You won't unravel me that easily.
Wow, amazing!
Trust Dr. Matoi to have
something like that up his sleeve!
I fell hook, line, and sinker for it.
Who are you?
I came to play.
Play?
I heard you were up to
something interesting, you see.
SIX MONTHS AGO
MATOI UNDERGROUND RESEARCH FACILITY
Let me in on the fun.
I see.
So you caught wind of
my research and came here.
Yup.
I promised someone I know that
I'd bring your findings back to them.
And it's important to
keep your promises, right?
Hup!
A shape-memorizing lab coat, huh?
That ability shows that
it's fitted with Life Fibers too.
Great.
Now I don't have to hold back!
Don't be such a wet blanket.
You've gotta take games seriously too,
or else you won't have fun in life!
This is what I've poured
my heart and soul into creating.
It cuts the very life of Life Fibers.
Its name: the Sword Scissors!
SWORD
SCISSORS
I see you're not very good
at naming things, Doc.
A scientist cares not for aesthetics!
All we need is for
our research to bear fruit!
It's not about how pretty it is,
but how you use it, huh?
Oh, so scary!
Looks like wielding those
scissors takes a lot of you.
You need to strengthen your body.
Mind your own business.
Scientists peak in their sixties.
Wow, they really do nullify Life Fibers.
Way to go, Dr. Matoi.
These scissors are really powerful.
So how does it feel to have the creation you poured
your heart and soul into rip out your heart and soul?
I bet it feels out of this world!
I'm so nice, aren't I?
...Stop mouthing off...
Anyway, I'll be taking this with me, okay?
...Dad...
Dad!
Begone!
Dad?
So he had one half of
the Sword Scissors stolen
but still managed to
conceal my existence.
I'm impressed, Dr. Matoi.
So the woman I saw back then was you?!
You got it!
If I'd known a girl as cute
as you was on her way,
I would've stayed right there
and waited for you.
You bitch!
Do you think you can
avenge your dad with that?
Not happening, girl!
We'll see about that!
Stop it, Ryuuko.
Your blood grows dangerously hot!
If this keeps up,
I won't be able to control myself!
...No...
Is this what you were after, Harime Nui?
I'm going down there.
Very nice!
Things are getting fun!
This doesn't look good.
She's gone completely berserk.
What?!
Are you saying she was
overwhelmed by her Godrobe?
Matoi is in grave peril.
In just a few minutes,
she'll die from blood loss!
What? Death from blood loss?
DEATH
FROM
BLOOD
LOSS
FROM
BLOOD
LOSS
FROM
BLOOD
LOSS
She needs a blood transformation!
You mean "transfusion".
My dad steals his patients' blood
so he can sell it off at a high price later,
so I've seen plenty of people
die from excess blood loss!
Wait a minute.
What is that supposed to mean?
People die when they're killed by blood loss!
...Right...
It is not right!
It's not okay for Ryuuko to die!
I have to do my job as the
daughter of a back-alley doctor!
Say no to death from blood loss!
Say no to blood theft!
This has become quite the debacle.
Sanageyama.
Oh, you were okay, wild monkey?
Thanks to you, I was able to
obtain some data on Nexus Threads.
Until I settle my score with Matoi,
I can't possibly die.
...Sanageyama, you...
Put on some clothes.
Our fears have been realized.
Please hold her down, Tsumugu.
Got it.
Lady Satsuki, will you be all right?
The voting grounds are a lost cause.
You four are to evacuate the students.
I had no idea a Godrobe
could be this powerful.
I'll stop her.
Life Fiber Override:
Godrobe Junketsu!
GOD
ROBE
JUNKETSU
I'm counting on you.
Yes, ma'am!
Wait, Ryuuko!
You're wasting your blood!
It's worth good money, you know!
Back-Alley Doctor
Mankanshoku
Oh, Mako.
What's wrong?
Dad!
We came all the way here to watch
Ryuuko fight live, up close and personal!
Sis, show us somewhere we can sneak in.
Where are the voting grounds?
This is no time for that!
Back-alley doctor Mankanshoku,
it's your time to shine!
Back-Alley Doctor
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor On Call
I don't really get what's
going on, but leave it to me!
Hang in there, Ryuuko!
You've got a back-alley doctor's
daughter on your side!
Excellent!
It keeps getting more and more monstrous!
That's what Life Fiber's gotta be like!
So even you ended up
consumed by your clothes, huh?
What's your deal?
I see no need to introduce myself!
You're getting in the way of my fun.
Like I said, you're in the way.
It was a trap?
Great job, Tsumugu.
You have my thanks.
This is a special adhesive round.
Long story short,
it has a kind of starching effect.
But there's no guarantee that the
person wearing the outfit will survive.
Forgive me, Ryuuko.
She noticed me?
At this distance?!
It can't be.
Shit!
Not on my watch!
Another trap?
Goodness me, how annoying.
Why, if it isn't Lady Satsuki.
That's a wonderful outfit you're wearing.
Even Kiryuuin's here now?
What are you plotting, Harime Nui?
The Godrobe that
...Dr. Matoi Isshin created...
Don't you want to see
how strong it is? I sure do.
Seems more like you're trying to get revenge for how badly Matoi Isshin outsmarted you.
Huh?
You were so distracted by the Sword Scissors that you didn't notice the Godrobe he was developing in secret.
That's your fault.
And you even lost your left eye.
That side of yours isn't
cute at all, Lady Satsuki.
That's fine.
Nothing good ever happens
to things you find cute.
On that note, Ryuuko's absolutely adorable.
She's coming after me
with everything she's got.
Come to your senses,
Matoi Ryuuko!
No use, huh?
Yup.
Useless, useless, useless!
Stand back.
In that case, it is
...my job to take her down—
to finish off the girl who's been consumed by her Life Fibers' destructive impulses!
That sounds interesting in its own right.
Get back, Tsumugu.
You're not safe there.
Gotcha.
Amazing!
You two are in your own little world!
There's no room for anyone else!
"And it'd be amusing
if you took each other out."
I know that's what you're thinking.
I wouldn't dream of it!
Too bad that's not going to happen.
A girl who's just being worn by her own
Godrobe is no match for me, Kiryuuin Satsuki!
Here I come,
Matoi!
Stop!
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Ryuuko!
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Back-Alley Doctor
On Call
Mankanshoku
Ryuuko!
Ryuuko! Ryuuko! Ryuuko!
Ryuuko! Ryuuko! Ryuuko! Ryuuko!
Ryuuko! Ryuuko! Ryuuko! Ryuuko! Ryuuko! Ryuuko! Ryuuko!
Stop!
Stop it, Ryuuko!
This isn't like you at all!
What are you getting in the way for?
Huh?
Hold your tongue and watch!
Did you forget what you said to me?
You said it wasn't about
avenging your dad,
but getting to know him better!
But you're just a monster right now!
You're kicking, screaming,
and destroying our school!
You're acting just like I did!
Like I did when I let the
Fight Club thing go to my head!
Back then, you brought me
back to my senses!
So now it's my turn to do the same!
I will bring you back!
...Mako...
...I'm... back... to... normal...
...You... can... stop... now...
Geez!
It's all okay now.
Calm down!
Ow! Stop it!
Ryuuko!
Thank you.
...Ryuuko...
Sorry I dragged you along
with my rampage, Senketsu.
Don't be.
I'm just glad you're all right.
You nearly died of blood loss, you know?
You stupid idiot dummy!
Huh? Ryuuko?
Ryuuko!
Ryuuko! Ryuuko!
Did she die?!
She's just unconscious.
Mankanshoku,
it's thanks to you
that she was able to survive.
L-Lady Satsuki!
Why are you here?
Wait, you know my name?
Wait, Ryuuko! Pull yourself together!
Whoa!
My entire body's been singed pitch-black!
Wow! It's like I got a free tan!
Lucky!
Good grief.
Thanks, Tsumugu.
We somehow managed to pull
through without using this thing.
I couldn't make a move.
I couldn't make a single move
on those three women.
Of course not.
In the state they're in, they're like
monsters that have transcended humanity.
Shit!
I need to start training from scratch.
...Aww...
That was such a boring ending.
Harime Nui.
From now on, you are barred from
setting foot in Honnouji Academy.
Huh?
I'll take care of Matoi Ryuuko
and her Godrobe myself.
If you try pulling anything funny,
I will show you no mercy,
Grand Couturier or not.
That's awfully cold of you.
Get lost.
Okay, okay.
I understand!
Just kidding!
chime ga naru mae ni
Before the bell rings
kugurinuketa
I sneak out of school
otonatachi no haiiro no me
Avoiding the adults' vacant stares
tawai no nai kaiwa
The pointless conversations
togirenu mama
Keep going on and on
sakamichi wo kudatteku
As I walk down the slope
nani wo suru demo naku
I have nothing to do
yuku ate sae mo naku
And nowhere to go
tada atashi ima wa ne
Right now, all I do
donna chuukoku mo mimi wo surinukeru
Is ignore any and all warnings
mada mada suki ni sasete
Because I still want to be free
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
To be an exemplary student
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
rojiura no nukemichi
And take the back alley
amai yuuwaku wa michi
A path of mysterious sweet temptation
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you
SEVERAL
DAYS
LATER
I see you're on your feet again.
Where's Harime Nui?
Why do you want to know?
Because she killed your father?
Exactly.
I was the one who ordered her to
take the Sword Scissors from Matoi Isshin.
If you must resent someone, resent me.
What?
"Why was Matoi Isshin killed?"
"What is a Godrobe?"
"What are Life Fibers?"
I know the answers
to all of those questions.
...Then let's do this, here and no—
Do you really think you can
win as you currently are?
I doubt you've recovered fully
from that rampage the other day.
Shut up!
You have my gratitude, Matoi Ryuuko.
Gratitude?
That's right.
Thanks to your battles with the Four Devas,
I've been able to perfect the Ultima Uniforms.
Now I can put them to use in actual battle.
Say what?
At long last, Honnouji Academy
will conquer every school in the country.
Is that why you held the Naturals Election
and the King of the Hill battles?
Correct.
Honnouji Academy will,
in one week's time,
subjugate every school in
the west that dares oppose us.
We will go on a Battlefield Trip
to conquer the big three!
CONQUEST
OF THE
BIG THREE
BATTLEFIELD
TRIP
Just sit back and watch.
What is youth?
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
It is the springtime of life!
And why is it the springtime of life?
WHY
For it is not in full bloom!
NOT IN BLOOM
Depressed? You're still budding.
BUDDING
Chasing after your ideals?
You're still budding.
BUDDING
...I say that as I—
Egad!
EGAD!
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"Feeling Like Scattered Roses... When You Are Near"!
EPISODE THIRTEEN
FEELING LIKE
SCATTERED ROSES...
WHEN YOU ARE NEAR