...No...
...Please...
Don't!
Senketsu!
Good grief.
How many times will I have to
take care of you after you've passed out?
Did you decide to change careers and become a Nudist like me?
Make one more lame joke
and it'll be your last.
Ah, sorry, sorry.
So, who took you out?
It was Harime Nui. Nagita was Nui.
Oh, so that's what happened.
You found me unconscious,
dressed like this?
Yeah. If I had arrived
on the scene a little later,
you would've been arrested
by the cops for indecent exposure.
You got a death wish?
Touchy, aren't we?
...Of course I am. I...
I lost Senketsu.
To Harime Nui?
That's right. He was
chopped to pieces by her.
I was weak and I couldn't draw upon
...any of his power, and he got shredded...
I am not lost.
Any more lame impressions like that
and I really am gonna kill you.
Hey, give me a break.
I didn't say anything.
Ryuuko, calm yourself.
See, you're doing it again!
I have him right here.
Senketsu, you're alive?! I'm so glad!
Only because you
held on to me so tightly.
And the rest?
Where's the rest of you?
The sleeves? The shoulders? The skirt?
H-Huh?
I didn't see anything else
when I got there.
Just you, lying there unconscious,
clutching that scarf like your life depended on it.
Ryuuko, my shredded body has been
divided amongst the Battlefield Trip students.
So the rest of you is in Kansai, huh?
Exactly. It was Kiryuuin Satsuki's doing.
Damn her.
She's always getting in my way!
Huh? What's a teacher like you
doing here, Mr. Mikisugi?
Sorry to say, but I am
no longer a teacher.
The time has now come.
Today, I bid farewell to my cover identity as the
homeroom teacher for Honnouji Academy's Class 2-A.
Today, I return to my unadorned self!
As one of the unclothed warriors of Nudist Beach
who do battle against the threat of Life Fibers:
a Splendid Naked Officer,
Mikisugi Aikurou! Let's begin!
NUDIST BEACH SPLENDID
NAKED OFFICER
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
Come on, Nude Shooting Star!
Farewell, students of Honnouji Academy!
What the hell was that about?
EPISODE 14
RIDE LIKE THE WIND
dareka ga katteni kimeta readymade na
This is a readymade world that is at someone's beck and call
kyou wo nugisutete
I'll break free of its shackles
RYUUKO
MATOI
hadashi de hashitte iku
And sprint toward my goal
GAMAGOORI IRA
machigattatte
Even if I lose my way
GAMAGOORI IRA
SANAGEYAMA UZU
JAKUZURE NONON
INUMUTA HOUKA
korondatte
Or trip and fall
INUMUTA HOUKA
MANKANSHOKU FAMILY
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
surimuita itami mo
Those wounds will still create
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
KINAGASE
TSUMUGU
original na ashita ni naru
An original future for me
KIRYUUIN
SATSUKI
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
I hold my destiny in my own hands
chikai ga hikari ni natte
And it shines ever so brightly
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
So until the day I reach you
naiteru hima nante nai kara
I don't have the time to sit around crying
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
My burning passion pours out from within me
yozora de kagayaki dasu
And shines like a star in the night sky
umarete kita imi ga
I think I now understand
wakatta ki ga shita
Why I was born
negaigoto wa zenbu kono te de
I'll make all of my dreams come true
kanaeru
With my own hands
I have selected students
with high Life Fiber tolerance,
and I am distributing the various parts
of Godrobe Senketsu amongst them.
They will be affixed to their
Battlefield Trip-spec Ultima Uniforms,
and I will ascertain whether they can be employed
as a power-up item that will boost their abilities.
Good.
KYOTO
The Kyoto Battlefield Trip Brigade
under Jakuzure Nonon,
KOBE
the Kobe Battlefield Trip Brigade
under Gamagoori Ira
and the Osaka Battlefield Trip Brigade
under Sanageyama Uzu
OSAKA
have each arrived at their
respective destinations.
BIG THREE CITIES
SPECIAL INTELLIGENCE
UNIT
INUMUTA
HOUKA
The Big Three Cities Special
Intelligence Unit also stands ready.
We've already seized the information
gateways for each city's academies.
Their information networks have been isolated,
and all phone and net connections
are under our control.
Good.
This operation will place all of Kansai's
high schools under our umbrella in one fell swoop.
BIG THREE BATTLEFIELD TRIP
Big Three Battlefield Trip,
commence operation!
Kami-Kobe High School Armed Faction
Alliance Representative, Oobayashi Kyuuji!
KAMI-KOBE HIGH
SCHOOL ARMED
ACTION ALLIANCE
REPRESENTATIVE
OOBAYASHI
KYUUJI
KAMI-KOBE HIGH
SCHOOL ARMED
ACTION ALLIANCE
REPRESENTATIVE
OOBAYASHI
KYUUJI
KAMI-KOBE HIGH
SCHOOL ARMED
ACTION ALLIANCE
REPRESENTATIVE
OOBAYASHI
KYUUJI
KAMI-KOBE HIGH
SCHOOL ARMED
ACTION ALLIANCE
REPRESENTATIVE
OOBAYASHI
KYUUJI
KAMI-KOBE HIGH
SCHOOL ARMED
ACTION ALLIANCE
REPRESENTATIVE
OOBAYASHI
KYUUJI
Deputy Armed Faction
Alliance Representative, Sakuramiya Kenta!
DEPUTY ARMED
FACTION ALLIANCE
REPRESENTATIVE
SAKURAMIYA
KENTA
DEPUTY ARMED
FACTION ALLIANCE
REPRESENTATIVE
SAKURAMIYA
KENTA
DEPUTY ARMED
FACTION ALLIANCE
REPRESENTATIVE
SAKURAMIYA
KENTA
DEPUTY ARMED
FACTION ALLIANCE
REPRESENTATIVE
SAKURAMIYA
KENTA
DEPUTY ARMED
FACTION ALLIANCE
REPRESENTATIVE
SAKURAMIYA
KENTA
DEPUTY ARMED
FACTION ALLIANCE
REPRESENTATIVE
We won't let them take a
single step beyond this point!
Molotov cocktails! Cut loose!
We got help from the
American school, too!
We'll drive 'em out with the power of
their Armed American Football Corps!
I am Gamagoori Ira, Honnouji Academy
Battlefield Trip Kobe Region Brigade Leader!
BATTLEFIELD
TRIP KOBE
REGION
BRIGADE
LEADER
GAMAGOORI
IRA
If you engage in armed resistance,
we are prepared to retaliate in kind!
Enhanced Disciplinary
Bureau Members, deploy!
What the hell?
Your blood will nourish
our armored protective gear!
All hands, charge!
Let's go!
Fire!
Oh my God!
...What the...?!
To a student, school regulations
are heavier than stone!
The Disciplinary Guidebook in which
these rules are inscribed is harder than steel!
Honnouji Academy
Disciplinary Guidebook
Honnouji Academy's
school regulations are as steel!
Honnouji Academy
Disciplinary Guidebook
Ironclad rules!
Honnouji Academy
Disciplinary Guidebook
Do you believe that such armor
can withstand our ironclad rules?!
Taste our Full Metal Disciplinary
Guidebook Regulation Hurricane!
FULL METAL DISCIPLINARY - GUIDEBOOK REGULATION HURRICANE
I-Impossible!
Do you see now the might
of Honnouji Academy?!
This is the might of Student Council
President Kiryuuin Satsuki!
Let's play this fortissimo, everyone!
JAKUZURE NONON
BATTLEFIELD TRIP
KYOTO REGION
BRIGADE LEADER
What's up with this?
Welcome, warriors of the East.
Abekamo Academy,
which has stood for a thousand years
here in the ancient capital,
is the linchpin of Kyoto's defenses!
If you wish to avoid a painful death,
leave this place at once.
Fail to do so, and you will be baptized
by a flood of demons and monsters.
Listen to you, trying to sound big!
There aren't any schools that
have been around for a thousand years!
What are these things?
They're monsters!
They're gonna eat us!
Guardian Student of the North,
Genbu Tarou!
GUARDIAN
STUDENT
OF THE NORTH
GENBU
TAROU
Guardian Student of the South,
Suzaku Jirou!
GUARDIAN
STUDENT
OF THE SOUTH
SUZAKU
JIROU
Guardian Student of the East,
Seiryu Saburou!
GUARDIAN
STUDENT
OF THE EAST
SEIRYU SABUROU
Guardian Student of the West,
Byakko Shirou!
GUARDIAN
STUDENT
OF THE WEST
BYAKKO
SHIROU
Do you see?
This is the Divine Four Formation,
Abekamo Academy's
impenetrable defense!
You Kanto barbarians
cannot hope to defeat it!
What are you talking about?
It's so obvious that these
monsters are all illusions!
Stay calm, everyone!
This is just a psychological attack!
What a fascinating bunch.
Would you mind if I
fought them for a while?
Inumuta?! I thought you were in Osaka!
What are you doing here?
Don't be startled.
This is merely a hologram projected by the Film Club.
Armed Arts Club! Advance!
This is a non-Euclidean space creation ritual calculated by the Math Club.
Art Club members, use this
as a basis for a Paradox Painting!
Our EM field! Impossible!
ESCHER
TOPOLOGY
ATTACK
An Escher Topology Attack.
What's that?
The Divine Four Formation employs geomagnetism to
envelop this location in special electromagnetic waves,
thereby disrupting the
nerve signals of the human brain.
The picture they just drew altered this area's
phase space and disrupted its geomagnetism!
In short, they have negated
the school's EM field!
I didn't understand a word of that,
but I guess when it comes to
obnoxious jerks, it takes one to beat one.
Then I guess this should be
your forte, should it not?
You uncouth boors and your strange words!
You leave us no choice but to fight!
This isn't my scene.
I'll leave them in your capable hands.
Thanks for nothing.
Okay, let's get jazzed up!
Armed Wind Instrument Club!
Combat Orchestration!
Pomp and Circumstance 'em!
I'm surprised you made it this far,
you pitiful Honnouji Academy fleas.
NANIWA
KINMAN
HIGH
SCHOOL
STUDENT
COUNCIL
PRESIDENT
TAKARADA
KANEO
I am the Naniwa Kinman High School
Student Council President, Takarada Kaneo!
You might've thought you were
hot stuff after Kobe and Kyoto,
but you ain't so tough here in Osaka!
Well, well, you've heard
what happened in the other cities?
BATTLEFIELD
TRIP
OSAKA
REGION
BRIGADE
LEADER
SANAGEYAMA
UZU
I thought we'd cut off
your information gateways.
I hate to break it to ya,
but I have powerful allies
in the form of Osakan grannies.
They'll spread gossip and rumors
in the blink of an eye.
Even if you lock down the net,
you can't stop gossipin' grandmas!
Now, listen close.
I'm gonna tell ya the rules of this town.
Osaka here is a merchant town!
It's money that
makes this town go 'round!
Whoever has the most cash wins!
Money? Philistine.
We have come to bring down those
like you who reek of the old system
in order to create the new world order
that Kiryuuin Satsuki strives to achieve!
You're adorable.
You naïve, naïve thing.
Don't start soapboxin' about society
until you learn how fearsome money can be.
Time to make you wake up to reality
by smackin' you in the face with wads of cash!
All right, men! Let 'em have it!
We're gonna kill ya!
Guns?
It's bills, sir!
They're shooting at us
with wads of bills as bullets!
They're literally using money as a weapon!
I put my money where my mouth is!
Get it? Then get lost!
Judging from the feel, these aren't
genuine Bank of Japan notes, are they?
Counterfeit bills, huh?
They ain't counterfeit!
They're Takarada Bucks!
Takarada Bucks?
Exactly. They're redeemable paper currency.
The word of the wealthy Takarada Conglomerate
is as good as gold here in Osaka.
They have more value than
our debt-ridden national currency.
But I guess a northern Kanto hick
like you wouldn't understand any of that!
How dare you!
If you go on mocking northern Kanto,
I'll grind you up with our konjac root harvest!
Not if we turn you jerks
into takoyaki first! Get 'em!
Armed Ping Pong Club!
Advance forward!
Sumo Club, advance forward!
Sumo Stomp Attack!
Armed Archery Club, Armed Track Club!
Ultra long range squads! Salvo attack!
Not bad, kiddo!
Now, storm the school building!
Over my dead body! Force 'em back!
You can stand against Ultima Uniforms?!
The Kiryuuins ain't the
only big players around here.
Don't underestimate the might of
the Takarada Conglomerate's money!
I'm gonna be heartbroken if I come all this way to Osaka
and all I get to do is this stupid ball bucket brigade!
...Hey, that's...
It's the veritable symbol of Osaka!
Jumbo takoyaki sold by a street vendor!
It just isn't a trip to Osaka
without eating some of those!
OSAKA
But I've got no money!
I got dragged here without knowing why,
so I'm flat broke right now! Penniless!
Boy, I sure wish somebody would
fire some money my way!
There is! There's a guy who's
spreading money around with a gun!
Bastard! I'm gonna send ya straight to Hell!
Not to Hell! I'm going straight to Heaven!
Go on, shoot me!
Don't you dare get between
Mankanshoku Mako and something she wants!
Who the hell are you?
...No way...
Bye!
Hey, gramps! Takoyaki, please!
I've got plenty of cash!
That's the Osaka-style okonomiyaki
that you eat with a spatula instead of chopsticks,
and that's kushikatsu,
where you're not allowed to double dip!
And ketsune udon, not kitsune!
And best of all is the butaman,
the ikayaki, the negiyaki, and more!
Now this is Osaka!
A Victory Road of food!
You are all that remain!
Attack!
Sorry, did I surprise you?!
Here's a little something
we had the Russian mafia smuggle in.
I don't know 'bout no Ultima Uniforms,
but can clothes stand up to a tank?!
Don't make me repeat myself!
Our ironclad rules will tear through
the armor of a mere tank as if it were paper!
How's this?!
The very latest iteration of Kobe's
specialty, composite meat armor!
KOBE SPECIALITY
COMPOSITE
MEAT ARMOR
Your "ironclad rules" or whatever get swallowed up by that
beautiful Kobe beef marbling and melt away into nothing!
Now, be a good boy and surrender, Gamagoori.
Laughable! If you think
you can make me, let's see you try!
Dumbass! Fire!
Fortified Disciplinary Unit, forward!
Discipline!
Oh crap! It's coming back!
That's hot! Hot!
Ow! It burns!
The meat's cooking! Yum!
It's so good!
These powered Godrobe patches certainly are something else.
Magnificent. Now, finish them!
So much for your final trump card.
Surrender peacefully, Oobayashi!
You! Matoi!
I came to get Senketsu back!
Lovely! What a beautiful sound!
With a Godrobe in our band,
we can play such beautiful music together!
I guess that about does it.
Transfer student!
What are you doing here?!
I don't have time to
mess around with you.
What's with that attitude?!
Why?
My bamboo sword is more
than enough for the likes of you!
It sounds like Gamagoori and Jakuzure have wrapped things up on their end.
How are you coming along?
Most of the Kinman High
students have been dealt with.
Tell Lady Satsuki that Osaka
will soon be under our control.
I wouldn't be so sure about that!
Takarada?
You underestimate my power, friend.
The students aren't my only pawns!
Thank you, come again!
How's business?! Not too bad!
You're making civilians
fight for you too, you bastard?
I am indeed.
But it's not quite accurate
to call them civilians.
They're all Combat Citizens
who have been blinded by money.
Everyone in this town
right now is just itchin' to fight!
They're tough!
That's the newest Osakan spot,
the Naniwa Sky Tower!
Right! Let's climb it!
When you see a high place,
you just get this irresistible urge to climb it!
How d'you like fightin' against Takarada Kaneo
and the "I Heart Osaka" Brigade?
If you want to take Osaka,
you'll have to kill every last one of us!
In the end, the real thing that
motivates people is cold, hard cash!
You "heart" it, eh?
What's the sense in
destroying your own city?
We'll just rebuild it afterward!
The contractors will love
all the extra work thrown their way!
Okay, people!
Kill that man, and I'll give you
a million Takarada Bucks!
Make him suffer!
So how are you gonna deal
with all these people, huh?
...That's—
What's that light?
L-Lady Satsuki!
...Ow...
Huh?
Hey, that's from Ryuuko's uniform, Senketsu!
Hey, you're Mankanshoku, the second-year!
What're you doing here?
You deserted in the face of the enemy
to go goofing around, didn't you?
What do you think the
Battlefield Trip is about, anyway?
Purge her!
I'm sorry!
Ryuuko!
I see you're taking things easy
and enjoying the sights of Osaka, Mako.
Boy, am I glad to see you, Ryuuko!
Senketsu's all chopped to bits!
Yeah, but I'll get him back.
I'll take back every last piece
and make him good as new.
Oh, I get it, Ryuuko.
You're going to all this trouble
'cause he's the only uniform you have.
There is only one left, Ryuuko.
Really? How are you feeling?
Rather well.
You've changed, don't you think?
How so?
The only part of me currently
supplying you with power is this scarf.
But even now, you're able to take down the
Ultima Uniforms augmented by my fragments in one strike.
You've become even stronger
than before, don't you think?
I'm getting stronger?
It's because what you desire
is almost in reach!
You're concentrating as hard as you can
on your desire to get Senketsu back to normal.
I get the same way, but with money!
Yeah, you concentrate pretty hard on that.
Of course! You can't spell "concentrate" without "cent", after all!
Okay, one to go.
Can you tell where it is, Senketsu?
...Yes, I can. However...
What is it?
The holder of the final fragment
is Kiryuuin Satsuki.
Satsuki? Seriously?
Fine. I'll get you back,
no matter who I have to face.
But in my current condition,
I cannot activate Life Fiber Synchronize mode.
How do you intend to
fight an opponent like Satsuki?
Don't worry. I'll pick up the slack.
I'm not the usual Matoi Ryuuko right now.
I'm concentrating everything I have,
now that my goal is almost within reach.
Isn't that right, Mako?
Yeah!
...Ryuuko...
I'm coming for you, Kiryuuin Satsuki!
chime ga naru mae ni
Before the bell rings
kugurinuketa
I sneak out of school
otonatachi no haiiro no me
Avoiding the adults' vacant stares
tawai no nai kaiwa
The pointless conversations
togirenu mama
Keep going on and on
sakamichi wo kudatteku
As I walk down the slope
nani wo suru demo naku
I have nothing to do
yuku ate sae mo naku
And nowhere to go
tada atashi ima wa ne
Right now, all I do
donna chuukoku mo mimi wo surinukeru
Is ignore any and all warnings
mada mada suki ni sasete
Because I still want to be free
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
To be an exemplary student
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
rojiura no nukemichi
And take the back alley
amai yuuwaku wa michi
A path of mysterious sweet temptation
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Osaka, a town where money talks!
OSAKA
Cash-crazy Osaka!
In search of her scattered Godrobe Senketsu,
Ryuuko dives into the fray!
SCATTERED
GODROBE SENKETSU
Will Godrobe Senketsu be revived in the end?! Oh, right, that's me.
IN THE END
GODROBE SENKETSU
THAT'S ME
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"Don't Stop Me Now"!
EPISODE 15
DON'T STOP ME NOW