...Those are COVERS...
Run, everyone! Run!
...Beautiful...
Ryuuko!
Very few humans are merged
this perfectly with Life Fibers.
Truly, you are my daughter.
No way! Ryuuko's the
daughter of the director?!
I'm being pulled up!
Mako!
Sis!
Cut the thread!
Escape, Mankanshoku!
Mankanshoku!
Somebody help!
Shut up!
My dad is Matoi Isshin!
You can't be my mother!
That's impossible!
If I'm not, then how do you
explain that body of yours?
I said shut up!
Calm yourself, Ryuuko!
Stay out of this!
How very, very interesting!
I knew there was something
special about you!
You're the greatest, Ryuuko!
...I'm... not... done yet...
Lady Satsuki!
Satsuki!
EPISODE 19
RAINDROPS KEEP FALLING ON MY HEAD
unmei no ito wo tachikitta sono saki ni
It all begins when we sever the threads of fate
senobi shiteitanda
I was trying to be someone I'm not
kutsuzure darake no
In a cramped world
semai sekai de
With no breathing room
runway wo aruku
As I walked down my runway
egao no uragawa
I thought I'd concealed it
kakushita tsumori de
Behind the smile that masked my face
dakedo itsumo kimi ni wa
But it doesn't work on you
minukarete shimatte ite
You always see through my facade
konna no wa hajimete de
Nobody's ever unraveled me like this before
tomadou kedo
I don't know what to do
hoka no dare ni mo kikonasenai
Nobody else can pull these outfits off
nandaka wakannai
A somewhat ambiguous fever
atsusa ga mune wo kogasu kara
Threatens to burn our hearts away
unmei no ito taguriyoseta sono saki ni
It all begins once we rein in the threads of fate
ima atarashii yoake ga kuru
A new day will dawn for us
omoi wa kitto hitotsu
We must be one in spirit
ONE
MONTH
LATER
Hurry, Guts!
Get outta my way,
you stinkin' business suit!
How d'ya like that?!
Oh, crap! Could this be the end of
the line for Mankanshoku Matarou?!
Return to the rags whence you came!
You're that chick from the Four Devas!
...Oh, you're that slacker's—
The streets are crawling
...with these scraps of cloth...
Let's get out of here!
Then follow me!
So you kids have survived on
your own this past month, huh?
You're that slacker's kid brother, all right.
Your ability to survive is the
one impressive thing about you.
The name's Matarou!
Come on. My ride's waiting over there.
SUSUKIGAHARA,
NORTHERN KANTO
Run! Run!
Hurry! There's a chopper
waiting just across this hill!
Damn, they caught up, huh?
...Hold together...
Blade Regalia Mk 3!
THREE-STAR ULTIMA UNIFORM
BLADE REGALIA MK 3
STAR
THREE
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
BLADE
REGALIA MK 3
Crap! It's finally reached its limit, huh?
Boss! We'll hold 'em off here!
...You guys...
We of the Northern Kanto
Gang Leader Alliance have our own pride!
Understood. Show those rag bastards
what human beings will do
when their backs are against the wall!
Okay, guys, cut loose!
Tear 'em a new one from the inside!
Hurry! Climb aboard
while they're distracted!
...I'm sorry, guys...
I saw your Northern Kanto
hooligans prove their resolve.
This is a war of attrition.
We won't last long.
True.
Even so, we did manage
to save a few lives.
Their sacrifice wasn't in vain.
OSAKA
NUDIST BEACH SECRET BASE
Show the people we rescued
to the living quarters area!
Good work. Looks like
you guys had it rough, too.
Yeah.
Is that Mankanshoku's little brother?
He and his friends had been living
in the sewers under Honnou Town.
They're an impressive pack of rats.
I said the name's
Mankanshoku Matarou, Deva chick!
I'm Jakuzure Nonon.
Call me Lady Nonon, slacker's brother!
If you want others to call you by name,
address them properly first, Jakuzure.
I'm ever so sorry,
Mr. Disciplinary Bureau Chairman.
The Northern Kanto
Gang Leader Alliance has also fallen.
NUDIST BEACH COMMAND CENTER
This means that all academies that
were under Honnouji Academy's control
have fallen to COVERS.
Which means that the bastions of the resistance
movement Satsuki built to fight the Life Fibers
have been lost.
Sanageyama also lost his Ultima Uniform,
which was the last we had left.
All we have left now are Jakuzure's
Bakuzan-Gako and Gamagoori's Bakuzan-Kouryu.
Both were reforged from
Lady Satsuki's shattered Bakuzan.
We also have my Tailor's Dagger
and your Doutonbori Robo.
DTR.
Whatever.
"DTR", got it?
I only hope that the item that
Iori is frantically working on
will be ready in time.
We would have had more proper facilities
if you people hadn't destroyed them all.
If you were planning to
rebel against Ragyou,
I think you could have at least considered
the option of joining forces with Nudist Beach.
The more people who know a secret,
the more likely it is to be exposed.
Even at Honnouji Academy, the only people
who were aware of Lady Satsuki's true intentions
were us Four Devas,
Iori from the Sewing Club,
and her butler, Soroi.
Well, considering that I never realized you guys
knew I was undercover, I can't really talk.
But why hasn't there been any
media attention or public uproar
despite COVERS attacking
academies all over Japan?
The masses have already
been mentally influenced.
Clothing made by Kiryuuin Ragyou's REVOCS Inc.
has spread through the entire population.
The Life Fibers woven into them are
manipulating the minds of their wearers
and devouring any unnecessary
information from their brains.
"They have eyes but fail to see
and ears but fail to hear", huh?
Well, they do use human
psychogalvanism as their energy source.
Honnouji Academy's students
have been building up a resistance to Life Fiber
manipulation by wearing Ultima Uniforms.
She feigns obedience to Ragyou,
only to use her money to
...raise an army to defeat her...
That Kiryuuin Satsuki girl
is a real piece of work.
Mr. Soroi here is even more impressive,
having feigned ignorance
while serving Satsuki as her butler.
I merely made tea.
As I do now.
However, I have not given up
on making more tea for Lady Satsuki.
You're right.
After all, even us Four Devas survived.
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
What about the other one?
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Infirmary
(Back
Alley)
Ryuuko... Why won't
you wake up, Ryuuko?
I'm so sorry that we can't
communicate with you, Senketsu.
The rest of us can't
tell what you're saying.
...Mrs. Mankanshoku...
But it's plain as day that you're alive,
that you're Ryuuko's Sunday best,
and that you're worried sick about her.
Mrs. Mankanshoku!
...Now, now...
If I were twenty years younger,
I'd wear you in a heartbeat.
How is Ryuuko today?
I can't tell one way or the other.
But the wound from when her heart was
pulled out has already healed completely.
How do I put this?
It's downright inhuman.
What did you say?!
Calm down!
You carried Ryuuko's unconscious body to us.
Even if we can't talk to each other, we understand how you feel.
Well, when a patient wants to sleep,
it's best to let them sleep.
After all, she's been through a lot.
I still can't believe that Ryuuko's
...mother was Kiryuuin Ragyou...
Dr. Matoi never mentioned
anything about it to me, either.
If I'd known sooner, maybe I could've
done something to soften the blow.
What's done is done.
Sometimes things work out
if you just stay alive.
Dad!
You're alive!
You're a Mankanshoku boy, all right!
See, sometimes things do work out.
True.
I'm sorry. I never found Sis.
Boy, you were searching
for Mankanshoku?
Yeah. I thought that if
I stayed in Honnou Town,
I might be able to find that
dishrag that swallowed Sis,
but before I knew it, it was
all I could do just to stay alive.
I'm proud of you for trying, Matarou.
Don't grieve just yet!
Mankanshoku girls don't die that easy.
Listen, boy! I will rescue
your sister, no matter what!
I, Gamagoori Ira, will devote
myself, body and soul!
Ow! You're breaking my collarbone!
Dad!
Oh, that's broken, all right.
That'll be ten million yen in damages, buddy.
Ten million?!
When I look at your family,
it gives me hope that the
human race can yet survive.
HONNOUJI ACADEMY
You have certainly exceeded
all of my expectations.
In terms of your foolishness, at least.
The students at the academies
that Honnouji Academy had conquered
have all been assimilated by COVERS.
If humans wear clothing for the
first twenty years of their lives,
their resistance to clothing
completely disappears.
So you planned to defeat me using students
in their late teens, who hadn't lost that resistance.
But it was all for nothing.
The more your followers resist,
the more they nourish COVERS
as their energy sources.
And before long, even your
little sister will return to me.
My little sister... Matoi Ryuuko?
Yes.
To think that she was the baby I
thought had died all those years ago.
Souichirou had deceived me
about a great many things.
...Matoi and I... are siblings...
He was a stupid man.
Souichirou faked his own death
and entrusted his revenge to you.
At the same time, he changed his face
and body to become Matoi Isshin,
and not only did he raise
the baby whose death he faked,
he founded that silly Nudist Beach
organization and gave a Godrobe to Ryuuko.
...Dad... I...
...I...
Ignorant of all this, you earnestly believed everything
he had said and plotted your rebellion against me.
It's so noble that it brings tears to my eyes!
What garbage.
As if a woman whose very tear glands
are Life Fibers could cry.
Even if that were the case,
I am your mother.
You should graciously accept
any kind words I have to offer.
Kindness ill becomes you.
Are you sure?
I'd like to think that my sparing
your life was out of maternal kindness.
Garbage.
You're letting me live because
I'm more valuable this way.
No more, no less.
Oh? How so?
Shinra-Kouketsu.
You also know about that, do you?
I put two and two together.
I see.
In that case, I suggest you bring
the rage in your heart to boiling point!
The deeper your rage,
the more useful you are to me!
The work is progressing smoothly, I see.
I have to hand it to Satsuki!
The Sewing Club members here
are pretty capable!
So it was worth the trouble
of mentally refitting them, eh?
They're way better than COVERS!
Is Satsuki doing well?
Yes. She was dying to wear
this outfit as soon as she could.
Non, she won't wear it!
Satsuki's gonna get eaten by it.
By my masterpiece.
Anyway, it's Ryuuko that
we need to worry about!
Yes, I know. I've already taken steps.
Having two teenage daughters
does keep one busy.
Both of them have grown into
fine young ladies, just like their mother!
La vie est drôle!
Yes, life is indeed most droll.
I can hardly wait to show this to them.
The ultimate Godrobe.
They're finally here.
We'll hold out as best as we can.
As long as you're alive,
things will work out.
It's pretty unusual for you
to sound so wishy-washy.
Maybe so.
DTR, launching! Brace for impact!
Use this.
Swords are more your thing.
Thank you.
Well, let's get going, Monkey.
Looks like I finished up just in time.
It's ready?!
In theory, yes. Give it a test run.
There's a whole bunch here, too.
It's like they're having
a winter clearance sale.
"A whole bunch" vs. five, huh?
I might just cry.
Stand firm!
We five are stronger than anyone!
Do you seriously mean that?
We've got to give it everything we've got.
Well, I'll do my best.
That's the Mankanshoku family's pet dog!
Could it be?!
Let's try this out right now!
Mankanshoku!
She's out!
Cloth-form COVERS are fed energy from their
parent body, the Original Life Fiber, via a linkage thread.
That's why we can cause them to
shut down by severing the thread.
However, human-form COVERS have
swallowed humans to use as energy sources,
so they can operate autonomously!
If we can extract the human within, the COVERS
will lose their energy source and shut down!
...Yes! We thin out their number...
...and rescue our allies!...
A weapon combining
offense and defense!
This is the Super Suction Saver!
SUPER
SUCTION
SAVER
In Heaven's stead, I smite clothing!
IN HEAVEN'S STEAD, I SMITE CLOTHING
Wow, I'm saved!
Mankanshoku, are you all right?
Yep! Mankanshoku Mako has returned!
Wait, you saved me, Gamagoori?!
Yes. I gave your little brother my word.
In any case, put this on.
Whoa, I'm in my birthday suit!
All right, enough flirting.
If it works, go rescue more people.
Hold up! How do you put this thing on?
I am not flirting!
We'll talk later.
I'm stuck!
Get clear, Mankanshoku.
Kay!
Hang on, isn't this Osaka?
When did I get back here?
Hey!
Mako, you're okay!
Sis!
Dad! Matarou!
What are they doing?!
What is this, the COVERS Orchestra Club?
Are they calling me out?
What's this noise?
...Oh, dear...
...That's—
Ryuuko!
Enough screeching, you bastards!
Get lost!
...What the—
With just one blow?!
And she even extracted the people inside!
Ryuuko! You're awake!
Get away from me!
I'm done with you.
I'm never putting you on again.
Ryuuko!
Just looking at you pisses me off!
'Cause we're both the
same breed of monster!
That's right! I'm not human!
I'm a Life Fiber monster!
kurikaesu mainichi ga
My monotonous everyday life
totsuzen iro wo kaeru
Took on a new hue
sonna koto dokka nozonde itanda kedo ne
A part of me always wished for that to happen
iza to naru to
But when it actually did
okubyoumono deshita
I was too scared to act
himitsu ne
That's a secret, okay?
hitori furuete
Trembling alone
soshite kimi ni aitakute
I miss you so much
zutto mikata da yo nante ieta nara
If only I could tell you that I'll always be on your side
muteki
We could be invincible
sou sa tobidatsu toki wa futari de
When we take flight, we'll do so together
tachimukai
We'll make a stand
kakaekirenai okubyou ni
I don't want to go back
zutto hitatte waratte ita
To being the bumbling coward I was
hitori kiri zutsu ga awasatte
Every little thing will come together
ookina chikara ni naru yo
To give us great strength
ima nee kanjita
That's how I feel right now
Damn you, Ragyou.
You let me live so
you could use me, did you?
Well, that was a miscalculation on your part.
So long as I still draw breath,
I, Kiryuuin Satsuki,
still have a chance at victory!
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Hello, everyone!
I have sad news for you today!
SAD NEWS
This will be the final preview for
the television broadcast of this show!
From now on, please tune in
to the web previews!
WEB PREVIEWS
Our battle is only just beginning!
JUST BEGINNING
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"Far from the Maddening Crowds."
EPISODE 20
FAR FROM THE MADDENING CROWDS