N-Now, now,
let's calm down, Ryuuko.
Don't give me that!
What the hell is going on?
Were you in cahoots with
that mohawked man too?
I-I have no idea what you mean.
Just try and play dumb
after you see this!
See? Here's you and the mohawked guy in the background, clear as day!
—Th-That's not—
After the mohawked guy attacked me, I asked Matarou to track him down.
That kid has connections
all over this town.
And he found pictures of a guy drinking booze who matched the description.
That also explains why
he brought me to your place.
He almost killed me, dammit!
So what the hell is your deal?!
And yet, wouldn't you say he brought you and Senketsu closer together?
His name is Kinagase Tsumugu.
I admit that he is a member of my organization.
After clashing in battle with him,
you and Senketsu have become true partners!
Now that Kiryuuin Satsuki
has her hands on a Godrobe,
only a partnership forged in
the heat of battle can defeat her!
You're just tryin' to make up a
justification after the fact, aren't you?!
I knew it!
That bastard tried to kill Senketsu!
Who are you people?!
I thought you were fighting
against the Kiryuuins!
Didn't you say that you'd
need Senketsu to do that?
What are those "Life Fiber" things, anyway?
What was my dad researching?!
Calm down.
Once I'm certain I can trust you,
I'll tell you everything.
I'm tired of hearing
that excuse from you!
Nudist Beach.
Huh?
We're Nudist Beach.
Have you lost it?
It's the name of our
organization. Nudist Beach!
Forget it. I was stupid to think I could expect a straight answer out of you.
Ryuuko?
Fine, I get it! I'll keep fighting
and growing stronger.
That's what you want, right?
But that really is our name.
Oh well, it worked out in the end.
EPISODE 6
DON'T TOY WITH ME ON A WHIM
dareka ga katteni kimetara kimeru you na
This is a world that is at someone's beck and call
kyou wo nugisutete
I'll break free of its shackles
RYUUKO
MATOI
hadashi de hashitte iku
And sprint toward my goal
GAMAGOORI IRA
machigattatte
Even if I lose my way
GAMAGOORI IRA
SANAGEYAMA UZU
JAKUZURE NONON
INUMUTA HOUKA
korondatte
Or trip and fall
INUMUTA HOUKA
MANKANSHOKU FAMILY
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
surimuita itami mo
Those wounds will still create
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
KINAGASE
TSUMUGU
original na ashita ni naru
An original future for me
KIRYUUIN
SATSUKI
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
I hold my destiny in my own hands
chikai ga hikari ni natte
And it shines ever so brightly
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
So until the day I reach you
naiteru hima nante nai darou
I don't have the time to sit around crying
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
My burning passion pours out from within me
yozora de kagayaki dasu
And shines like a star in the night sky
umarete kita imi ga
I think I now understand
wakatta ki ga shita
Why I was born
negaigoto ga zenbu kono te de
I'll make all of my dreams come true
kanaeru
With my own hands
SEWING CLUB RESEARCH LAB
UNDERGROUND PARKING LOT
Okay. Load the Life Fibers into the vault.
SEWING
CLUB
PRESIDENT
IORI SHIROU
I wonder what Lady Satsuki intends to do with so many Life Fibers?
She means to mass-produce
Ultima Uniforms.
What else could they be for?
LIFE
FIBER
But every time we've proposed increasing the number of Two-Star Ultima Uniforms to bolster our ranks,
she personally vetoed the suggestion.
If we focus on increasing the quantity of
club presidents, we risk lowering the overall quality.
That was Lady Satsuki's primary concern.
However, she has deemed it necessary to increase the club president head count despite the risks.
I guess this means that Matoi Ryuuko's arrival has set things into motion in a big way.
Yeah. In fact, the Anti-Uniform Guerilla himself showed up the other day.
And the clincher is that Lady Satsuki has chosen to don a Godrobe herself.
I'm amazed that there are even two people out there who can handle a uniform made entirely of Life Fibers.
To be frank, I have trouble believing it.
Wow! There's something out there that not even Inumuta, Intelligence and Tactics Officer, can believe?
It's just one unbelievable
thing after another, really.
That's what makes this
academy so fascinating.
Ah, I see.
Personally, I came here because I heard
that I'd be able to fight with my full strength.
That Matoi is worthy of
my complete attention.
Hold on, Sanageyama.
Have you forgotten that Lady Satsuki ordered us Four Devas to simply stand by and watch?
Oh? Did she really say that?
It is rather draining, isn't it?
Please try not to
overexert yourself, milady.
Don't worry. This is the path I chose.
Your tea warms me
through and through, Soroi.
Thank you, milady.
Did you think you'd managed to get behind me, Sanageyama?
Of course not.
If I'd had the slightest intent to attack,
you could have easily killed me with just that teacup.
What do you want, then?
Allow me to fight Matoi.
Why?
Need you even ask?
I believe you know perfectly well what happens whenever I catch sight of someone powerful.
Just like three years ago, then?
THREE YEARS AGO
NORTHERN KANTO, SUSUKIGAHARA
One against five hundred, eh?
This will prove once and for all whether Kiryuuin Satsuki is fit to lead us.
I suggest you start
practicing your bow, then.
I'm Sanageyama Uzu, Northern Kanto Gang Leader Alliance Representative!
NORTHERN KANTO GANG LEADER
ALLIANCE REPRESENTATIVE SANAGEYAMA UZU
MIDDLE
SCHOOL
THIRD
YEAR
You've got guts, Kiryuuin,
picking a fight with me!
I have no intention of fighting you.
I expect you to surrender.
KIRYUUIN SATSUKI
MIDDLE
SCHOOL
THIRD
YEAR
Who do you think you're screwin' with?!
You stopped them
with just your spirit, huh?
But that won't work on me!
I've seen through your moves!
You're mine!
Did you think you'd
managed to get behind me?
Come.
I'll provide you with the ultimate stage
—where you can unleash your full strength—
the stage called Honnouji Academy.
My bamboo sword is itching to test out the skills of this girl
who managed to infiltrate
the stage you provided for me.
I trust you understand
the price of failure?
Not to worry.
With these eyes, I can't possibly lose.
Nicely blocked.
I've managed to grow strong enough to
defeat your middle-school self in battle.
That was the way you
moved three years ago.
I assume you were holding back.
Very well. See what you can do.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
If I win, treat me to tea or something.
I've done you a discourtesy, Soroi.
Not at all, milady, though I do find it
a shame. That was your favorite cup.
Make a fresh pot for me.
Certainly, milady.
Hello. You have reached the Honnouji Academy Student Council President's Office.
Y-Yes, ma'am. One moment, ma'am.
It is Mistress Ragyo.
This is Satsuki.
What's this I hear about you
putting on your wedding dress?
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
Challenge To A Duel
Attention, Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A:
I will be waiting in the
Kendo Club dojo after school.
— Sanageyama Uzu
SPORTS
GYM #1
That wild monkey
beat us to the punch.
If I'd gotten permission to make a move on her, I would've taken her out first.
Where is Lady Satsuki?
She has gone out.
She said this battle
was not worth watching.
What's that supposed to mean?
So you've come, Matoi.
I was summoned by name
by one of the Four Devas.
How could I run away
after such an invitation?
I like your spirit!
Let's get right to it!
Three-Star Ultima Uniform: Blade Regalia!
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
BLADE REGALIA
It's not just the Godrobes
that can transform!
I'm impressed, Deva!
Time for me to follow suit!
Life Fiber Synchronize, Godrobe Senketsu!
GODROBE
SENKETSU
...Why, you...
I can read all your moves!
Senketsu! I'm going full speed!
Understood!
—What the—
Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
No matter how quickly you move, you can't outrun my blade!
Behold! Secret Technique: Heaven's Eye!
HEAVEN'S
EYE
As long as I have these eyes, I can
anticipate any move my opponent makes!
Say what?!
For every motion a human makes, there is a preparatory motion.
Be it a movement of the eyes
or a twitch of the muscles,
ORBICULARIS
OCULI
DORSAL
INTEROSSEOUS
ADDUCTOR
POLLICIS
Sanageyama instantly reads
all of those preparatory motions
PECTORALIS
MAJOR
GLUTEUS
MAXIMUS
and pre-empts any move
his opponent attempts to make.
That is the power of the Heaven's Eye.
And his Ultima Uniform succeeds
magnificently in amplifying that ability.
Gosh, Mr. Wild Monkey has
learned some new tricks, hasn't he?
Is that what Lady Satsuki meant when she
...said this fight was not worth watching? But...
I didn't hear it that way at all.
Keep it together, Ryuuko!
I'd love to, but it's all I can do just to deflect these strikes!
I'm impressed!
But let's see how you handle... this!
God-Speed Thousand Thrusts!
Now I can read all your
attempts to block me, too!
Even your Ultima Uniform-destroying
Sword Scissor is worthless if it can't hit its target!
Come on, is that all you've got?
A little disappointing, don't you think?
That's more like it!
Senketsu. I have a favor to ask of you.
I understand. Bet it all on
a single roll of the dice, eh?
Ryuuko!
You're mine!
T-They won't come off!
M-My eyes!
Now!
Finishing Move: Thread Stripper!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
Oh, dear. He went and lost.
It would appear that this is what Lady Satsuki was referring to.
You did it, Ryuuko!
You beat one of the Four Devas already!
You're amazing! And so fast!
And so awesome! Yeah!
This isn't over yet!
I can still fight! Come on, Matoi!
Don't be pathetic, Sanageyama!
You have disgraced the Four Devas!
One who over-relies on a single skill will be brought low by that very same skill, huh?
BACK-ALLEY DOCTOR
MANKANSHOKU
Ah, that hits the spot.
It feels good?
Yes, irons are wonderful.
It feels like all the wrinkles in my body are
melting away as my Life Fibers line up one by one.
I'm glad my plan for you to
blind Sanageyama worked.
Being cut up was rather
painful, I'll have you know.
Sorry about that.
Don't worry about it.
If we hadn't won, I wouldn't be enjoying this pleasant ironing.
True.
And make sure to get
behind my lapels, too.
Be through about it.
Man, you're one demanding
article of clothing, you know that?
Ryuko's mumbling
to her uniform again.
I think it's fine.
Who's there?!
Iori, I have a favor to ask of you.
How was your mother's disposition?
I explained to her
why I took out Junketsu.
You needn't worry, Soroi.
I've no time for losers, Sanageyama.
I was overconfident in my eyesight.
Please give me one more chance!
I'll defeat Matoi for certain next time!
Pathetic.
I don't need subordinates
who lack resolve.
But resolve I have,
and here is my proof!
Challenge
HONNOUJIGAHARA
Giving someone who was
beaten a second chance?
You're a soft touch, Kiryuuin Satsuki.
Let's see how how soft you think
I am after the fight, Matoi Ryuuko.
Observe what happens
when you force a man to change.
Three-Star Ultima Uniform:
Blade Regalia Mk 2!
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
BLADE REGALIA
MK 2
Be careful, Ryuuko.
I'm getting a totally
different vibe to last time.
Let's work fast, then.
Life Fiber Synchronize, Godrobe Senketsu!
GODROBE
SENKETSU
Sorry about this, Senketsu.
I've covered up every last eye you've got!
Now you can't use your Heaven's Eye!
Look, Ryuuko!
His eyes are shut!
Iori, I want you to sew my eyes shut.
But if I did that,
you'd lose your Heaven's Eye!
That's all right.
I lost due to my own overconfidence.
Unless my eyes are sewn shut,
I can never beat Matoi!
This is the resolve of a man who has realized
the error of his ways and sacrificed everything!
Know that as you face him, Matoi!
Here I come.
What is this intimidating aura?
Head!
Body!
Wrist!
Oh, crap! These aren't the moves of someone with no eyes!
You're terrified, aren't you, Matoi?
Say what?!
The sound of your breathing.
The smell of your sweat.
I can see the inner workings
of your mind as clear as day.
I can see it far, far more clearly than I could with my eyes!
Everything about this world!
The Mind's Eye.
Sealing his eyes shut boosted his affinity with his Ultima Uniform.
Head! Body! Wrist!
That Ultima Uniform is now
Sanageyama's eyes! His nose! His ears!
Head! Body! Wrist!
He has acquired the Mind's Eye,
which surpasses even the Heaven's Eye.
MIND'S EYE
None can evade his attacks!
Head! Body! Wrist!
Without your weapon, you have
no means of turning the tables this time.
So you'd think, right?
—What the—
I thought I told you that
I could see the entire world.
Did you think your pathetic
little trick would work?
Head!
Body! Wrist!
Head! Body! Wrist!
Head!
It's all over.
—It's—
What?!
What? What happened?
The Ultima Uniform overheated!
This was no disgrace, Sanageyama.
It was the result of your own power
outstripping that of the Ultima Uniform.
Yes, ma'am.
Matoi, you got lucky this time.
That was a close call.
Yes, I guess the Four Devas
of Honnouji aren't all show.
That guy was seriously tough.
But I can't run away from this.
I have to learn the truth
behind Dad's death!
I swapped out the Life Fibers in
your Ultima Uniform and restitched it.
It should be able to keep up
with even your movements now.
Thanks.
Did you think you'd managed to get behind me, Sanageyama?
Front and behind
mean nothing to me now.
Now that my eyes have been sewn shut, I can sense the world in its entirety.
I only came to thank you
for giving me a fresh start.
Wait.
We had an agreement.
Let's have tea.
Thank you, but I'll pass.
My other senses have become so heightened that my tongue can no longer bear the heat.
chime ga naru mae ni
Before the bell rings
kokuu ni muketa
The adults' vacant stares
otonatachi no haiiro no me
Drift into empty space
tawai no nai kaiwa
The pointless conversations
togirenu mama
Keep going on and on
sakamichi wo kudatteku
As I walk down the slope
nani wo suru demo naku
I have nothing to do
yuku ate sae mo naku
And nowhere to go
tada atashi ima wa ne
Right now, all I do
donna chuukoku mo mimi wo surinukeru
Is ignore any and all warnings
mada mada suki ni sasete
Because I still want to be free
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
To be an exemplary student
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
rojiura no nukemichi
And take the back alley
amai yuuwaku na michi
A path of sweet temptation
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
The Mankanshoku family had a dream.
Four people in a one-room house,
along with a dog and a freeloader.
FAMILY
DOG
A FREELOADER
This poor family suddenly find
themselves living in the lap of luxury!
POOR
LUXURY
Walk on air as you aim for the top!
TOP
WALK ON AIR
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"A Loser I Can't Hate".
EPISODE 7
A LOSER I CAN'T HATE