Welcome back, Lady Satsuki.
You did well on the
Big Three Battlefield Trip.
Thank you.
How did it go with the Director?
She was pleased with our results.
She has also decided to pay
a visit to Honnouji Academy.
...Then...
Yes. It is time at last.
I'll be counting on you four.
Students of Honnouji Academy!
You did well on the
Big Three Battlefield Trip!
We eradicated the dens of the
Kansai forces and anti-clothing guerillas
and completed our mission.
For that reason, we will welcome
Honnouji Academy Director Kiryuuin Ragyou,
and in the Ragyou Stadium
that bears her name,
we will hold a grand ceremony!
Welcome the Director by putting forth all the
energies that you have stored up within you!
This is the Honnouji Academy
Great Culture and Sports Festival!
GREAT
CULTURE
AND SPORTS
FESTIVAL
EPISODE 17
WHY DO YOU
unmei no ito wo tachikitta sono saki ni
It all begins when we sever the threads of fate
senobi shiteitanda
I was trying to be someone I'm not
kutsuzure darake no
In a cramped world
semai sekai de
With no breathing room
runway wo aruku
As I walked down my runway
egao no uragawa
I thought I'd concealed it
kakushita tsumori de
Behind the smile that masked my face
dakedo itsumo kimi ni wa
But it doesn't work on you
minukarete shimatte ite
You always see through my facade
konna no wa hajimete de
Nobody's ever unraveled me like this before
tomadou kedo
I don't know what to do
hoka no dare ni mo kikonasenai
Nobody else can pull these outfits off
nandaka wakannai
A somewhat ambiguous fever
atsusa ga mune wo kogasu kara
Threatens to burn our hearts away
unmei no ito taguriyoseta sono saki ni
It all begins once we rein in the threads of fate
ima atarashii yoake ga kuru
A new day will dawn for us
omoi wa kitto hitotsu
We must be one in spirit
Fine by me.
I was just thinking I needed
to settle things with you.
Right now, you don't have
your Godrobe or your scissor.
Do you honestly think a
half-naked high schooler can beat me?
You think your threats are gonna faze me?
I can go full-on naked if it'll even the odds.
No, you can't!
A girl only reveals
herself in her full glory
to the person she loves most
in the whole, wide world!
Can you honestly say that you love
Mr. Mohawk that deeply, Ryuuko?
Uh, that's not the point.
After all, the reason you wear Senketsu
is because you love him the most, right?
You'd never be able to wear a piece of
living clothing otherwise. That'd just be icky!
That's what it means for a maiden
to entrust her bare skin to someone!
Ryuuko, I am flattered that
you are angry on my behalf.
But I still say this:
put me on.
...Senketsu...
If you don't, you'll catch cold.
That's what you're worried about?
I can't believe you two.
Playing at being friends
with clothing again, huh?
I don't feel like shooting them anymore.
This is Osaka?
It's horrible.
I suppose it is.
This is all the result of
the Life Fibers' power,
as well as yours and mine.
Yeah.
Mikisugi was right to keep us
in the dark up until now.
Even looking at this, it beggars belief to be told
that Life Fibers are lifeforms from outer space.
This, coming from you?
I guess I'm just scared.
It's like, this started off
as me pickin' a fight
and turned into some grand battle
full of crazy crap I don't understand,
like the fate of humanity and the
extinction of the species or whatever.
I really just wanted to say that I
didn't give a crap about any of that.
But I pinned the cause of
my anger on you instead.
No, you really did get angry
on my behalf, Ryuuko.
That's the kind of person you are.
What's his deal?
Kinagase Tsumugu's older sister
died in a Life Fiber experiment.
After Dr. Matoi founded Nudist Beach,
his top assistant was
Tsumugu's sister, Kinagase Kinue.
Only Life Fibers can fight Life Fibers,
so they needed to create Life Fibers
that would obey a human's will.
That was the purpose of
Dr. Matoi and Kinue's research.
...But during one fateful experiment...
So she's the "foolish woman"
he mentioned, huh?
Earlier, he said that I'd share her fate.
Oh, right.
"Please continue the experiments."
Those were Kinue's dying words.
Dr. Matoi made further improvements
and completed Godrobe Senketsu.
Senketsu's Life Fibers have been spliced
with your central nervous system's DNA.
What?!
That's why he can only communicate
with and be worn by you.
He's a combat uniform that
Dr. Matoi made specifically for you.
Why would Dad do something like that?
He said he did it to protect you.
What the hell, man?
Your tea.
Thank you.
I've drunk a lot of your tea, haven't I, Soroi?
Indeed. I have been making it
for you since you were five.
Ah, yes.
Ever since that day.
The day father showed me
Junketsu for the first time.
That day, Father said to me:
This will be your wedding dress.
"This will be your wedding dress."
So I have heard.
I suppose it was on that day
that all this really began.
It seems like only yesterday.
Even this tea that I once found so bitter
is now the most delicious
thing in the world to me.
What is it?
You... found it bitter?
Did I never mention that?
From the very first cup, you smiled,
saying that it was delicious.
To think you were merely humoring me
...and enduring the bitterness...
I beg your forgiveness.
It's ancient history now.
I suppose I was a
kindhearted girl back then.
Form up! At attention! Listen closely!
Tomorrow, the Great Culture and Sports Festival
will be held at Honnouji Academy!
All No-Star students and their parents are to
welcome Director Kiryuuin from the spectator seats!
Ceremonial dress uniforms
will be distributed to all of you!
Gather at the stadium entrance
in these uniforms by 8:30 AM!
Tardiness will not be tolerated!
Unkempt dress will not be tolerated!
Assume that even the slightest breach
of etiquette will carry the death penalty!
Dismissed!
Wait just one minute!
And who are you?!
Mankanshoku Barazou,
father of Class 2-A's Mankanshoku Mako!
Sukuyo, his wife!
Matarou, their firstborn son!
Guts, guts!
What a well-mannered family.
Even the dog introduces itself.
What do you want?
Where is Mako?
I heard that Mako was
conscripted for the Battlefield Trip.
The other students have returned,
but not Mako or Ryuuko.
What's the meaning of this?
Matoi and Mankanshoku?
They are rebels.
As the family of rebels, your home is to be confiscated
and you are to be banished from Honnou Town!
However, tomorrow is the
Great Culture and Sports Festival.
GREAT
CULTURE
AND SPORTS
FESTIVAL
I will grant you a special pardon!
SPECIAL PARDON
You will be allowed to participate!
If you wish to atone for your daughter's
crimes, participate in the ceremony
PARTICIPATE
IN THE CEREMONY
and wholeheartedly toast the honor and
glory of Lady Satsuki and Lady Ragyou!
WHOLEHEARTEDLY
TOAST
Is that clear?!
I'd like to ask you two things.
What?
Firstly: are the girls alive?
Yes.
And secondly:
will this ceremony be catered?
O-Of course.
Very well!
On the honor of the
Mankanshoku family,
in order to clean
our daughter's stigma,
we shall clean our plates of this food,
leaving not one crumb uneaten!
Mark my words!
GREAT
CULTURE
AND SPORTS
FESTIVAL
What the hell is this?
A video feed from hidden cameras
I had set up inside Honnouji Academy.
If even Kiryuuin Ragyou is involved,
this must be something big.
Kiryuuin Ragyou?
The leading figure of the
Kiryuuin Conglomerate.
She's currently using
her position as REVOCS CEO
to sell clothing laced with
Life Fibers all around the world.
Good grief, she's blinding!
She's gaudier than Satsuki!
Like daughter skank, like mother skank.
She's even more charismatic
than Satsuki. A formidable opponent.
What's this?
They're bringing in Life Fibers in bulk.
What are they up to?
Oh, no... She plans to conduct the
final experiment at Honnouji Academy!
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
Honnouji Academy is the grounds
for a large-scale experiment.
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
EXPERIMENT GROUNDS
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
Here, she created Ultima Uniforms, thereby
studying humanity's resistance to Life Fibers,
ULTIMA UNIFORMS
MILITARY APPLICATION
and then repurposed them for military use
to conquer all of the country's academies.
MILITARY APPLICATION
NATIONAL CONQUEST
She is forcibly distributing
...Life Fiber-laced uniforms to teenagers—
NATIONAL CONQUEST
those who have the highest resistance.
And once that is complete,
she plans to offer up every last person
gathered at Honnou Town
as human sacrifices to the Life Fibers.
Human sacrifices?!
Yes. It must be her final experiment
to fully awaken the Life Fibers.
She means to gather a mass of people
wearing Life Fiber-laced clothing
and instantly convert
them all to Life Fibers.
That is the true purpose of the
Great Culture and Sports Festival.
Wait, so you're saying that
Mako's dad and mom
are gonna be consumed
by their clothes?!
Put in simple terms,
I suppose they will.
...Consumed by their clothes...
Screw that! Not on my watch!
Ryuuko?
...Kiryuuin Ragyou and Kiryuuin Satsuki...
I'm gonna take them both out!
So you'll leap straight
into the jaws of danger?
Yeah! I'm gonna jump down danger's throat
and rip out its guts with my teeth!
Ryuuko!
Don't worry.
I won't lose control again.
I won't make you shed
any more bitter tears.
One way or another, I have to
settle this fight with Kiryuuin.
Are you with me, Senketsu?
Of course.
This will be interesting.
Oh, brother. I guess
you leave me no choice.
Let's hurry, then.
We don't have much time.
The Hyper Inner manufacturing facility
in Mozambique was attacked.
Militant extremists?
Yes, ma'am.
It would seem that even
anti-establishment organizations
are awash with rumors that wearing REVOCS
special innerwear boosts physical capabilities.
That's fine. It's just as we planned.
We don't just make people buy them.
There are some who are best tricked
into taking them for themselves.
Regardless of how it came
into their possession,
they will be worn by their
REVOCS clothing all the same.
What a beautiful world.
Now, now. We're only just getting started.
Tomorrow, we step onto a new stage.
The next step to the awakening of COVERS.
Lady Satsuki is most impressive.
She masterfully conquered the teen demographic,
which has the highest resistance to Life Fibers.
It was ingenious,
negating their resistance to Life Fibers
by getting them hooked on
the power of Ultima Uniforms.
But things are so dull
if they're too neat and tidy.
Grand Couturier.
Oh, right. It was Matoi's daughter
that you were more interested in.
Yes. To think that she gathered up the pieces of her
...Godrobe and stitched them together all by herself...
There aren't many girls
who can be quite that rude.
"Fair is foul, and foul is fair", eh?
How very like you, Nui.
Yep!
Still, that is but empty rhetoric.
There is only one truth.
Only that which earns Kiryuuin Ragyou's
approval may be called beautiful.
The Great Culture and
Sports Festival is tomorrow.
I expect you to dress up
for the occasion.
Enough to satisfy
even my sense of style.
Honestly, like mother, like daughter.
Tsumugu.
What's this?
A Tailor's Dagger and Tailor's Glove.
They're capable of cutting Life Fibers.
You're at a disadvantage in close combat
with just those sewing machine guns.
Sever the Ultima Uniform's Nexus Thread
and my opponent goes all-nude, huh?
Good. Very good.
Our targets are Ragyou and Satsuki.
Ignore everything else.
Well, it's not like there's anything else
we can do with just the three of us.
Keep Mako safe.
Sure.
I've asked our remaining
members to look after her here.
Don't ditch me here, Ryuuko!
...Mako...
C'mon, let's go home!
Honnouji Academy isn't
safe for you, you dummy!
But it's my home!
I've got souvenirs to
give to Dad and Mom!
Dammit, Mako!
If you're going, so am I!
Oh, right. I forgot your stubborn
streak's as wide as mine.
Tomorrow is the long-awaited
Great Culture and Sports Festival!
I want you all to see to it
with determination in your hearts!
Yes, sir!
I can't hear you!
Straighten out those lights a little!
Good. I want them to wreathe the stage.
Tomorrow will be
Honnouji Academy's climax!
Let's make it even more dramatic!
Okay, right there!
Good, good!
Work fast, people!
We're on the home stretch!
How are things coming along, Iori?
It's the day that Lady Satsuki
has been dreaming of.
We'll be ready, come hell or high water.
Understood. I'll be done here soon.
It looks like the naked apes
have taken the bait.
It was worth leaving those
hidden cameras they installed.
This will fill in the
final piece of the puzzle.
Summon everyone to the
Student Council chambers.
The preparations to welcome
my mother are now complete.
I appreciate all your hard work.
Ma'am!
And so, let us toast the success of the
Great Culture and Sports Festival!
Attention, all students and
families of Honnouji Academy!
We have succeeded in conquering
all the nation's academies!
All the fools who dared oppose our
Ultima Uniforms have been eliminated!
Today is a celebration
of those accomplishments!
Eat and drink your fill!
Praise the Kiryuuin name!
The Honnouji Academy Great Culture
and Sports Festival begins now!
It's begun, dear!
Who cares?! Just eat!
Yeah! We'll stuff ourselves
and then skip out afterwards!
Hold on, Matarou.
Now that I look closely, you're naked!
I sold off that stupid
dress uniform ages ago!
Damn, I wish I'd thought of that!
And now, the guest
you've all been waiting for.
Let us welcome her
with the utmost respect.
I present to you this academy's founder,
Director Kiryuuin Ragyou!
As grand an entrance as one
would expect from our director.
A ruler must shine
like the sun at all times.
It has been far too long, Ms. Kiryuuin.
Ah, Nonon. How is your father?
Fine, thank you.
Do you still engage in hacking
and stock manipulation?
Oh, I've put all that behind me.
Is that so? A pity.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I put a question to you.
What is the world?
The world is clothing.
Life Fibers are the rulers of this world.
I, Kiryuuin Ragyou,
know and carry out their will!
Honnouji Academy was
created for just that purpose.
The weak will serve as the
foundation for what is to come.
You should consider that an honor.
What the heck is the
Director talking about?
She means that the day has come for the pigs in
human clothing to be consumed by their garments.
Now, let the celebration begin!
Dad! Mom! Guts, too?!
What's that screaming?!
Sounds like it's started. Let's hurry.
I'll use the DTR to jump us
to the stage in one go.
Come on, Tsumugu! Ryuuko!
You mean Doutonbori Robo?
DTR!
It's Doutonbori Robo, right?
He hates that name.
Is this the time to be splitting hairs?
What about me?!
I slipped off!
There's nowhere to grab on to!
Go and hide! I'll give you snacks!
DTR, take off!
Have fun storming the stadium!
Such glorious silence.
The cacophony spewed forth by the foolish
creatures known as humanity will fade away,
and nothing but tranquil
fibers will fill the world.
The experiment is a
success, Lady Ragyou!
I'm putting an end to this,
Kiryuuin Satsuki!
Turn everyone back to normal!
Oh, so you are Matoi Ryuuko?
You're—
I see. And that is Godrobe Senketsu?
The fruit of Matoi Isshin's
last, futile efforts.
I must say, I didn't expect
it to be so beautiful.
So you're Kiryuuin Ragyou, huh?
I swear, you Kiryuuins sure
love to talk down to people!
I do. I am the one who knows
everything in this world.
I am the leader of the Kiryuuin
Conglomerate, Kiryuuin Ragyou,
What is the meaning of this, Satsuki?
The time for speeches is over, Director.
As of this moment, I, Kiryuuin Satsuki,
along with Honnouji Academy,
declare rebellion!
What... the hell?
Oh, so that's her game.
You're trying to take
the throne from me?
No, I'm not!
People do not live
for the sake of clothing!
I, Kiryuuin Satsuki, am rising up
to overthrow Life Fibers!
Honnouji Academy is the fortress
I created in order to defeat you!
Remember that, Kiryuuin Ragyou!
kurikaesu mainichi ga
My monotonous everyday life
totsuzen iro wo kaeru
Took on a new hue
sonna koto dokka nozonde itanda kedo ne
A part of me always wished for that to happen
iza to naru to
But when it actually did
okubyoumono deshita
I was too scared to act
himitsu ne
That's a secret, okay?
hitori furuete
Trembling alone
soshite kimi ni aitakute
I miss you so much
zutto mikata da yo nante ieta nara
If only I could tell you that I'll always be on your side
muteki
We could be invincible
sou sa tobidatsu toki wa futari de
When we take flight, we'll do so together
tachimukai
We'll make a stand
kakaekirenai okubyou ni
I don't want to go back
zutto hitatte waratte ita
To being the bumbling coward I was
hitori kiri zutsu ga awasatte
Every little thing will come together
ookina chikara ni naru yo
To give us great strength
ima nee kanjita
That's how I feel right now
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Pandemonium breaks loose on the stage.
Whose are the fingers that
tug on the thread of destiny?
THREAD
When the spinning wheel of destiny
spins, weaving the fabric of karma,
THREAD
SPIN
KARMA
FABRIC
who will it be that smiles from the shadows?
WHO WILL IT BE THAT SMILES FROM THE SHADOWS?
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"Into the Night".
EPISODE 18
INTO THE NIGHT