HONNOUJI ACADEMY
NATURALS ELECTION
KING OF THE HILL FINAL BATTLE
AND NOW...
CONQUEST OF THE BIG THREE
BATTLEFIELD TRIP
BATTLEFIELD
TRIP STRATEGY
MEETING
Sports club squads one through eleven,
preparations complete.
Assigning to Osaka Battlefield Trip Brigade.
Culture club squads one through eighteen,
preparations complete.
Assigning to Kyoto Battlefield Trip Brigade.
The Disciplinary Bureau is more than sufficient
for the Kobe Battlefield Trip Brigade!
Using a small, elite taskforce
is all well and good, but don't fail.
Yeah, nobody wants to
see you commit seppuku, Ira.
It'd be a real mess cleaning
all your guts off the floor.
Worry not. We shall succeed.
I have formed an Intelligence and Tactics Team
with the Computer Club at its core,
using Two-Star students from
the Information Systems class.
The information networks in each city
are already under our control,
and we are monitoring all communications
throughout their high schools.
Iori, are the Special Ultima Uniforms ready?
Yes, milady. Development and
manufacture of the Anti-Osaka,
Anti-Kyoto, and Anti-Kobe Combat-spec
Ultima Uniforms are complete.
They are being distributed to the
Battlefield Trip Brigades as we speak.
We are also producing new Three-Star
Ultima Uniforms for you Four Devas right now.
However, as the final adjustments are expected to take some time,
you will have to set out with the same
Special Ultima Uniforms as the other students.
Your uniforms have been improved based on
your battles with Matoi Ryuuko and Harime Nui.
They will not disappoint.
There is no shame in your defeat against
Godrobe Senketsu and Grand Couturier Harime Nui.
Through trials,
you will mature even further.
It is merely a rite of passage.
And now, I look forward to
your maturation as commanders.
Lead the Battlefield Trip Brigades to victory!
Understood!
Very well. The Battlefield Trip is set to leave
at 0200 hours the day after tomorrow.
Understood!
Is the helicopter ready?
It is, milady.
Thank you.
EPISODE THIRTEEN
FEELING LIKE SCATTERED ROSES...
WHEN YOU ARE NEAR
dareka ga katteni kimeta readymade na
This is a readymade world that is at someone's beck and call
kyou wo nugisutete
I'll break free of its shackles
RYUUKO
MATOI
hadashi de hashitte iku
And sprint toward my goal
GAMAGOORI IRA
machigattatte
Even if I lose my way
GAMAGOORI IRA
SANAGEYAMA UZU
JAKUZURE NONON
INUMUTA HOUKA
korondatte
Or trip and fall
INUMUTA HOUKA
MANKANSHOKU FAMILY
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
surimuita itami mo
Those wounds will still create
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
KINAGASE
TSUMUGU
original na ashita ni naru
An original future for me
KIRYUUIN
SATSUKI
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
I hold my destiny in my own hands
chikai ga hikari ni natte
And it shines ever so brightly
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
So until the day I reach you
naiteru hima nante nai kara
I don't have the time to sit around crying
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
My burning passion pours out from within me
yozora de kagayaki dasu
And shines like a star in the night sky
umarete kita imi ga
I think I now understand
wakatta ki ga shita
Why I was born
negaigoto wa zenbu kono te de
I'll make all of my dreams come true
kanaeru
With my own hands
Boy, I wish I could go!
I don't want to go! But I wish I could!
I do wish I could go! But I don't want to!
But I really wish I could go anyway!
A woman's heart is a fickle thing.
I know, right?
It's not like being asked if you want to go
somewhere makes you want to go,
but I sure would've loved to go to Kyoto!
So you short-bus students are getting
left out of the School Battlefield Trip, huh?
Yeah, 'cause it's war out there, apparently.
I hate fighting, but it's a free trip!
If you could go somewhere for free,
you'd want to go, right?
Kyoto! Kobe! Osaka!
You got them all wrong.
Kyoto is here. Kobe is here.
Osaka is here.
Wow! They're all really close together!
Pretty much. It's the Kansai region, after all.
It boggles my mind that you
managed to make it to high school.
It's my mind that's boggled!
By the way, is Ryuuko still in a bad way?
Ryuuko's developed a sudden
aversion to wearing her uniform.
After she snapped out of her rampage,
she went straight to the school,
but after she came back,
she was all mopey for some reason.
She doesn't even try to
put on poor Senketsu.
Ah, I see.
You there.
You're Mankanshoku Mako, aren't you?
Yes.
Please! Take me to see Matoi Ryuuko!
You can trust me!
I'm Nagita Shinjirou,
formerly of the Newspaper Club!
FORMERLY
OF THE
NEWSPAPER
CLUB
NAGITA
SHINJIROU
Found him!
There he is!
Hold it right there, newshound!
Crap!
H-Hey, what are you doing?!
They're with the Disciplinary Bureau!
I cant let them find me!
I've been barred from school grounds!
Come back here!
But I don't even read the newspaper!
Stop right there!
You're not getting away!
Barred from school grounds, huh?
I made you something, Ryuuko!
What's that?
My special croquettes, made with
finely-chopped, super-mysterious ingredients!
They'll get you back on your feet!
Matarou and the others had some earlier.
See?
It's so wonderful to be alive!
Dance, Matarou!
I'm twirling, Dad!
Round and round and round!
Spin, spin! Churn and turn into butter!
I really turned into butter!
I feel like I've melted into goo!
I think those might be a bit dangerous.
Anyway, eat up, get your body
moving, and sweat it out!
If you do that, all the bad things bottled up in your heart will flow right out of you!
Thanks, ma'am.
I couldn't hold in my rage.
All I wanted was to kill Harime Nui,
even if I had to destroy everything to do it.
...Senketsu...
Is it safe for me to wear you?
Please do!
What the hell?
Please put it on!
Wh-Who are you?
...Mom, I brought a friend—
Oh, he's already inside!
Welcome!
HONNOUJI NEWSPAPER
And what have we here?
It says "We Are Not
blankety-blank's blanks!"
Wow, there's all sorts of incomprehensible stuff written in here, Ryuuko!
Read the kanji, too!
Kiryuuin Satsuki and the
Kiryuuin Conglomerate
are trying to turn the
academy's students into soldiers.
I couldn't let that happen.
But the school paper ran afoul
of the Disciplinary Bureau censor,
and I was unable to
distribute it to the students!
It drove home just how powerless I truly am!
Nagita says he's gotten on
the Student Council's bad side
and has been barred from
the school grounds ever since!
There is no freedom of speech in this school.
There isn't a single person
who stands up to Kiryuuin.
Or so I thought. But you're different!
You defeated the Four Devas all by yourself
and struck fear into even Kiryuuin Satsuki!
You're Honnouji Academy's revolutionary!
I can fight, too!
Just as long as you lead the way!
You'll have to fight by yourself.
I'm not fighting because I want to.
Get outta here! Beat it!
What are you fighting for, then?!
How the hell should I know?
You've reached one person, at least!
One man who saw what you'd done and took back his life!
Your fight hasn't been for nothing!
So put on that sailor uniform,
and fight one more time!
I don't fight for the sake of others!
Go on, beat it! Just give up and get out!
I won't give up, Matoi!
...You are my—
...no, all of Honnouji Academy's—
virtuous star of hope!
Quit it!
...I won't let the courage you gave me...
go to waste! Farewell!
What the hell was that guy's problem?!
Ryuuko.
Zip it. Not a word out of you.
CO.
LTD.
AUDITORIUM
I put this question to you, gentlemen.
What is clothing?!
Clothing is sin! Man's original sin!
Indeed. Clothing is sin.
When Man ate the forbidden fruit
of the Tree of Knowledge,
he became ashamed of his nakedness
and covered his nethers with fig leaves.
From the moment Man first gained free will as a human being,
REVOCS CEO KIRYUUIN RAGYO
it has been his fate to cover
his body in the clothing called "sin".
Clothing made by REVOCS is sold in
ninety percent of the world's countries
and controls an overwhelming
share of the market.
Why is that?
Because we alone know man's sin
and create clothing for clothing's sake!
I put the question to you again!
What is clothing?
Clothing is the world!
The grand will that binds the heavens, the earth, and mankind, covering all.
Indeed.
That is exactly the intent of COVERS.
How does Junketsu feel on you?
A rather powerful article
of clothing, is it not?
You wear it well.
Thank you, Mother.
Hououmaru.
Yes, ma'am.
Is this what brings you here today?
Godrobe Senketsu, eh?
La vie est drôle.
I have already filed a report
regarding that incident.
You said that it would be
left to my discretion.
Of course.
Matters should be settled youth
against youth, Godrobe against Godrobe.
That's the way it should be.
Why, then, was the Grand Couturier sent to Honnouji Academy?
The Grand Couturier?
Oh, you mean Nui? I had no choice.
Not even a CEO can rein
in the whims of an artiste.
I see.
However, if anyone should
interfere with my plan,
I will deal with them under my own discretion.
Do as you wish.
As long as you continue to
act in the interest of COVERS,
Revocs Market Shares
the world will remain your ally.
I shall set out on the Big Three
Battlefield Trip the day after tomorrow.
BIG THREE
BATTLE
FIELD TRIP
I've read your report.
How many days will it take?
One day will be sufficient.
Magnificent.
With this, Honnouji Academy's rule over
all the schools in the country will be complete.
COMPLETE
RULE OF
ACADEMIES
COUNTRY
WIDE
REVOCS uniforms will be
supplied to every school in Japan.
REVOCS UNIFORMS IN
EVERY JAPANESE
ACADEMY
And the naked apes lurking behind the students will be dragged out into the open.
NAKED APES
You understand perfectly.
You have a reason to save
the Kansai region for last.
Or so I believe,
given that you are my daughter.
Leave everything to me.
I shall show you a battle
worthy of the Kiryuuin name.
La vie est drôle. "Life is droll", eh?
It is. And it's about to get even more so.
Well, I'm off to do things my own way.
I suggest you be careful.
Anger my daughter at your peril.
Fine by me!
That way, we can see her go all out.
And that's something you
want too, isn't it, Lady Ragyou?
Yes, that's right.
These are the forces that
Honnouji Academy is mustering.
I've sent the data to HQ as well.
So they're finally launching
an all-out assault, huh?
But thanks to your investigation, we have a tool we can use.
It bums me out that we might have to
take on that monstrous girl, though.
It's rare to hear you complain, Tsumugu.
But we have no choice but to do this.
Even if it means becoming naked Nudists.
I'll join you as soon as I deal
with a little problem of my own.
He really has been
suspended indefinitely, huh?
...It's just like he said, but still...
Good morning, Mankanshoku!
Oh, Nagita! Is it okay
for you to be at school?
Matoi stayed home again, did she?
Yeah, she and the sailor uniform
were staring each other down again today.
I see. We have no choice, then.
We'll have to do it ourselves.
What's this?
I'm done with running away.
Please tell Matoi that.
All students in attendance at
Honnouji Academy, lend me your ears!
Can you not see that there is something wrong with how this academy is run?
Obeying Kiryuuin Satsuki's every word
and then putting on Ultima Uniforms to fight?
Don't you think that's wrong?!
Go on, Mankanshoku!
Hand out those newspapers!
Hurry!
Schoolmates! Let us take back
this academy together!
Thank you! Thank you! Read our paper! Thank you! Read all about it!
For the details, read this newspaper!
...You two! Unauthorized soapboxing is against—
Oh no! It's the Disciplinary Bureau!
Oh, no! Run, Mankanshoku!
Nagita! Don't be a hero! Run! Run!
Never! I refuse to live in fear any longer!
I will resist to my last breath!
He ran!
After him!
You're not getting away!
Nagita!
Mankanshoku!
What do you think you're doing?
Gamagoori!
Under normal circumstances, your actions would
merit a one-month stay in the Time Out Chamber,
but these are not normal circumstances!
I am commuting your sentence to hard labor in the School Raid Commissariat Unit!
Now, load that cargo onto the trucks!
Are you afraid of me, Ryuuko?
No. I'm afraid of myself.
Back then, you were crying.
You were pulled into my mind as I rampaged out of control,
got pumped full of rage-filled blood,
had more power than
you wanted pulled out of you,
and then you broke down and cried.
Even then, I could tell
how bitter your tears were.
But in spite of that, I couldn't stop myself.
If Mako hadn't shown up,
I don't know what would have happened.
Did you forget what you said to me?
You said it wasn't about avenging your dad,
but getting to know him better!
Even so, do not reject me.
I want to be worn by you.
I was likely born for the express purpose of being worn by you.
Have you remembered something?
No. I just get that feeling.
And every time I drink your blood, that feeling grows stronger.
Save me, Matoi!
We have you now!
Take him away!
I'm sorry! I never intended to get you mixed up in all this!
Our straw mats!
Our dressers!
S-Stop it!
Our sliding screen!
Pops!
Mr. Mankanshoku!
Matoi!
Prepare for surgery!
You know how to operate, Mom?!
Everyone has to start somewhere!
Got it, Mom! I'll help!
Senketsu, if I go too far,
I'll need you to stop me.
I cannot promise that.
It is you who wears me.
Sheesh, you're not very flexible
for a piece of clothing, you know?
However, you were able to
bring yourself back under control.
With your own willpower.
That is why I am not
frightened in the least.
Gotcha. We're all responsible
for our own actions.
What are you doing?! Stop it!
Do what you will with me!
I will... never yield!
I won't be beaten!
Hold it!
What do you think you're doing to that guy?
Matoi!
Don't look at me like that.
You know I couldn't
stand by and do nothing.
No time to chat, huh?
Have it your way. Let's do it, Senketsu!
Sword Scissor: Decapitation Mode!
SWORD
SCISSOR:
DECAPITATION
MODE
"STRIPPED"
Thread Stripper!
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
Hey, these guys aren't human!
So you've finally gotten dressed, Ryuuko.
Nagita... You set all this up?
Indeed! Those men were all my puppets!
And I guess you are too.
Come again?
Fear from when you lost control.
Rejection of your Godrobe.
But you conquered your fear in order to save the helpless.
You're so predictable
that it's downright adorable!
No! You can't be!
Ta-dah!
Harime Nui! It was you all along?
The data is disappearing?
...Then that boy really was—
Oh, no! Ryuuko!
What's got you all frowny?
HARIME NUI
Wasn't that a good rehabilitation for you?
Why devise this elaborate plot
just to get me to put on Senketsu?
Well, Lady Satsuki barred me
from the school grounds.
HARIME NUI
I have my own problems,
I'll have you know.
HARIME NUI
Will you show me just how much power you can wring out of it this time?
...You little—
HARIME NUI
Come on, what's that?
It's nothing like last time!
Bite me!
You really are afraid of yourself!
I am not!
After all the trouble I've gone to,
you're still holding back.
You're weaker than I thought.
I'm bored!
It's all over.
Sen... ketsu...
You don't have what it takes
to wear a Godrobe.
Go and join your father.
Oopsie, you figured it out already?
Why are you here?
Are you mad?
There is only one way to deal with those who do not obey my orders.
Oh gosh, she really means it!
Would you like to undergo the blood purge?
Fine, fine, I'll leave.
I'm bored with her, anyway.
How disgraceful.
Is this... Matoi Ryuuko's Godrobe?
Its remains.
What shall I do with it?
Find suitable hosts,
and divide the scraps among them.
Then use them to gather combat data
during the Battlefield Trip.
Understood.
Three years of study here
at Honnouji Academy!
This battle is the first step
towards realizing our ambitions!
I have but one command
to impose upon you: win.
Honnouji Academy Big Three
Battlefield Trip, roll out!
I-I'm going, too?!
We're going, Soroi.
Yes, milady.
Ryuuko!
...Is that...
chime ga naru mae ni
Before the bell rings
kugurinuketa
I sneak out of school
otonatachi no haiiro no me
Avoiding the adults' vacant stares
tawai no nai kaiwa
The pointless conversations
togirenu mama
Keep going on and on
sakamichi wo kudatteku
As I walk down the slope
nani wo suru demo naku
I have nothing to do
yuku ate sae mo naku
And nowhere to go
tada atashi ima wa ne
Right now, all I do
donna chuukoku mo mimi wo surinukeru
Is ignore any and all warnings
mada mada suki ni sasete
Because I still want to be free
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
To be an exemplary student
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
rojiura no nukemichi
And take the back alley
amai yuuwaku wa michi
A path of mysterious sweet temptation
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Field trips are the source
of many youthful memories,
YOUTHFUL MEMORIES
but they're a little different
at Honnouji Academy!
BUT
A LITTLE
DIFFERENT
Theirs is a battlefield trip to conquer the
Big Three cities of Kobe, Kyoto, and Osaka!
BIG THREE
BATTLEFIELD TRIP
The album of their youth
is drawn in a deep, blood red!
ALBUM OF
THEIR YOUTH
BLOOD RED
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"Ride Like the Wind"!
EPISODE 14
RIDE LIKE THE WIND