How is it?
The pleasure of being
enveloped by Junketsu?
...I... This is just...
You and I are the only ones in this
entire world who can feel that pleasure.
Enjoy it to the fullest.
She's right.
Not even I know how it feels.
I'm so envious of you.
The Life Fibers within
Nui's body resist all others.
Even if she wears a Godrobe,
she can't use its powers.
Yeah.
Which is why I chose to
become the Grand Couturier.
I'll just create the ultimate Godrobe myself.
You should be able to
understand how I feel now.
People exist for the sake of clothing.
Indeed.
The beings that stand at the
very apex of life on this planet.
That is what Life Fibers are.
Hey, Ryuuko.
Hurry up and show us.
We want to see you looking your very best.
Life Fiber Override:
Godrobe Junketsu.
Amazing!
Lady Ragyou.
Miss Satsuki managed to escape.
Satsuki did?
I leave her to you.
Gotcha.
Do you still want to avenge your father?
Something to feel good about.
Looks like she can't
suppress her own emotions.
She's even better than you,
despite her lack of experience.
Lady Ryuuko has awakened completely.
Life Fibers are most active
when their host's life is in danger.
Regardless of how deeply
Souchirou sealed them away,
subjecting the host to an
intense near-death experience
makes it trivially easy to awaken them.
Hououmaru.
Have all employees gather
at REVOCS headquarters.
I'll head back to the mansion.
The climax is finally upon us.
I'm getting goosebumps!
Time to get a move on with my work.
EPISODE 21
INCOMPLETE
unmei no ito wo tachikitta sono saki ni
It all begins when we sever the threads of fate
I was trying to be someone I'm not
senobi shiteitanda
kutsuzure darake no
In a cramped world
With no breathing room
semai sekai de
As I walked down my runway
runway wo aruku
I thought I'd concealed it
egao no uragawa
kakushita tsumori de
Behind the smile that masked my face
But it doesn't work on you
dakedo itsumo kimi ni wa
minukarete shimatte ite
You always see through my facade
Nobody's ever unraveled me like this before
konna no wa hajimete de
tomadou kedo
I don't know what to do
hoka no dare ni mo kikonasenai
Nobody else can pull these outfits off
nandaka wakannai
A somewhat ambiguous fever
atsusa ga mune wo kogasu kara
Threatens to burn our hearts away
It all begins once we rein in the threads of fate
unmei no ito taguriyoseta sono saki ni
A new day will dawn for us
ima atarashii yoake ga kuru
omoi wa kitto hitotsu
We must be one in spirit
Matoi Ryuuko.
I never expected you to be my sister.
Don't go all "older sis" on me now.
Makes me sick.
Oh, you don't have to worry about that.
I will crush all lapdogs to the Life Fibers
without mercy, no matter who they are.
Here we go, Senketsu.
Okay!
Life Fiber Synchronize:
Godrobe Senketsu!
SENKETSU
GODROBE
She synchronized with Senketsu
despite having only just put him on?
That's Lady Satsuki for you.
I can't just sit back
and watch this any longer.
We should go too!
Let's back Lady Satsuki up!
Wait!
Now is not the time, underachiever!
I have a message from
Lady Satsuki to the Four Devas!
Let's do this,
Satsuki!
Is that Bakuzan?
You're still holding on to
something Mother broke in half?
Crying over spilled milk, are we?
What I'm showing isn't tears. It's tenacity!
It doesn't matter if it's
smashed to bits and pieces.
So long as a single fragment of it remains,
it will come back to life without a doubt.
My Four Devas took good care of it for me.
Both I, Kiryuuin Satsuki, and Honnouji Academy
share that tenacity and desire to win.
That is what these two blades symbolize!
Shut up already!
Run your mouth all you want,
but if you couldn't even manage
to wear Junketsu completely,
you've got no chance of making
full use of that fake either.
You think I'm all bark and no bite?
...Then let me show you...
Senketsu Blade Flash!
Senketsu Gale!
Quit ripping me off, bitch!
Oh, we're only getting started.
Blade Gale!
Interesting.
Okay.
That should do it for today.
Guess you're not completely inept.
Ryuuko.
Take that outfit off
and wear me instead!
You've gotta be kidding me.
I never want to look that ugly again.
I'm ugly?
Do you really mean that?
Yeah.
That half-assed getup where you
can't even tell if they're clothed or not?
It's the very definition of ugly.
By making the least possible
amount of skin contact,
one can draw out the Life Fibers' powers
without falling under their influence.
GODROBE
SENKETSU
That is the purpose of the
Life Fiber Synchronize form.
If anything, it's proof of human ingenuity.
"Ingenuity", my ass.
It's just fear.
You want the power of clothing,
but you're afraid of
losing control of your mind.
That outfit symbolizes your
unwillingness to go all the way.
It's completely and utterly shameful.
That's not true.
Whenever you activated
Life Fiber Synchronize mode,
you were wearing me,
and I was being worn by you.
Right now, you're just
being worn by Junketsu.
And what's wrong with that?
The pleasure of being worn
by Junketsu is out of this world!
People are born to be worn by Life Fibers.
Adorning them should be
their greatest happiness in life.
That is a slave's happiness!
If you don't like it,
then you'd better die.
"Submit or die".
Sounds like your kind of phrase, eh,
Kiryuuin Satsuki?!
Senketsu Blade Flash!
Falter not!
I see, I see.
You aren't truly wearing
that Godrobe, are you?
Senketsu Gale!
Too slow.
Blade Gale!
Still too slow!
Lady Satsuki!
What is wrong with you?!
What's the matter?
Can't attack me?
You can't, can you?
I can see through your
every move, after all!
Take that!
"Life Fiber Synchronize", my ass.
You and Senketsu aren't
on the same page at all.
All you're doing is ordering
Senketsu to attack using his powers.
That's why your teamwork's all wonky.
You're the one who's just
being worn by her Godrobe.
You haven't improved
since wearing Junketsu at all!
I've had it up to here with your posturing.
What's wrong?
Hard to look down on people
from the dirt, ain't it?
If you can't stand by yourself,
maybe I should lend a hand.
Does this calm you down, "Lady Satsuki"?
But you know what?
You've got nothing at your feet.
You're a pathetic princess who
stands atop a mere sandcastle.
One wave is all it takes to
wash your kingdom away.
Stop it, Ryuuko.
Yes, my words don't reach Satsuki.
And yes, this Life Fiber Synchronize
is but a stopgap measure.
However, our hearts are as one.
We stand together in our desire
to bring you back to your senses.
Shut the hell up.
Do you have any idea how much stress
Satsuki's placing on her body to let me fight?
No other human could pull that off.
Only Kiryuuin Satsuki can!
So what?
She's still a loser!
You sure are annoying
for a scrap of clothing.
I'll chop you to pieces along with Satsuki!
Don't you dare insult Satsuki!
Her sandcastle is made of steel!
It won't fall apart that easily!
Stay out of this!
Don't you realize what
Lady Satsuki wants?
You must have holes for eyes!
You're just a human. Spare me.
What can you do with those paltry knives?
"What", you ask?
Well, he can lure you into firing range.
Did you really think
that'd work on Junketsu?
No, but it did give me
the chance to close in on you.
What?
I'm going to pull you out from Junketsu!
Damn it, Satsuki!
Was this your plan all along?
Precisely!
Senketsu and I can't
beat you as you are now.
But entrusting the Four Devas with
the finishing blow gave us a chance!
All right! Just as planned!
Still, I can't believe Lady Satsuki suggested
a combination attack with the Four Devas.
And most of all, I can't believe Mankanshoku
accurately relayed that complicated message.
Lady Satsuki wrote it down
on my hands for me!
Trust her to be thoroughly prepared.
Who would've thought
you'd play the decoy yourself?
I'll do whatever it takes to win.
Did you forget that's how I do things?
Now, I'll tear you away from Junketsu
and bring you back to your senses!
Why can't I separate Matoi?!
Run, Gamagoori!
Harime Nui!
Damn you!
Useless, useless, useless.
Really, humans waste
so much time on pointless things.
Those shots will never hit me.
And Ryuuko can never take Junketsu off!
Why is that?
I mean, I sewed the Life Fibers
within her body and Junketsu's together.
If you try to forcefully take it off,
they'll get ripped apart, and she'll die.
What?!
How dare you!
She sewed the Godrobe onto her body?!
That's awful!
What kind of punishment is that?
I'm Mankanshoku Mako,
leaping into action!
We successfully completed the acquisition of
every sewing factory in China and India the other day.
As a result, REVOCS now holds a
100% share of the world's market.
Humans all across the globe are wearing
our clothing in one way or another.
Congratulations!
Life Fibers have spread
through all of mankind.
Now there's just one last task
for you all to complete.
The original Life Fiber,
which touched down on planet Earth,
stimulated mankind's evolution
by providing it with clothing
and then went into a dormant state
until humanity advanced sufficiently.
Our job as the Kiryuuin family
was to protect it until then.
Only one Kiryuuin head
would ever see it reawaken.
I thank Father Time for
choosing me as that person.
Now I can witness this
amazing event with my own eyes.
What's happening?
This world shall belong to the Life Fibers.
This is the genesis of the Cocoon Planet!
COCOON PLANET
GENESIS OF THE
Congratulations, milady.
Kuroido.
Do you and the others
wish to take part as well?
May we?
Indeed.
Thank you very much!
How wonderful!
This is most pleasant,
Lady Ragyou!
Let us go to where it all begins.
Eat this!
Senketsu!
This is the end!
Stop!
I can understand
why you're mad, Ryuuko.
Yeah, if you can't take those clothes off,
you can't wash yourself
even if you take a bath,
and you can't dress up
when you have to go on a date!
But that doesn't mean
you should go this crazy!
Objection
What the hell are you talking about?
Run away, Mankanshoku!
Matoi's not her usual self right now!
Ryuuko is always herself!
Even if she's got Life Fibers in her body,
or if she's mad that she's not human,
Ryuuko's still herself!
Objection
And Senketsu is her best outfit!
She's such a nuisance.
...Mako...
Mako!
...Whoa, could this be...?
I took some of your blood.
Please, just don't get anemic!
Girls who try to punch above their weight and wear
outfits that don't suit them are what I hate most.
They're so pathetic I could hurl.
I told you it was useless!
You still don't get it?
A mere human couldn't possibly beat me.
Be that as it may, the blade
within my heart still stands firm.
Sheesh, how persistent.
Ryuuko belongs to Lady Ragyou.
I wonder about that.
Are you going to appeal to her emotions too?
That's just useless.
How naïve you've gotten, Satsuki.
You're the reason I believe there's
still a chance to turn this around.
I am?
Indeed.
If Matoi Ryuuko is indeed
completely on your side,
then why don't you let her
have that Sword Scissor?
Those scissors are the last weapon
that can oppose the Life Fibers.
You're holding on to one half of it
because you're still a touch anxious.
That very anxiety is our path to victory!
The look on your face has convinced me.
We will prevail!
Leave her to us!
You take care of Matoi!
You're our only hope!
I'm counting on you!
Ryuuko!
Kill that girl along with Senketsu!
That's what Lady Ragyou wants.
Show these simpletons talking about
hope just how dark reality can be!
Gotcha.
Outta my way.
Knock it off, Ryuuko!
So you're going to protect that girl?
Yes, I will.
But I also want to protect you, Ryuuko!
Me?
That's right.
If you kill Mako right here and now,
that will hurt you most of all!
So I won't let you, no matter what!
Say what?
It's all because you're so selfish, Ryuuko!
Now Senketsu's been worn by me instead!
This just isn't right!
I'm sure you can take that outfit off.
So hurry up and change!
Shut up already, will ya?!
Now, Mankanshoku!
Stick Senketsu into this wound!
What?!
Senketsu!
Use your powers to untangle
Matoi's and Junketsu's Life Fibers!
All right!
Understood!
Here I come, Ryuuko!
I'm going to force you to change!
It's high time you learned how
powerful one's best outfit can be!
Ryuuko!
We've come for you!
I'll kill anyone who dares
destroy my happiness.
How can you call this happiness?
This isn't like you at all!
Shut up.
Come to your senses, Ryuuko!
Shut the hell up!
You stupid, foolish, fool!
Fine. Kill me!
If you insist on staying
cooped up in here forever,
kill me, and quit being Ryuuko!
Ryuuko!
...Matoi...
Oh dear.
Looks like your plan to
win her over ended in failure.
Come on, Ryuuko.
...Let's send this ship...
to Davy Jones' locker!
What?
Quit doing as you damn well please!
No way!
How dare you make me wear this outfit?!
Ryuuko!
Screw it. I've had enough!
I've had enough!
Underachiever!
Matoi!
I've had enough!
Stop it, Matoi!
You'll die if you try to
take it off by force!
Dying is fine by me!
I have to take this thing off,
even if it costs me my life!
...Or else...
I won't be able to wear Senketsu again!
My monotonous everyday life
kurikaesu mainichi ga
totsuzen iro wo kaeru
Took on a new hue
sonna koto dokka nozonde itanda kedo ne
A part of me always wished for that to happen
But when it actually did
iza to naru to
I was too scared to act
okubyoumono deshita
That's a secret, okay?
himitsu ne
Trembling alone
hitori furuete
I miss you so much
soshite kimi ni aitakute
zutto mikata da yo nante ieta nara
If only I could tell you that I'll always be on your side
muteki
We could be invincible
sou sa tobitatsu toki wa futari de
When we take flight, we'll do so together
tachimukai
We'll make a stand
I want to keep smiling
kakaekirenai okubyou ni
tsuppattatte waratte itai
Even when my cowardice freezes me in place
hitori kiri zutsu ga awasatte
Every little thing will come together
ookina chikara ni naru yo
To give us great strength
That's how I feel right now
ima nee kanjita