People do not live
for the sake of clothing!
I, Kiryuuin Satsuki, am rising up
to overthrow Life Fibers!
Honnouji Academy is the fortress
I created in order to defeat you!
Remember that, Kiryuuin Ragyou!
I pretended to obey you
as I waited for this day to come.
Fear is freedom!
Control is liberty!
Contradiction is truth!
That is the reality of this world!
Listen well, you pig that serves clothing,
and bow before that fact!
You fool.
Know your place!
Not on my watch!
Shackle Regalia Mk 2!
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SHACKLE
REGALIA MK 2
Inumuta.
Release the audience.
Yes, ma'am.
Huh?
What was that all about?
Thank goodness!
Dad, Mom, Guts!
What is this?
Jammers that keep
Life Fibers in check.
I based them off
Nudist Beach's weapons.
Impertinent high schoolers!
You'd best not look down on us.
Every student here is a soldier that has been
trained to fight you—no, to fight Life Fibers!
Behold the might of Honnouji Academy!
Uh huh.
Now it all makes sense.
Way to go, Satsuki!
...Your opponent here...
is me!
Blade Regalia Mk 3!
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
BLADE
REGALIA MK 3
And who might you be?
One of Honnouji Academy's Four Devas:
Sanageyama Uzu!
I'm going to pay you back
for what you did to me last time!
EPISODE 18
INTO THE NIGHT
Satsuki's going to
take down her own mother?
That means we share a common goal.
What the hell's going on?
Don't ask me.
This is beyond my wildest predictions.
Matoi.
Lady Satsuki planned to fight the
Life Fibers from the very beginning.
But in order to trick Director Ragyou,
she couldn't let even a shred
of her true intentions show.
Then why the heck did she
fight Nudist Beach and me?
I have no need for half-baked allies.
If you can't beat my army,
then you don't stand a snowball's
chance in Hell against the Life Fibers.
Say what?
If you don't like my methods, then I'll
gladly take you on after I'm done here.
However, if you have the resolve
to protect the freedom of man,
then fight with everything
you've got for now.
I applaud your resolve.
Are you saying you don't mind stabbing
your own mother in the back to see it through?
That goes without saying!
I'll do whatever it takes
to defeat a monster like you.
Call me a coward or a crook
all you want. I'd love that.
Did you just call your
own mother a monster?
I don't think someone who can shrug off a
stab through the heart has any right to disagree.
You became a monster the moment you threw away
your humanity and fused yourself with Life Fibers.
I am no monster, young lady.
I am a life-form that is
one step away from divinity.
What the heck?
What a resilient lady.
I think you mean "freak".
This is the truth behind Life Fibers.
If this battle caught your eye, burn any
REVOCS-made clothing in your possession!
With your help, we can liberate mankind!
Pay me back? I don't remember
lending you anything.
Did you already forget the sneak attack
you pulled on me during the Naturals Election?
Sorry about that.
When a lady changes her underwear,
she leaves the past behind her!
Do you really think you can beat me
just by getting a little facelift?
Yes, I do!
Hm?
See that?
My eyes may have lost their light,
but my sword's surpassed
the speed of light!
There you go,
running your big mouth again.
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
PROBE
REGALIA MK 2
It's impossible for humans
to move faster than light.
However, it is possible to make
someone believe that you are.
By leaving behind a clear afterimage while hiding
the actual body behind optical camouflage, that is.
Optical camouflage is so computer geek.
It's totally creepy, I hope you know.
Let's have you stay put, shall we?
Oh? So it's three-on-one?
Nah.
We're called the Four Devas
because there are four of us!
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
That's news to me!
My apologies.
I'll have you know
that we're a tough lot.
We could never be defeated
by the likes of you!
How annoying.
...That tough-guy act...
really gets on my nerves.
Dad, Mom!
I'm home!
Oh, Mako.
Welcome back.
So you were alive, my daughter?
Yep!
I can't rest easy until I finish handing out
all these souvenirs from Osaka.
That's my sis.
You know where it's at.
Time to dig in!
What's the matter with you,
Mankanshoku?
What do you mean, "matter"?
If you mean "the Matarou
with you", I'm over here!
I couldn't care less!
Mankanshoku,
help the audience escape!
What?
Me?
This place isn't safe right now.
We don't want to cause
any unnecessary casualties.
Now get to work!
Right away, sir!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Run away!
Back-Alley Doctor
Mankanshoku
All You Can Eat
Kansai Specialties
Check it out! We have
octopus dumplings from Kansai!
And pork kebabs, too!
It's all-you-can-eat!
Come one, come all!
When did you change your mind?
I did nothing of the sort.
Ever since I grew old enough to make my own
decisions, I've lived in anticipation of this day.
What did you say?
I was five when I learned the truth.
Father told me everything.
About Life Fibers, COVERS,
and you: Kiryuuin Ragyou!
He told me about your wicked goals.
Everything.
He said to me,
This will be your wedding dress.
"Satsuki, this will be your wedding dress."
"But the moment you put it on,
you will be enslaved by clothing."
FATHER
KIRYUUIN
SOUICHIROU
He was an ingenious scientist.
His talents recognized,
he married into the Kiryuuin family.
And then he fathered a child: me.
But I was only brought into this world to
be a test subject in Life Fiber experiments.
This isn't working.
We shouldn't have left it
until she was a year old.
I suppose it will have to be this one.
The next year,
they tried fusing their newborn
second child with Life Fibers.
Not even a body which carries my genes
can overcome its resistance to Life Fibers, huh?
Oh well.
That's when my father
...made up his mind...
to rebel against the
Life Fibers and Kiryuuin Ragyou.
At the end of the day,
he was just a plebeian.
The likes of Souichirou could never
comprehend the truth of the universe!
My father was well aware
that you'd go after him.
That is why he left everything to me.
I can't believe he left a
five-year-old girl to do his dirty work.
It was no ordinary five-year-old.
Don't you dare forget that
it was me, Kiryuuin Satsuki!
KIRYUUIN SATSUKI
I'll admit, you sure know how to talk big.
However, killing me
won't destroy the Life Fibers.
Are you talking about
the original Life Fiber?
If so, then I've already made my move.
You are members of
Honnouji Academy's Sewing Club, yes?
I've been expecting you.
Those are the COVERS, huh?
All hands, fire the
instantaneous coagulants!
I've put a stop to the
original Life Fiber's activities.
How did insects like them
make it all the way underground?
I took out Kuroido and
everyone else who served you.
It was when I stayed the night there.
Ragyou!
In order to free humanity
from its shackles,
I will take your life
right here and now!
Lady Ragyou!
Out of my way!
...Satsuki. All of your soldiers...
belong to me now.
That bitch!
She turned the students
into her puppets!
They've been mentally refitted.
MENTAL REFITTING
I sewed my Marionette Thread
throughout their brains.
Go forth, men.
Lady Satsuki!
It matters not!
Consider anyone that comes
after us to be an enemy!
Until we defeat Ragyou,
we must have minds of steel!
Life Fiber Override:
Godrobe Junketsu!
GODROBE
JUNKETSU
...Wha—
Hold it, Kiryuuin!
Ryuuko.
Leave this to us
and go after Ragyou!
Uh, okay.
Who would've thought Kiryuuin Satsuki
was planning a rebellion?!
But if that's the case,
I don't care who takes Ragyou out!
Sheesh.
What did we even come here for?
Kiryuuin Ragyou!
There's no escape for you!
Very impressive, my girl.
Even if I do say so myself.
But you've made some huge mistakes.
Matoi!
Ryuuko, I can't unravel this thread!
Your first one was
bringing this Matoi girl here.
Maybe you thought
she'd be of use to you,
but she's my pawn now.
Too bad for you.
She's this powerful without
activating Life Fiber Synchronize mode?
Marvelous.
Looks like this is what
she's truly capable of.
You damn fool!
Got you!
Mind's Eye: Critical Thrust!
What?!
Mon Mignon Prêt-à-Porter!
You guys are too serious. Such a bore!
My adorable clones will play with you,
so take this opportunity to learn
how to have a little fun, 'kay?
Get a hold of yourself, Matoi!
I took great care to bind
her cranial nerves extra tight.
She cannot escape my control.
Matoi Ryuuko!
...Don't...
...look down...
on us!
What?
Quit making light of us!
This puny thread isn't anywhere
near enough to shackle Senketsu and me!
I don't believe it.
How could she break free
of your mental refitting?
...That sensation I felt just now...
No wonder you give me
such a hard time.
Talk about condescending.
I've got a graveyard full of bones
to pick with you, woman!
But for now, I'm gonna kick her ass!
La vie est juste drôle.
Let's go, Senketsu!
...Life is truly...
droll!
Long time no see, Ryuuko!
...You bitch...
Harime Nui!
Satsuki said she was the one
responsible for killing your dad,
but that was a great big fib!
It was all my and Lady Ragyou's doing.
I know you want this
Sword Scissor returned to you,
so why don't you avenge
your father right here and now?
That said, don't get mad
when I turn the tables on you.
Kiryuuin.
I leave Ragyou to you.
I don't see why you get
to leave anything to me.
Killing my mother has
always been my goal.
Life Fiber Synchronize:
Godrobe Senketsu!
GODROBE
SENKETSU
Have you always been this slow?
Mon Mignon Prêt-à-Porter!
Mere cloth is no match for me!
How could this be?
What's the matter?
I've never seen you put on
such a serious face before.
Ryuuko.
What's up?
Are you gonna tell me
not to get full of myself again?
No. It's the total opposite.
We've never been in such good shape.
You and I have become completely one!
This is truly life and fiber synchronized!
LIFE
&
FIBER
SYNCHRONIZED
You can say that again.
This feeling is out of this world!
LIFE
&
FIBER
SYNCHRONIZED
How can a normal human be so powerful?
Out of my way!
Kiryuuin Ragyou,
you killed my father, Souichirou,
and my little sister who you didn't even name.
You shall atone for that sin!
So in the end, this is all a
mold-ridden plot for revenge?
Such a boring aim
for someone so young.
Great causes are always
fuelled by personal desire!
With your heart bound by Life Fibers,
you couldn't possibly comprehend that!
Can you kill me?
I don't care who or what you are!
...If I slice through your neck...
you can't possibly survive!
Give me your head!
Lady Ragyou!
It's finished.
What's happening?
Shirou!
Honnouji Academy, do you copy?
Honnouji Academy!
Is it just my imagination?
You're the one who's finished,
Satsuki.
So long as a shred
...of the skin on my neck—
no, so long as a single thread
of my neck stays connected,
my body can regenerate.
Not even your Bakuzan
could cut it off entirely, eh?
...How...
Lady Satsuki!
You shall not interrupt.
Satsuki, you seem to be
under a grave misunderstanding.
You're not truly wearing Junketsu.
What are you talking about?
All you're doing is forcing
your arms through its sleeves.
Though for a plebeian like you,
that is still quite an impressive feat.
I applaud your efforts.
...However...
Wearing outfits that are
...out of your league...
is a most unfashionable thing to do!
Wearing Junketsu to this battle
was your second huge mistake!
Though I'm sure you wouldn't have been able
to even stand in front of me without its help!
Enough of your nonsense!
Your thought processes
entertained me greatly.
But it's about time you
returned Junketsu to me.
Ryuuko! Look at the sky!
What the hell?
...Don't tell me that's...
Indeed.
They are COVERS.
Beings born from the original Life Fiber.
Kiryuuin Satsuki!
How unsightly of you, Kiryuuin Satsuki.
Behold the fate of fools that dare
defy me—no, defy the Life Fibers!
You rotten bitch!
Ultimately, Satsuki was
never fit to wear Life Fibers.
Life Fiber Override:
Godrobe Junketsu.
GODROBE
JUNKETSU
That said, that fool did bring me
someone I never thought I'd meet.
...That's...
Impossible!
Matoi Ryuuko,
your body has been fused
with Life Fibers, just like mine.
And here I thought you were dead,
daughter of mine!
kurikaesu mainichi ga
My monotonous everyday life
totsuzen iro wo kaeru
Took on a new hue
sonna koto dokka nozonde itanda kedo ne
A part of me always wished for that to happen
iza to naru to
But when it actually did
okubyoumono deshita
I was too scared to act
himitsu ne
That's a secret, okay?
hitori furuete
Trembling alone
soshite kimi ni aitakute
I miss you so much
zutto mikata da yo nante ieta nara
If only I could tell you that I'll always be on your side
muteki
We could be invincible
sou sa tobidatsu toki wa futari de
When we take flight, we'll do so together
tachimukai
We'll make a stand
kakaekirenai okubyou ni
I don't want to go back
zutto hitatte waratte ita
To being the bumbling coward I was
hitori kiri zutsu ga awasatte
Every little thing will come together
ookina chikara ni naru yo
To give us great strength
ima nee kanjita
That's how I feel right now
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Ryuuko's down, Satsuki's vanished,
and even Mako's missing!
EVEN MAKO
With all three heroines absent,
the show has hit its biggest crisis.
ABSENT
BIGGEST CRISIS
However, the Four Devas are still here.
HOWEVER
STILL HERE
The naked warriors are still here.
Show 'em how tough humans can be!
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"It's Always Rainy at the End of the Road"!
EPISODE 19
IT'S ALWAYS RAINY AT THE END OF THE ROAD