Behold!
SUPER ULTIMA UNIFORM
HUNDRED-MAN ASSAULT
This is the Super Ultima Uniform Hundred-Man Assault!
Charge!
We're not done yet!
It's a super high-speed jammer!
Millions of tiny Life Fibers are
...rotating at a very high speed—
Whoa! It's a huge rubber barrier!
Sanageyama!
This is what you get for
barging in on your own.
You never learn, do you?
...Unless we take that jammer out...
...we can't do a thing, huh?...
Hup!
You two always behave
in such an unsightly fashion.
Let me show you who's boss.
What the?
The stars are gone!
Omnisilk Kouketsu:
Absolute Domination!
EPISODE 24
BEYOND THE INFINITE DARKNESS
What's wrong, Senketsu?
I've lost all my strength.
That light causes all who
touch it to cower in terror!
Omnisilk Kouketsu
rules over all Life Fibers.
Any Life Fiber that opposes it
will tremble in fear and lose all power.
That is Absolute Domination.
ABSOLUTE DOMINATION
Here are the pictures our communications
satellite took from all over the world.
Just take a look.
Everyone across the globe is
clad in REVOCS, Inc. clothing.
Unleashing Absolute Domination
across the whole world
will awaken the Life Fibers
lying dormant in those outfits.
All of mankind will be
consumed by clothing,
and this planet will be covered
in a single piece of cloth.
Earth will become another
Celestial Seed Cocoon Planet,
and newborn Life Fibers shall
once again spread across the universe.
Wonderful.
That is the truth
behind the universe.
You have all been stripped
of the means to resist.
Don't forget about us!
We're still here!
...And we'll show off...
our naked souls!
Ultimate Double Naked DTR!
ULTIMATE DOUBLE NAKED DTR
I don't think so.
Huh? You're not gonna kill them?
Not yet.
They're a valuable energy source
for the original Life Fiber.
The original Life Fiber?
It's still alive?
The original Life Fiber will consume
you all and return in its full glory.
I'm sorry, Ryuuko,
but the plan you risked
your life for was all in vain.
Not yet!
We're not done yet!
Gamagoori!
Mako!
Guys!
Oho?
You can move even under the influence of
Absolute Domination? You're impressively strong.
But it's futile.
Humans are meant
to be slaves to clothing.
That hierarchy will never, ever change!
That's not true!
It can't be true!
I mean, there's no hierarchy in the
relationship between Ryuuko and Senketsu!
That's what humans and clothing
are supposed to be like!
I've had enough of your shtick.
Die!
G-Gamagoori!
As Honnouji Academy's Disciplinary
Bureau Chairman, I, Gamagoori Ira,
will protect Kiryuuin Satsuki
and all of Honnouji's students!
I am their living shield!
Ugly, ugly, ugly!
You're one ugly primate!
Not on my watch!
You bitch...
You may have rendered
Godrobes powerless,
but I can still fight by myself.
It's all thanks to the
Life Fibers within my body.
What?
I am neither human nor clothing.
Rather, I'm somewhere in between.
But right now,
I'm grateful to have this body.
Because it looks like I'm the only one immune
to that Absolute Domination crap of yours!
Gamagoori!
So you're okay, Mankanshoku?
Then I regret nothing.
G-Gamagoori!
Gamagoori!
Harime, you bitch!
...You bastards...
Come, Ryuuko.
This is it.
Lookie here.
It's all thanks to Hououmaru here
that Absolute Domination is active.
Right here.
This is what you should be targeting.
Don't look down on me!
But it's not like you can do anything,
even with that knowledge!
You're being reckless, Ryuuko!
Settle down, Senketsu!
...But... But Ryuuko's...
I know how you feel.
However, Ryuuko won't stop
just because we tell her to.
...Satsuki! Can you...
Yeah. I can hear you.
I see.
Lady Ragyou.
It's almost time.
...Now...
This marks the end for mankind.
Guys!
I'll start with your friends.
They'll all come together to form a single
piece of cloth that will cover this planet.
H-How?
I, too, am neither human nor clothing.
Blade Gale!
...Is this...
I can move again!
This must mean our Ultima Uniforms
have regained their powers.
Precisely.
Life Fiber Override:
Godrobe Junketsu!
GODROBE
JUNKETSU
Mankanshoku!
I never expected you to
be the one who'd save us.
No need to thank me.
Good job, Senketsu!
See that, Ragyou?
This is the power of those
so-called imitations of yours!
...Why? How could a fake Godrobe...
It's because he's a fake.
I realized it when my voice
managed to reach Satsuki.
That I'd been given the
same powers as Ryuuko!
...We're neither humans...
nor clothing!
...And that is the real...
Life Fiber Synchronize!
Ryuuko!
You guys take care of the transmitter.
Yes, ma'am!
Nope.
Nope, nope, nope!
You guys will have to go through me!
Mon mignon prêt-à-porter!
Oh, shut up, you mass-produced rip-offs!
These aren't even worth
collecting data from.
There's no end to them!
...We can't get to...
...the transmitter!...
Leave the transmitter to me!
Gamagoori! You're alive!
Yeah.
I had a metalworker relative of mine fashion
this custom-made titanium protector just in case.
It hurt a little, but it's
barely a flesh wound!
Quit trying to act cool!
You totally passed out there!
I'll make up for that
disgrace with my actions!
Shackle Regalia:
Ego Burst!
SHACKLE REGALIA
EGO BURST
Behold the power of Ego Burst!
It frees me of my restraints and
allows me to unleash my emotions!
Eat this!
UNRESTRAINED
EGO BLAST
Unrestrained Ego Blast!
UNRESTRAINED
EGO BLAST
Leave the rest to us!
Let us exhibit what we nudists can do!
To do so, we need only expose ourselves!
You're just a plain exhibitionist!
What?
...No way...
Your grand Cocoon Planet
Genesis plan is in tatters now,
Ragyou!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Nui!
Cast away your body.
Oui, Maman!
What the hell is that?!
Nui, my girl.
My pitiful girl who couldn't don Life Fibers because
the ones within her body were too powerful.
...But at last, you managed to wear...
the greatest dress of all:
the original Life Fiber.
No, Lady Ragyou.
You will be the one to wear me!
Marvelous.
You feel amazing to wear, Nui.
Of course I do.
But that still makes me happy!
...Nui...
Leave the rest to me.
Hold it!
I figured out what
Ragyou's planning to do.
She's headed for REVOCS, Inc.'s
communications satellite!
So Ragyou and Kouketsu are gonna
make direct contact with the satellite
to transmit the Absolute Domination
signal across the world?
Yes.
But that's an activation signal.
It can't nullify our Ultima Uniforms.
We still have a chance!
...Now awaken...
every last Life Fiber.
Return to your original form,
and cover this entire planet!
Omnisilk Kouketsu:
Absolute Domination!
So it's begun.
I'll go.
I'll go!
Let's go on a date, Ryuuko!
Listen up.
Let's go on a date once you're back.
Let's dress up in cute clothes,
put on some cute accessories,
go shopping,
and eat ice cream
in a world where girls are free
to dress up in the clothes they like!
I'm sure you'll create a world like that!
A world like that!
Gotcha.
We're counting on you.
...For mankind's surviva—
For girls' fashion!
Leave it to me!
Allow me to wear
all of your Ultima Uniforms!
Senketsu Fashion Week!
SENKETSU
FASHION
WEEK
Beautiful.
Truly beautiful.
This is the genesis of the Cocoon Planet.
What?
That's enough, Ragyou!
I see.
So you stitched together all the
Life Fibers you had to get here.
But it's too late.
Look at the surface.
My signal made it to every
Life Fiber across the planet.
Mankind's fusion into clothing
can no longer be stopped.
I can't just give up that easily.
I've got a date riding on this!
What nonsense.
What's the matter?
Those Sword Scissors are
essentially hardened Life Fibers too.
They are powerless against my Absolute Domination,
which rules over all Life Fibers!
No way!
Even so, you committed the grave sin of
pointing your blade at this divine garment.
For that, you will pay!
Pull yourself together, Ryuuko!
Yeah, I'm fine!
I can still fight!
Oh, you poor girl. You've been
shackled by Souichirou's will.
Why can't you comprehend the truth
behind the universe when you're that powerful?
Take a look, Ryuuko.
At that blue planet.
At the shining sun.
At those twinkling stars.
This is space.
But even this beautiful sight
will one day be gone.
All creations will ultimately perish.
That was determined the
moment this universe was born.
The actions of the Life Fibers are
merely in accordance with that principle.
They are but one part of
the truth behind the universe!
Enough of your prattle!
You're my daughter!
How can you be so dull?!
I wasn't raised by you!
Oh, I see.
How rude of me!
That's not nearly enough to kill me off!
Hmm. I must have unwittingly held back.
It seems I still harbor the
faintest trace of a human heart.
In that case,
I should cast it aside!
This is the end!
I'll be the one to decide my end.
You're not the boss of me!
Are you regenerating faster now?
It's a shame that I have to kill someone
who has so high an affinity with Life Fibers!
In that case, you could
go a little easier on me!
Ryuuko, we're running out of time!
All right.
I'll end this now!
End what, exactly?
Your own life?
No, yours.
What?
Did you forget already?
The closer I come to death,
the more powerful I become!
What? Don't tell me you
took that attack on purpose!
Sure did.
I thought of it as my mother's
tough love, and I took it on the chin.
So that Senketsu and I could
reach the peak of our strength!
It matters not!
Life Fibers cannot harm me!
Even if I take that
Absolute Domination ability for myself?
...You can't mean...
The Sword Scissors weren't
Dad's final weapon.
It was Senketsu and me!
Say what?
It's the unlimited absorption ability
that the two of us possess!
I realized it during the fight
with Omnisilk Kouketsu.
The reason I've been absorbing Life Fibers
all this time was to hone that ability!
I was born capable of evolution.
And one day, I developed
a will of my own,
and was able to convey
my thoughts to people!
Yeah, we're neither humans nor clothing!
NOT    HUMAN
NOT CL OTHING
But at the same time,
we are humans, clothing,
ARE       HUMAN
ARE  C LOTHING
and everything else!
ARE   EVERYTHING
Humans can't become clothing!
ARE
HUMANS
Humans are humans,
and clothing is clothing!
IS
CLOT HING
What is this incomprehensible garbage?!
INCOMPREHENSIBLE
That's just who we are!
THAT'S
US
Hear my call, Life Fibers!
Humans are humans,
and clothing is clothing!
Return all of mankind to
the humans they once were!
She did it.
Yeah.
Now we're finally free
of the Kiryuuin family curse.
Impossible.
How could this be?
Will everything I strove
for come to naught?
That's right, Mom.
Earth won't ever become
a Cocoon Planet.
Surrender peacefully,
and let's go back together.
Ridiculous.
I'll be the one to decide my end.
Looks like I'll follow through
on those words before you do.
Don't!
This is not the end, Ryuuko.
Life Fibers are still spreading
across the universe.
And they will reach
this planet again someday.
You can count on that.
Even so, humans will stay human.
Let's go back, Ryuuko.
What's the matter, Senketsu?
Looks like Omnisilk Kouketsu
was more powerful than I thought.
...Don't tell me you're—
Let's hurry back.
We're running out of time!
Don't push yourself, Senketsu!
It's a bit late to be saying that
after all we've been through.
Senketsu!
But this is for the best.
I'm sure your father
can rest in peace now.
I'm glad I met you.
It was fun.
You idiot! I don't want your farewells!
Don't cry, Ryuuko.
Sailor uniforms are
made to be grown out of.
From now on, you're
free to wear what you like.
Clothes that are far cuter
than I could ever be.
Fine! I'll do just that!
I'll wear clothes that'll
dye you green with envy!
Senketsu!
...in there!...
Hang in there!
Ryuuko!
Matoi!
Boss!
Guts!
Welcome back.
I'm home, Sis.
What'll happen to the
rest of the Life Fibers?
The same thing that
happened to COVERS, I guess.
Once they're separated
from the human body,
they'll be cut off from their
energy source and will perish naturally.
With this, Nudist Beach
has completed its mission.
We can finally wear clothes again.
Now, then.
Cleaning up this mess
is going to be hard.
But it's our job as adults
to take care of it.
Besides, those girls have a date to go on.
You're always so obstinate
katakuna ni itsumo
Never willing to give in
yuzurou to shinai ne
Holding on to that childish pride of yours
otonagenai pride
Everyone's the same
douse minna sou
They put themselves first
jibun ga kawaii
I've had enough of it all
mou iikagen ni shite
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
To be an exemplary student
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
rojiura no nukemichi
And take the back alley
amai yuuwaku wa michi
A path of mysterious sweet temptation
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru