This is a king of the hill
final battle!
KING OF
THE HILL
FINAL
BATTLE
Matoi! Battle the Four Devas
and emerge victorious!
Do so, and I shall tell you the
truth behind your father's death.
Say what?!
Matoi! This is where
I will face you in battle!
I am Lady Satsuki's impenetrable shield!
And this is where
I am going to crush you!
I accept!
Life Fiber Synchronize,
Godrobe Senketsu!
GODROBE
SENKETSU
FIRST
NATURALS
ELECTION
KING OF
THE HILL
FINAL
BATTLE
What's this? You talk as though
you're going to be the first to fight.
I'll be the first to fight Matoi.
Fine by me! I'll take you all on!
You really are a fool.
Say what?!
We said one-on-one, didn't we?
We each want to defeat your Godrobe with our own power.
The battle order
has already been decided.
Haven't you Devas noticed that the
pillars you stand on are of different heights?
The more students you have
defeated, the higher your pillar.
Gamagoori defeated
the fewest, so he is first.
Then Inumuta will fight, followed by Jakuzure, and then Sanageyama.
Damn, I beat too much
of the cannon fodder?
That efficient fighting style of mine proved effective, I suppose.
Well, well. The one who suggested
this is at the top of the lineup, huh?
It's sweet that you're so considerate of your fellow students, Gama.
All I did was defend
myself when attacked.
Still, I suppose this means that
you three won't get a chance at her!
What's the holdup?! Get to it already!
What are you in such a hurry for?
The battle begins at 1PM!
What difference does the time make?
Let's get it over with!
No, we will abide by the schedule.
That is what discipline is about!
That is what the rules are about!
EPISODE 9
A ONCE IN A LIFETIME CHANCE
dareka ga katteni kimetara kimeru you na
This is a world that is at someone's beck and call
kyou wo nugisutete
I'll break free of its shackles
RYUUKO
MATOI
hadashi de hashitte iku
And sprint toward my goal
GAMAGOORI IRA
machigattatte
Even if I lose my way
GAMAGOORI IRA
SANAGEYAMA UZU
JAKUZURE NONON
INUMUTA HOUKA
korondatte
Or trip and fall
INUMUTA HOUKA
MANKANSHOKU FAMILY
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
surimuita itami mo
Those wounds will still create
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
KINAGASE
TSUMUGU
original na ashita ni naru
An original future for me
KIRYUUIN
SATSUKI
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
I hold my destiny in my own hands
chikai ga hikari ni natte
And it shines ever so brightly
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
So until the day I reach you
naiteru hima nante nai darou
I don't have the time to sit around crying
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
My burning passion pours out from within me
yozora de kagayaki dasu
And shines like a star in the night sky
umarete kita imi ga
I think I now understand
wakatta ki ga shita
Why I was born
negaigoto ga zenbu kono te de
I'll make all of my dreams come true
kanaeru
With my own hands
The Honnouji Academy King of the Hill
Final Battle will be held starting at 1PM today.
It will be a bloody clash between the
Honnouji Academy Student Council Four Devas
and Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A.
Special live coverage will be
brought to you by Honnouji Television!
Grandmas, grandpas, fathers, mothers,
and good little boys and girls,
let's sit back and enjoy the show!
What? Ryuuko's gonna fight them?!
We can't just sit here!
Matarou, go steal us a
TV set from somewhere!
No prob! I already got us one
for just such an occasion!
Attaboy, Matarou!
It's not showing anything.
Huh?
You try hitting it?
...Better open it up...
Got it.
...Then poke around inside...
...Poke around...
What's in here?
Nothing, looks like.
There aren't any parts inside!
Fine! Let's go to the electronics store!
Aye-aye, sir!
I'm coming too!
No more TV stealing for me!
Here, Ryuuko! Have some tea!
First
Naturals
Election
First
Naturals
Election
Yeah!
Eating Mom's boxed lunches
gives you one million horsepower!
You'll win for sure!
What a pickle this is, Matoi.
Mr. Mikisugi!
Did you come to
cheer Ryuuko on, too?
Yes, that's right.
After all, I'm her homeroom
teacher, more or less.
You bastard!
What did you do to Mako?!
I triggered a pressure point.
She'll just be out for a
little bit, so don't worry.
So what the hell do you want?
Drop out of the fight
against the Four Devas.
Say what?!
They're on an entirely different level
from the club presidents you've faced.
If you're crazy enough to
face four of them in a row,
I don't know what will happen
to you and Senketsu.
If you don't know,
spare me the lecture.
...Ryuuko...
Or are you finally
going to tell me everything?
Like why my father was killed.
I... can't do that.
Then sit down, shut up, and watch.
Senketsu and I will
beat Kiryuuin Satsuki.
And then I'll wring the truth out of her.
With my own two hands.
Hurry up and bring Mako back.
Talking to her makes me feel a
whole lot better than talking to you.
I'll be cheering for her all the way!
Because she's my friend!
Yes, of course! Don't push
yourself too hard, okay?
I'd rather not end up on the
Student Council's bad side because of you.
Is something the matter?
Nope! Your mom's
lunches are delicious!
Seriously, they're great.
Begin!
King Of
The Hill
Round 1
Matoi Ryuuko
vs.
Gamagoori
Ira
King Of
The Hill
Round 1
Matoi Ryuuko
vs.
Gamagoori
Ira
The Hill
Matoi Ryuuko
vs.
Gamagoori
Ira
Begin
Fighting
His Ultima Uniform
has a double transformation.
He's a tough customer.
You listening, Senketsu?
Oh. Yes.
What's wrong?
Nothing, really.
Were you thinking about something?
Possibly.
He's a formidable enemy.
Keep your mind on the fight.
I know. I will.
Let's do it!
Consider that your
final transformation, Matoi!
Three-Star Ultima Uniform:
Shackle Regalia!
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SHACKLE REGALIA
Hey.
What?
Do you want to fight or not?!
Of course!
Then why aren't you attacking me?!
I'll throw what your buddy said this morning back in your face.
You really are a fool, aren't ya?
What did you say?
I know that your Ultima Uniform absorbs the power of
any attacks against you and turns it back on the attacker!
Why would I attack you?
I see. So you really are a fool.
Come again?
Do you think that I wouldn't
anticipate something so obvious?
What the...
Even if no one disciplines me,
I discipline myself!
I use my own techniques
to punish myself!
I punish and punish and punish, bringing myself to a climax!
This is my Secret Technique:
Self-Flagellation!
SECRET
TECHNIQUE
SELF
FLAGELLATION
No way!
Now, let me show you!
THREE
STAR
Three-Star Ultima Uniform:
Scourge Regalia!
ULTIMA UNIFORM
SCOURGE REGALIA
What are you waiting for?
If you fall out of the battle area, you lose right then and there!
Nobody said that was a rule!
That's why I'm telling you now!
Are we clear, Matoi?
Crystal clear!
Thank you ever so much!
You acknowledge that a contest
of endurance against me is futile?
All right, what's your next move?
In that case, it's business as usual!
Finishing Move: Thread Stripper!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
Huh?
His uniform has no
Life Fibers on its surface.
There is nothing for me to absorb!
No way!
Surprised? My Shackle Regalia's
surface is cloth armor,
reinforced by means of special powers.
To absorb its Life Fibers,
you will have to pierce this cloth armor
and thrust your blade
into the uniform proper!
Then I'll just have to cut
all the way to the inside!
Is that wise?
If you attack me,
I become that much stronger!
Scourge Regalia!
Ryuuko!
Stardust Electronics
Look out!
This is bad!
That's the Four Devas for you! He has Ryuuko on the ropes!
Don't you worry.
She ate the lunch I made for her.
So she can't possibly lose!
Impressive. That Godrobe is far more
potent than any other Ultima Uniform.
It gives me the power I need to wield
...my Scourge Regalia ever longer—
your very own power, Matoi!
Oh, dear. What's wrong
with the transfer student?
She's more of a pushover
than I was expecting.
The Disciplinary Bureau Chairman's
forehead is more wrinkled than usual.
Because to him, this is a fight
in the presence of his empress.
No wonder he's giving it his all.
Matoi.
The resolve of this man,
Gamagoori, is nothing to sneeze at.
FIVE
YEARS
AGO
Rinne-Dou
Junior High
63Rd
Graduation
Ceremony
To think that such an earnest former council president
would skip his own graduation ceremony...
If you intend to rule
this school with force,
then I will stop you at all costs!
That is the final task I must
carry out at this school!
Steel armor over your entire body, eh?
Courtesy of my relatives,
who run an ironworks.
Your attacks won't work on me!
Be that as it may,
you cannot defeat me.
I never thought that I could.
My own strength
is not nearly enough.
If you know that,
then why do you oppose me?
I can't defeat you,
but I won't lose to you either!
What did you say?
You can't make me
kneel before you.
If you intend to use force
to conquer this school,
I'll take all of it on myself!
I'll show you that there are those who will never yield to force.
That is my resolve!
Easily said, somewhat
more difficult to do.
If your words are hollow,
expect no mercy!
I won't kneel before you... Never!
I'll never kneel before you!
Did... Did I lose?
Gamagoori. I have seen the
full measure of your resolve.
Come with me, and become my shield.
What are you planning?
People are pigs in human clothing.
I will fight against everything
this world stands for
and completely remake it.
As the first stage of my plan, I will
create a new high school in two years' time.
A high school that will be my army.
Join me there, and you will
be able to attain new strength.
Very well. I will wait two years.
I told you: I am Lady
Satsuki's ultimate shield!
I will crush you here and now!
Like hell you will!
I'm not about to lose to you!
What are you even fighting for?
Vengeance for your father's murder?
You're petty! Petty! Petty!
An attack driven by a
mere personal vendetta
wouldn't even scratch a
great being like Satsuki Kiryuuin!
What?!
And not just her!
You'll never be able to defeat me either!
Oh, gosh!
Are you all right, Ryuuko?
Yeah. I'm in rough shape, though.
But I can't drop out. Not now.
So not only are you a fool,
but you're also a bad loser.
What's bad around here is your luck.
Your bad luck for getting
stuck with fighting me!
Don't do that!
You can't just wail on him
without a plan like that!
He'll hit you with another counterattack!
Is it out of desperation?
That's no good.
Has she finally lost all capacity
for rational thought?
Struggle all you want!
You don't have a chance of winning!
Learn your place as a student
and quietly accept my discipline!
Scourge Regalia!
As if! If I lose to the likes of you,
I'll never learn who killed my dad, no matter how long I try!
Go get him, Ryuuko!
It still hasn't gotten through
that thick skull of yours?
I am Disciplinary Bureau
Chairman Gamagoori Ira!
By shackling and whipping
myself mercilessly,
I tried to set an example
for the students.
"See my behavior,
and correct your own!"
"Mend your ways of your own accord!"
I wish to entrust Honnouji Academy's order to the independence of its students,
and the Shackle Regalia is the
very embodiment of that desire!
To those who still refuse to learn,
I hold back my tears and give them a taste of the cleansing whip!
That is the Scourge Regalia!
If you refuse the whip of love,
then you leave me no other choice!
Let me show you the true terror
of the Shackle Regalia!
Matoi Ryuuko,
your independence is revoked!
I'm going to mold you
into a proper student!
Where do you get off, anyway,
modifying your sailor uniform
into that slutty outfit?!
How utterly depraved!
How utterly deviant!
What about your precious
Lady Satsuki, then?!
She is an exception!
Her form is forged from her
iron will and well-trained body.
Don't give me that
self-serving garbage!
Crap! I'm wrapped up!
Oh? Did I manage to strike a nerve?
All right, Matoi Ryuuko,
it's time to mold you into shape!
This mold is of the ideal,
proper high school girl.
"A proper spirit starts with a proper shape."
...Have a taste of this mold...
and reflect on your wicked ways!
Struggle! Struggle!
She's like a toasted human sandwich!
I won't give up!
I won't rest until I've
straightened you out!
I will mold you!
Mold you into a proper student!
Do you want to win, Ryuuko?
You're asking me such
an obvious question now?!
If you do, I have an idea.
That thing you were
thinking about earlier?
Yes. Will you let me handle this?
Got it!
Ah, she used the power released when disengaging her transformation to break free of the shackles.
But she doesn't have a
hope of winning like that.
Oh, so my words
finally got through to you?
I see that you have returned
to a more proper appearance!
Who would listen
to you, you big pervert?
In that case, taste the
ultimate whip of love!
So, you're applying the idea that "even the
hunter spares the bird that flies to his bosom"?
I must warn you, however,
that I'm not that sentimental!
I'll choke the life
from you here and now!
Having trouble breathing?
But without your Sword Scissor, you have no way to fight back!
Uh-oh. Is it all over?
A shame. I was hoping to
gather more Godrobe data.
No! What's this I'm sensing?
Gamagoori, that was foolish.
Life Fiber Synchronize!
What?!
Senketsu Blade Flash!
SENKETSU
BLADE FLASH
She turned her Godrobe into a blade?
You don't have enough energy to
transform into your Scourge Regalia!
Too late!
Your Life Fibers are
totally exposed now!
Finishing Move: Thread Stripper!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
I-Impossible!
Become obsessed with resolve,
and even that will turn to arrogance.
A shame.
King Of
The Hill
Round 1
Victor
Matoi
Ryuuko
You did it, Ryuuko!
Just like you planned, Senketsu!
If an Ultima Uniform can transform,
it would be unthinkable to
suggest I could not do the same.
That positive outlook of yours is what I love about you, Senketsu!
It learned to alter its configuration based on battlefield conditions.
I'm impressed, Ryuuko.
Still, I guess I can't
simply be happy about it.
Disgraceful!
That was disgraceful, Gamagoori Ira!
...Lady... Satsuki...
Wipe away your own tears.
It's too early to kneel in defeat.
That's one down, Kiryuuin!
...I suppose that means...
...that I will be your ...
next opponent, Matoi.
You are free to rest, Matoi!
Get real!
I gotta waste your chumps
and then come after you!
...Ryuuko...
Okay, let's get to it.
So impatient.
Still, I hate to waste time
just as much as you do.
chime ga naru mae ni
Before the bell rings
kugurinuketa
I sneak out of school
otonatachi no haiiro no me
Avoiding the adults' vacant stares
tawai no nai kaiwa
The pointless conversations
togirenu mama
Keep going on and on
sakamichi wo kudatteku
As I walk down the slope
nani wo suru demo naku
I have nothing to do
yuku ate sae mo naku
And nowhere to go
tada atashi ima wa ne
Right now, all I do
donna chuukoku mo mimi wo surinukeru
Is ignore any and all warnings
mada mada suki ni sasete
Because I still want to be free
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
To be an exemplary student
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
rojiura no nukemichi
And take the back alley
amai yuuwaku wa michi
A path of mysterious sweet temptation
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
To be skilled at searching out
information is to be skilled at love.
Inputting opponent data! To be skilled at analysis is to be skilled at love!
DATA
ANALYSIS
Meticulously observe where
one's feelings are headed!
METICULOUSLY
It's man versus woman:
who will win?!
MAN VERSUS WOMAN
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"I Want to Know More about You"!
EPISODE 10
I WANT TO KNOW MORE ABOUT YOU