This is horrible.
That damn Kiryuuin always does
whatever the hell she wants.
I've arrived, too.
About to enter HQ.
Welcome back, Mr. Mikisugi!
Is everyone ready?
EPISODE 15
DON'T STOP ME NOW
It's been too long, missy!
You've become quite the babe, I see!
And you've become
even more loathsome.
Though I can't remember
where our paths last crossed.
It was back at the garden party to
celebrate your graduation from grade school.
Don't you remember the Takarada Conglomerate's
heir honoring you with his presence?
You should feel honored that
I even recognize your seedy face.
So you still get off on
lookin' down on everyone, do ya?
If you think everyone you meet's just gonna
do what you say, you're sorely mistaken.
The only one who's sorely mistaken is you
for thinking you can stand against me.
You think you can purchase
human lives with money?
What twisted upbringing
led to your vile methods?
All's fair in love, war,
and splashin' out the cash!
Japan is divided between two massive conglomerates:
the Takaradas in the west and the Kiryuuins in the east.
KANEO TAKARADA
KIRYUUIN SATSUKI
If we don't throw this
money around, who will?!
It looks like you've become obsessed
with the power of those strange outfits lately,
but lemme give you the bottom line.
Look!
For the right price, all these people will
gladly lay down their lives for me in battle!
Regardless of the era,
it's money that motivates folk!
That's the power of cold, hard cash!
That is where you're mistaken.
What was that? Some kind of bluff?
What I struck was their hearts.
Begone, fools!
Or my next strike will take your lives!
She's bad news!
Get out of here while you can!
Bye, now!
We're no match for her!
Wait for me!
Do you see now, Takarada?
It is not money that rules
the hearts of men. It is fear.
You think that little stunt
was enough to beat me?
Cut the empty bravado, Takarada.
Your voice is shaking with fear.
Oh, I'm scared! I'm scared, all right!
Acting tough ain't gonna
make me any cash.
So you won't even
try to be a man, huh?
And just when I thought
you couldn't sink any lower.
You gotta be kiddin'.
I'm about to rise higher
than ever before!
Say hello to my anti-Honnouji Academy
mechanized weapon, Doutonbori Robo!
ANTI-HONNOUJI
ACADEMY
MECHNIZED
WEAPON
DOUTONBORI
ROBO
If you're weak, rely shamelessly
on something stronger!
That's my foolproof strategy for winning!
Pathetic.
How incredibly tacky.
Oh? You can tell that
without even usin' your eyes?
Yes. I can sense it in the very air—
the stench of your overblown arrogance.
I hate holdin' the check.
What say we go Dutch?
I'm not speaking of money.
I'm speaking of your disposition.
...Your opinions...
don't add up to jack!
Club members! Guard Lady Satsuki!
Archery! Javelin!
Discus! Shot put!
Everyone else!
Jocks like you ain't worth one red cent!
Good match!
How d'ya like this, missy?
Your precious Ultima Uniforms ain't no thing
against the full might of the Takarada Conglomerate!
Go sell 'em at the
thrift shops in Americamura!
They'll take 'em off your hands for cheap!
You dare mock clothing,
despite never having tasted the fear it brings?
The only thing that's
cheap here is your life!
...As if! Here we go...
Gourd Missile Shower!
Whaddaya think of my
golden gourd bombardment?
There's plenty more
where that came from!
Die! Die! Die!
Die, bitches!
Nobody could've survived that.
So long as I,
Gamagoori Ira, draw breath,
I will not allow so much
as a scratch on Lady Satsuki!
You should quit while
you're behind, Naniwa monkey.
I'll be recording the data from these
new Three-Star Ultima Uniforms.
My apologies for the delay, Lady Satsuki.
The Kobe and Kyoto Battlefield
Trip Brigades have now arrived.
Good work.
Catch, Sanageyama!
Here's your new Ultima Uniform!
At last!
What's with the cheap hero show crap?
Spare me the commentary!
You face Sanageyama Uzu of the
Honnouji Academy Four Devas!
Three-Star Ultima Uniform:
Blade Regalia Mk 3!
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
BLADE
REGALIA MK 3
Oh boy. He really gets into it.
Subjugating Osaka is his mission.
It's only natural that
he should give it his all.
The northern Kanto monkey
versus the Osakan monkey.
It's a monkey vs. monkey battle royale.
Wow, that's quite insightful
coming from you, doggie.
I'm simply taking a page
out of your book, Jakuzure.
After all, the venom of the snake's
flickering tongue is powerful stuff.
Gee, thanks.
Head! Body! Wrist!
Gourd Missile Shower!
Head! Body! Wrist! Head! Body! Wrist! Head! Body! Wrist!
Head! Body! Wrist!
What the hell?!
Do you think I'll allow you to continue
with that pathetic gourd shower?!
You're finished!
Head!
Wh-What the hell is this?!
That there is crab paste slime!
Once you get it on you,
it never comes off!
You ain't movin' any more!
Now you're finished!
Eat-'til-you-drop Fire!
It's baked crab paste for you!
Flame off!
Now, let's see if you turned out
golden brown and delicious.
Oh?
He's not here!
Did you think your
crab paste could coat me?!
...What the—!
Don't underestimate me!
Thrust! Thrust!
Thrust! Thrust! Thrust!
Out!
No, not there!
Anywhere but there!
Not there, not there, not there!
Thrust!
Oh, yes!
I'm dead, I'm dead, I'm so dead!
Do you value your life?
Lookin' down on me again, huh?
You must really be
gettin' off right now.
But this ain't over.
Osaka's all about tenacity and conviction.
Of course.
My target here was never you.
What was that?
Do you think that I would mobilize
a force of this size to fight mere students?
No... You can't be serious!
Who gave you the power to
stand against Ultima Uniforms?
Looks like you're having fun
throwing your weight around, Kiryuuin Satsuki.
Don't you think wrecking
an entire town's a bit much?
Did you come all this way
merely to tell me that?
If so, your trip was for nothing.
Their fate was sealed
the moment they defied me.
I'm going to change that fate.
You're going to give Senketsu back.
Ah, so this is what you are after.
Sanageyama. Dispose of that fool.
At once!
Mako, fall back to someplace safe.
Kay!
Mankanshoku?
The rest of you, stay out of this.
Yes, ma'am!
Can you take it back, Matoi Ryuuko?
Yeah.
I see your defense
is no less impressive.
And I see your drive is the only thing
that's impressive about you.
Very well, then.
The lioness uses her full strength,
even when hunting a rabbit!
Life Fiber Override, Godrobe Junketsu!
GODROBE
JUNKETSU
I won't hold back, Matoi.
Why isn't the transfer student
transforming?
Part of her Godrobe is still in
Lady Satsuki's possession.
When a Godrobe completely awakens,
powerful bio-energy flows
through its Life Fibers.
Any missing part interrupts the flow,
preventing transformation.
It would appear that you cannot
synchronize without this glove.
You transformed knowing that, huh?
Typical Kiryuuin Satsuki!
Your ruthlessness knows no bounds!
You challenged me knowing full well
you were at a disadvantage.
Don't whine to me now.
I'm not whining!
But you are shortsighted and reckless!
It's him! The ripped mohawk dude!
Matoi, run!
Attention! Your objective is the rescue
of Takarada Kaneo and Matoi Ryuuko!
When the mission is complete,
withdraw immediately!
Avoid any unnecessary combat!
Launch all units! Open #4 gate!
That said, I doubt the good Miss Satsuki
will just sit by and let us do that!
Why the change of heart, mohawk guy?
I have no choice.
Mikisugi asked me to back you up.
First you attack me,
and then you protect me?
You must lead a busy life.
We have but one objective:
to resist subjugation by the
Life Fibers that Kiryuuin uses.
That is Nudist Beach's goal!
That name was for real?!
What the hell are you wearing?
I wish I could have kept playing
the lazy teacher forever,
but it looks like
that's no longer possible.
I see you've shown yourselves,
you naked fools.
The true objective of the
Big Three Battlefield Trip
was to smoke out the rebel force lurking
in the shadows behind the Kansai academies.
That is why Lady Satsuki allowed your
activities to continue, Mikisugi Aikurou!
Goodness, you saw through me?
How impressive!
I'd expect no less from one of Lady Satsuki's
stratagems. It worked exactly as planned.
Well, it was technically me
who came up with it.
We were worried that you'd never show
and our new Ultima Uniforms would go to waste.
Do you think a group with a foolish name
like Nudist Beach can thwart our grand design?
Fade like morning dew
before my Blade Regalia Mk 3!
Three-Star Ultima Uniforms!
Shackle Regalia Mk 2!
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SHACKLE
REGALIA MK 2
Symphony Regalia Mk 2!
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SYMPHONY
REGALIA MK 2
Probe Regalia Mk 2.
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
PROBE
REGALIA MK 2
Blade Regalia Mk 3!
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
BLADE
REGALIA MK 3
Honnouji Academy
Four Devas Regalia Mk 2!
HONNOUJI
ACADEMY
FOUR
DEVAS
REGALIA
MK 2
Four Generals, Dressed To Kill!
FOUR
GENERALS
DRESSED
TO
KILL
Ryuuko!
Mako! I told you to go
hide someplace safe!
Yeah, so I came here.
The safest place I know
is by your side!
Oh, right.
Senketsu, let's transform.
Impossible.
Yes, you may have collected
enough to restore my form,
but without that glove,
the bio-energy cannot flow.
Make up for what's left
with my own skin.
No way!
Human skin cannot withstand the energy
that flows through Life Fibers for even one minute!
One minute is more than enough.
Ryuuko?
You want to be worn by me, right?
So don't worry about me.
I'm not scared anymore, either.
If you're my friend,
believe in me like Mako does.
...Friend...
Yeah.
Very well. Let's do it, Ryuuko.
Right on!
Life Fiber Synchronize: Godrobe Senketsu!
GODROBE
SENKETSU
...Son of a...
What?
Kiryuuin Satsuki!
This is nothing but pretense!
Are you that eager to die, Matoi?
Nope! This is how I'll survive!
What?!
Godrobe Senketsu!
Now I have it all back.
Snatching life from
the jaws of death, eh?
Nevertheless,
you still cannot beat me!
We'll see about that!
Your power has increased?
That's what I'm saying.
It has! Don't underestimate Matoi Ryuuko when she's
concentrating on a goal that's almost within reach!
That fool!
Concentrating on
what's in reach? Pathetic!
Have you forgotten the rampage you went on
when you gave in to the rage before you?
Have you forgotten the burning fury
you felt for your father's killer?
I haven't forgotten!
But I won't let it drown me!
I'll never make another
mistake like that again!
I'll push aside the rage
that confronts me
and live for the desire
of what's almost in reach!
The desire to take back my friend!
To protect the friends
that are precious to me!
That is why you wander aimlessly
through life, bereft of ambition!
What about your
oh-so-lofty ambitions, then?
Look at this scorched wasteland.
Is this your ambition?
A necessary sacrifice?
If this is the way you
use the power of Life Fibers,
Senketsu and I will stop you!
You've had your way long enough!
If that's the case, prove it to me
not with words, but with action!
Ryuuko!
Senketsu Blade Flash!
What?!
Senketsu Gale!
...Why, you...
Lady Satsuki!
Lady Satsuki, climb onto me!
Just you watch.
I'll catch up to her in no time!
Perhaps, but like this, you can
never rise above me. Can you, Nonon?
Don't be silly.
Matoi Ryuuko!
...Why, you...
Damn it!
Lady Satsuki!
How impertinent!
What?!
Let's go, Jakuzure. Let's finish this.
Leave it to me.
Matoi!
Now, now. I'd like to collect some
combat data for my Probe Regalia Mk 2.
Ryuuko!
You should worry about your
own skin, Mikisugi Aikurou.
Ryuuko, snap out of it! Ryuuko!
Ryuuko, catch!
Stop it, Mankanshoku.
Take your hands off that scissor.
I show none who stand against me
any mercy. Not even you.
Are you all right, Ryuuko?
Yeah, somehow.
Do you wish to end this here in Osaka?
Ryuuko, trust me.
What?
If we are friends,
put your faith in me.
All right. You got it.
Using your Godrobe as a blade?
Impressive, but pointless.
Junketsu cannot be cut so easily!
I'm well aware of that!
Impossible!
Nice job, Senketsu.
All the blood I had sucked up
was collected in the blade.
It was an all-or-nothing
gamble, but it worked.
You heard him. This blade can
cut your Junketsu, can it not?
Indeed, but not before my Junketsu
pierces through your Godrobe.
Mutually assured destruction... Huh?
Withdraw your troops, Kiryuuin.
Do that, and I'll lower the sword.
Are you sure?
You would be failing
to avenge your father.
I won't sacrifice the lives
of others to achieve my goal.
You wish to trade my life
for theirs, do you?
I'm insulted at how low
a price you've put on me.
Lady Satsuki, please stand down!
Yours is a noble goal!
You mustn't fall here
out of mere stubbornness!
See? He agrees with me.
All students, stand down!
We are returning to Honnouji Academy!
Ryuuko, you dropped this!
Thanks.
Kiryuuin, maybe it's true that you've
mastered that Junketsu of yours.
But you're alone.
And you are not?
No. Senketsu and I are two in one.
Are you suggesting you've formed a
symbiotic relationship with the Life Fibers?
That is a fairy tale.
Come again?
I shall leave Bakuzan
in your care to mark today's battle.
Kiryuuin.
What?
The Kiryuuin Satsuki I know
isn't so petty a woman that she'd rescind an order
she'd given just because she got her sword back.
What the?!
Did you forget about me?
They call us the Four Devas
because there's four of us!
Lady Satsuki, as per your orders,
I have destroyed the Nudist Beach base.
Well done.
With that, we have crushed
the fools who opposed us.
The objective of the Big Three
Battlefield Trip has been fulfilled.
There is no need whatsoever to
rescind my order to return home.
I commend your valiant efforts,
Matoi Ryuuko.
But you merely caught me by surprise.
The same tactic will not work twice!
This battle cost us most of
Nudist Beach's forces.
Still, we should be
grateful that we're alive.
You fought Kiryuuin Satsuki to a draw.
That was impressive, Ryuuko.
Come with me.
I gave you my word.
It's time to tell you everything.
This is a readymade world that is at someone's beck and call
dareka ga katteni kimeta readymade na
I'll break free of its shackles
kyou wo nugisutete
And sprint toward my goal
hadashi de hashitte iku
Even if I lose my way
machigattatte
Or trip and fall
korondatte
Those wounds will still create
surimuita itami mo
An original future for me
original na ashita ni naru
I hold my destiny in my own hands
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
And it shines ever so brightly
chikai ga hikari ni natte
So until the day I reach you
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
I don't have the time to sit around crying
naiteru hima nante nai kara
My burning passion pours out from within me
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
And shines like a star in the night sky
yozora de kagayaki dasu
I think I now understand
umarete kita imi ga
Why I was born
wakatta ki ga shita
I'll make all of my dreams come true
negaigoto wa zenbu kono te de
With my own hands
kanaeru
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
After her battle with Satsuki,
Ryuuko learns her father's secret at last!
SECRET
...That secret is...
Oh, there's not nearly enough time!
NOT NEARLY
ENOUGH TIME
For the full story, search online for the
web version of the KILL la KILL preview!
WEB VERSION
OF THE PREVIEW
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"The Girl Can't Help It".
EPISODE 15
THE GIRL
CAN'T HELP IT