KINAGASE
TSUMUGU
What do you want?
I see you've been looking
after our flowers for us!
GARDENING
CLUB TERRACE
TERRACE
MANAGER
YAGURUMA
KUSANOSUKE
We thought we'd offer you
a token of our thanks.
Hey, this is a non-smoking area!
People who rely on Life Fibers aren't entitled to complain.
How do you know about those?!
Nor are they entitled to answers.
H-He threw a c-cigarette butt into the s-sacred flower bed!
You'll pay for this!
Gardening-Spec, Green-Thumb-Enhancing Two-Star Ultima Uniform!
Remember it well, for this
uniform shall seal your fate!
Fool! A mere gun is useless
against an Ultima Uniform!
Devour him, my pretty!
I-Impossible!
...M-My power is draining away...
Let me tell you two useful
pieces of information.
One: I smoke whenever I want.
—For pity's sake, spare me—
Two.
...I hate...
interruptions!
EPISODE 5
TRIGGER
dareka ga katteni kimetara kimeru you na
This is a world that is at someone's beck and call
kyou wo nugisutete
I'll break free of its shackles
hadashi de hashitte iku
And sprint toward my goal
machigattatte
Even if I lose my way
korondatte
Or trip and fall
surimuita itami mo
Those wounds will still create
original na ashita ni naru
An original future for me
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
I hold my destiny in my own hands
chikai ga hikari ni natte
And it shines ever so brightly
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
So until the day I reach you
naiteru hima nante nai darou
I don't have the time to sit around crying
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
My burning passion pours out from within me
yozora de kagayaki dasu
And shines like a star in the night sky
umarete kita imi ga
I think I now understand
wakatta ki ga shita
Why I was born
negaigoto ga zenbu kono te de
I'll make all of my dreams come true
kanaeru
With my own hands
Life Fiber Synchronization,
Godrobe Senketsu!
Taking hostages? That's pretty low!
You're so cool, Ryuuko!
Mankanshoku Mako
Shut up! This girl isn't a hostage!
She is the Biology Club's
prestigious Guinea Pig #1!
Mankanshoku Mako
I-Impossible!
Don't delude yourselves into thinking that you can beat me with tools you'd use on carp and frogs!
Finishing Move: Thread Stripper!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE WILL
TO FIGHT
I guess that wraps it up.
Thanks, Ryuuko!
You can change the size
of your scissor now, too!
Yeah, basically. It's no big deal.
Your blood has grown salty as of late.
Don't you think you're
getting a little cocky?
You can tell that
from the taste of my blood?
I can immediately spot
any change in your physiology.
Everything from
your weight to your BMI.
That's none of your business!
You've been eating too many of those croquettes, Ryuuko.
No, this is just you poking your lapels where they don't belong!
I can't waste my time on
chumps like these guys!
Calm yourself.
Impatience is bad for you.
As is greasy food.
Give it a rest, damn it!
Wipe that smug look off your face!
I'm incapable of having
a smug look on my face.
I don't even have a face.
Quit nitpicking every little thing I say!
Wow, that's amazing!
You're doing a two-man
comedy act all by yourself!
Oh wait, you were talking
to Senketsu, right?
Sorry, sorry!
Still, that was a close call!
If they had sliced open my belly,
my lunch would have spilled out,
and I would've had to
eat it all over again!
Worry about your life before you worry about your lunch.
—Time to dig in—
You're gonna get fatally wounded
—one of these days, so—
Mako!
Hey, Mako! Say something!
I got her out of our hair for a while.
She is unharmed.
Thanks to the effects of the
needles, when she wakes up
any fatigue she had will be
alleviated, any sickness cured,
and she will be full of vim and vigor.
Oh. Thanks for that.
Your uniform, however,
will receive no mercy!
Run, Ryuuko!
You bastard!
Which club do you belong to?
Take off your clothes.
Huh? Wh-What the hell
are you saying?!
I know, you're from the Pervert Club!
You're from the Pervert Club, aren't you?
The way you're built,
you've got to be in the Pervert Club.
Let me tell you two useful pieces of information.
One: I'm not a pervert.
Keep telling yourself that, pervert!
Two: You are unable to
transform in front of me.
If I fire at this range,
you'll die. Take off your clothes.
You leave me no choice, then.
Come back here, damn it!
I'll be back... to strip you tomorrow.
"I hate interruptions."
That's what you wanted
to say, right, Tsumugu?
Why did you call me?
Pull up a seat. The Kiryuuins
don't have eyes down here.
Why did you call me?
Leave Matoi alone.
This is a crucial period.
I can't do that.
Kiryuuin Satsuki's national school
conquest is complete, except for Kansai.
"Thwart the ambitions of the
Kiryuuins by using the Godrobes."
That was Dr. Matoi's goal,
and that's the path that we of Nudist Beach have chosen.
You're interfering with our mission.
That uniform is too dangerous.
What if Matoi proves herself
to be a powerful ally?
If she's consumed by that thing,
it'll give rise to a threat
even greater than the Kiryuuins.
That's why I'm going to terminate it now,
before that uniform
turns her into a monster.
"People and clothing are not enemies."
Isn't that what Kinue said?
I am greatly indebted to you.
I'll do anything you ask of me.
Unless a Godrobe is involved.
If HQ were to find out,
they'd confiscate all that gear of yours.
Even if they did, I would
continue to go after the Godrobes.
As a naked Nudist.
Wow, you're really chowing down, sis!
Yeah, I'm totally starving!
It's like my fatigue's been alleviated, my diseases have been cured,
and I'm full of vim and
vigor or something!
You've got so much food.
Are you celebrating?
No, I just felt so darn
good when I woke up!
I went to the meat shop,
the grocery store, and the fish store!
I bought all they had!
Wow! Where did you
get all that money?
I put it on your tab, of course, Dad!
Ah, what the heck.
If it comes down to it,
I'll just sell Matarou's organs!
Earth to Ryuuko!
Guts is gonna eat all your food again!
Stop that, you cur!
Don't jump on me!
Don't dig your claws into me!
Don't drool on me! Don't fart on me!
Ryuuko, do something!
I'm done.
Here is the intruder who
attacked the Gardening Club today.
His data matches the Anti-Uniform Guerilla we've had trouble with before.
Anti-Uniform Guerilla?
The man who's been attacking
our affiliated academies?
This is the weapon he uses.
Analysis has revealed that these needles are composed of a special alloy,
and they have the ability to sever the connection between Life Fibers and the human body.
A weapon that can counteract an Ultima Uniform? How impudent.
So this means that
those people sent him.
Those fools who dare
oppose Honnouji Academy!
However, his target this time appears to be Matoi Ryuuko.
Matoi?
So it's the Godrobes he's after.
Then this is nothing more than a
struggle between a sandpiper and a clam.
Sandpiper
Clam
In that case, it's my job to cast the net.
What's this?
Is the musician becoming a fisherman?
The Biology Club I oversee was also
devastated by the transfer student.
The Culture Committee
will take care of this.
If I may, Lady Satsuki?
As you wish.
BACK-ALLEY DOCTOR
MANKANSHOKU
Ryuuko, don't wear me today.
I am the one that man is after.
If you do not wear me, he has no reason to come after you.
And the one I'm after is Satsuki. I'll wear you and take her out!
Otherwise it'll be
open season on us forever.
Shut up. If you keep yammering on,
I won't give you any blood!
She's talking to her uniform again! That's so creepy!
If it weren't for that,
she'd be such a great girl.
I get it, I get it! Just shut up already!
She doesn't have any friends at all, does she?
That's why that uniform means so much to her!
Shut up! I'm not listening!
I'm gonna wrinkle you up!
She's a bit strange, but we of all people should accept her.
Mako, go on ahead. I'll catch up later.
Please.
'Kay, I will!
Ryuuko, Senketsu isn't your only friend!
You have me too!
Anyway, see you later!
Are you afraid, Ryuuko?
Shut up.
Can you fight properly in this state of mind?
Didn't I say to quit nitpicking?
You're just a piece of clothing!
So shut up and clothe me!
Just a piece of clothing, you say?
We'll talk later.
So no more nagging.
Life Fiber Synchronize, Godrobe Senketsu!
I seem to recall someone saying that he wouldn't let me transform!
Victory isn't determined
by physical might alone.
An attack like that
isn't gonna work on me!
Senketsu?
"In the early dawn..."
W-What the hell?
Presenting the three masters of the Honnouji Rakugo Club!
RAKUGO
CLUB
THREE
MASTERS
Hundred Poems By Hundred Poets Club!
The Hundredfold Horde!
HUNDRED POEMS BY
HUNDRED POETS CLUB
HUNDREDFOLD HORDE
Gardening!
Gardening Club Backyard General Manager, Squint-Eyed Uwabami Kusatao!
GARDENING CLUB BACKYARD GENERAL MANAGER
SQUINT-EYED
UWABAMI
KUSATAO
Now we shall exact our revenge for what you did on the terrace.
After that speech before,
are you really satisfied with just
sending small-fry clubs after them?
It'd be boring to simply
beat her outright, wouldn't it?
Wouldn't you do the
same if you were me?
This is an opportunity
to watch a pro at work.
Isn't this a perfect lesson to train for the
genuine battle that Lady Satsuki has in the works?
Oh? I see you've put
some thought into this.
I've been with Lady Satsuki the longest.
I know exactly how she thinks.
Maybe you should be gathering data instead of evaluating me, Four-Eyes.
Where'd you go, Pervert Club?
Ow!
When did he have time
to set up a trap like that?
Ryuuko.
Quit bugging me!
What now, another lecture?
I'm sorry, Ryuuko,
but I can't go on any longer.
Senketsu!
So, the jamming rounds
have finally taken effect.
I can't believe how many rounds it took. That's a Godrobe for you.
Bastard!
Now, take off your clothes!
I sealed the power of your Godrobe.
You have no hope of winning.
You think I'm gonna do
what some pervert tells me?
Let me tell you two useful
pieces of information.
One: There was once a woman.
She believed that people
and clothing were not enemies.
She was a fool.
And because of her foolishness,
she was betrayed by clothing.
Two:
The path you are heading down ends in the same place as hers.
I don't have any damn idea
what you're talking about.
I suppose not.
Ryuuko... Escape without me!
—Sen—
Do you understand now?
This thing just tried to escape by itself.
You're wrong.
It knew that you were
—of no more use, so it—
...Senketsu was trying...
...Life Fibers...
...to protect me!...
...are parasites!—
This uniform is the
only clothing Ryuuko has.
Just look at what you've done to it.
Don't you have any idea how people
who only own one set of clothes feel?!
Who is this?
Ryuuko loves this uniform
more than anything!
She's always whispering to it.
Pretty creepy, huh?
My whole family's weirded out by it!
But that's what people who only own one set of clothes are like!
Taking the clothes off
the back of someone like that
is the same as taking away a friend!
That's right! This uniform
is Ryuuko's friend!
People and clothing can't communicate.
It's impossible for
them to become friends.
They can too!
Up until now, the only friends
I had were in my head.
But then I met Ryuuko,
and I made a real one!
A girl like that could totally
make friends with clothing!
More to the point, she already has!
Shame on you!
You have to take
better care of your friend!
...Thank you, Mako...
Anyway, I'm cleaning the girls' bathroom as punishment for sleeping in class!
Buh-bye!
Where were we again?
Now then. Let go of it.
You'll have to pry him
from my cold, dead fingers!
You want to go through
all that suffering again?
Don't you dare lay a finger on Ryuuko.
If you do, I'll make you pay.
Did it... talk just now?
The uniform talked?
These two... care for each other?
Your battle against the
Godrobe was magnificent.
However, I've grown bored
with the melody you play.
Hand over the girl.
And hand over the Godrobe
to the likes of you?
Turn yourself in, too.
Let me tell you two useful
pieces of information.
One: You people will never catch me.
Two: I'll never hand over
these two, either!
I won't let you escape!
So after all that,
you let him get away?
Inumuta. How is the
Anti-Uniform Guerilla's combat data?
Analysis is complete.
I was able to deduce a pattern.
Very well.
I'm glad that Jakuzure understood what my true intent was.
Thank her for her trouble.
Senketsu!
I'm here.
What a relief.
We'll have to thank
that man, I suppose.
Damn it, I lost!
It was a complete rout!
...Ow...
We're both in tatters.
Don't push yourself.
Senketsu.
You and I need to
become even stronger.
No, we can become even stronger. As long as we're together.
Yes. After all, I am the
only clothes you have.
No, you're not just that.
You're my friend.
Indeed.
But don't measure my BMI anymore.
I can't accept that request.
I thought we were friends!
You need to lose
2cm from your waist!
2cm?! Get off my case, man!
Well done saving Matoi.
I suppose this means
your debt to me is repaid.
That isn't enough.
It's plenty. I only put girls
in my debt, anyway.
Let me tell you two useful
pieces of information.
One: I'm only giving her a chance.
Two: If I see things
coming apart at the seams,
I'll be back to rip it off her.
chime ga naru mae ni
Before the bell rings
kokuu ni muketa
The adults' vacant stares
otonatachi no haiiro no me
Drift into empty space
tawai no nai kaiwa
The pointless conversations
togirenu mama
Keep going on and on
sakamichi wo kudatteku
As I walk down the slope
nani wo suru demo naku
I have nothing to do
yuku ate sae mo naku
And nowhere to go
tada atashi ima wa ne
Right now, all I do
donna chuukoku mo mimi wo surinukeru
Is ignore any and all warnings
mada mada suki ni sasete
Because I still want to be free
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
To be an exemplary student
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
rojiura no nukemichi
And take the back alley
amai yuuwaku na michi
A path of sweet temptation
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Sanageyama Uzu, Honnouji Academy's Athletic Committee Chair.
SANAGEYAMA UZU
Sanageyama Uzu, one of the
Honnouji Academy Student Council Devas.
SANAGEYAMA UZU
Sanageyama Uzu, a man with so many titles that introducing him has eaten up this entire preview!
MAN
SANAGEYAMA UZU
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"Don't Toy With Me on a Whim."
EPISODE 6
DON'T TOY WITH ME ON A WHIM