I knew without
a doubt that I killed—
Nothing can change that fact.
That's why I decided
to come clean.
This is my confession.
It's been two weeks
since that trip,
and nobody can remember—
being a member of the class.
He's been completely forgotten,
and only I, the person involved
with his death, can still remember—
I get the feeling it's only
a matter of time, though.
That's why, while I
can still remember,
I want to tell you the truth,
and how you can
stop the calamity.
Are you listening?
Send them back to death,
where they belong.
Send the dead back to death.
That's how to stop the
calamity once it's begun.
There was a girl who looked like
her back in elementary school.
Are you talking about Misaki?
Yes.
Isn't Misaki an only child?
We weren't in the same class,
but I know there was
someone called Misaki.
That's strange.
Judging by her address,
she wouldn't have been
in the same school as you.
Right? That's why it's strange.
Did she wear an eyepatch
over her left eye?
No, she didn't.
Our Misaki lost her eye
when she was four!
Huh? That means...
Tragedy
Is the dead person
here with us?
The extra person...
...is here.
Who is it?
It's...
Sakaki!
I think I fucked up!
Teshigawara? What happened?
May I ask you both a question?
What is it?
Do you know someone
named Kazami Tomohiko?
Huh?
Just answer me!
Do you know Kazami?
Who is he?
Of course I know him.
He's a class officer and the guy
you've always been stuck with.
And you, Misaki?
How would I not know him?
Fuck...
Something bad happened.
What happened?
I think I fucked up bad.
How? What did you do?
I... I, uh...
I was certain that
he was the extra...
So I...
The extra? Don't tell me...
Kazami.
No way!
Yes!
You can't be serious.
Why on Earth would
I lie about this?!
I kept poking at him because
he'd been acting strange lately.
He told me that he didn't remember anything about our childhood.
That he didn't remember much
from elementary school, either.
And then?
I prepared myself, and asked him,
"You're not really Kazami, are you?"
"You're the extra person, aren't you?!"
He was alarmed at first,
but then flew into a rage.
He acted so suspicious that
I was certain it was him.
So, like we heard on the tape,
if he died—if he "returned to death",
we'd all be saved.
Don't tell me...
...you killed him?
Did you... really?
I didn't intend to.
We had started grappling, and then ended up outside on the balcony.
Before I knew it...
...he laid still on the brick floor.
There was blood
pouring from his head.
Then, I got scared,
so I ran down the hall.
I saw you come in here earlier...
...and you wanted to find out
if Kazami was the extra?
Yeah.
I thought that,
if the extra died,
then it'd be as if
he'd never existed.
Since you two said
you know him, though....
I must have fucked up!
Hey, Sakaki. What should I do?
You either made a mistake,
or he's not really dead.
Huh?
Falling two stories down
wouldn't necessarily kill him.
You can't see it from here.
It's past that row of shrubs.
We should check to
see if he's alive, first.
Y-Yeah.
Maejima?
What happened?
Blood...?
I can't...
No way...
Were you stabbed?
I looked... in the dining hall...
Th-The manager...
The manager?
Maejima!
We've gotta get out of here!
Why are you
screaming, Kouichi?
Sakaki! What's going on?
Who is that?
It's Maejima!
He's hurt!
How?
He's been stabbed!
There's also a fire
in the dining hall!
A fire?
The manager's inside, dead.
He was murdered!
The killer must've
started the fire.
Seriously?!
Dammit.
Did you find Kazami?
No.
Huh?
Was that... Takako?
Sugiura!
Get Maejima someplace
safe, and call 119!
Right...
This room...
...is mine and Takako's.
Takako, are you here?
No way...! Takako!
Takako! Where are you?
Takako!
Sakakibara?
What's happening?
Have you seen
Sugiura or Kazami?
I saw Kazami.
He came by my room, covered with mud, his face clouded with anger,
saying that Teshigawara
was acting weird.
Huh?
I asked him what happened,
but he glared daggers at me.
Then I mentioned the tape...
You told him?
Yeah.
Where is he?
It's gone!
The tape recorder's gone!
Wha— How?
Sakaki!
Is Kazami in here?
How's Maejima?
I left him with someone who heard the screams and came by to help.
Hey...
What on Earth is happening?
Let's split up and
search for Kazami.
Stop by every room and
tell everyone to evacuate.
There's a fire! We need to leave!
Huh?
A fire?
A killer?
Somewhere inside this building.
There's also a fire
in the dining hall,
and we've no clue as
to where Kazami went.
Everything's going horribly!
We have to tell Ms. Mikami.
Ms. Mikami? Are you there?
We're coming in.
She's not here.
Is that blood?
No doubt about it.
Do you think something
happened to Ms. Mikami?
H-Hey... maybe we should go outside and call the police.
No.
Not until we make
sure Ms. Mikami's safe.
Ms. Mikami...?
Who's voice was that?
Teshigawara's...
...and Mochizuki's.
It came from downstairs.
Let's take a look.
There you are.
Takako!
Are you okay?
Thank goodness.
If you had died too,
I wouldn't be able to go on.
Much like how you
can't live without me.
Takako...?
Send the dead back to death!
Ouch!
Teshigawara! Let's run!
M-My leg...
Send the dead back!
Stop!
Get the fuck out here!
"Send the dead back to death"...
How did she know about that?
She... listened to the tape.
You found it in class 3's
old homeroom, right?
Ogura told me.
We're looking for a clue
to help stop the calamity.
Seriously?
I see.
So someone brought the tape here?
Yes. Mochizuki did.
As the head of countermeasures,
I had to listen to it.
Why does she think Misaki
is the dead person, though?
Ever since our trip to the beach,
Takako's been emotionally unstable.
I'm going after her.
Akazawa!
It's dangerous to go alone!
This is an important announcement from the head of countermeasures to all the students of class 3.
The tape you are about to hear
was left behind 15 years ago,
when the calamity was stopped midyear.
—and how you can
stop the calamity.
Are you listening?
Send them back to death,
where they belong.
Send the dead back to death.
That's how to stop the
calamity once it's begun.
This is the truth.
This is how the calamity was
stopped midyear, 15 years ago.
And, the dead person this year is...
Misaki Mei.
I know this for a fact because we both went to the same elementary school,
and her left eye was intact.
Yet now, she is
missing her left eye.
Do you know
what this means?
It means she was
reborn incomplete.
The Misaki Mei we
now know is a fake.
That's why...
...we must kill her!
No!
Return the dead...
...to death.
Stop it!
Ms. Mikami!
You can't kill your own classmate!
But if we send the dead
person back to death,
no one else will have to die!
If we kill Misaki,
the calamity will end!
No!
Don't do this!
You're making a mistake!
Who the fuck's the
dead person, then?!
I don't know, but...
I... I don't...
I don't want to die!
No!
You fucking...!
Asshole!
There she is!
The dead girl!
I'll avenge my brother!
No!
You—
I'm sorry!
Open up!
Dammit.
Move!
Careful, it's slippery.
Found you!
Send the dead back to death!
Ogura!
They're in the hallway!
We're saf—
Go in from downstairs!
You really think it's Misaki?
There's something off about her.
I know, but...
Something smells burnt.
He did say there was a fire.
I don't see any flames, though.
The dining hall?
We should be safe here.
I think it's over.
What on Earth happened?
An explosion in the
dining hall, probably.
I see.
Maejima passed out in
front of the dining hall...
Could Sugiura have...?
It wasn't me.
It was probably that old hag.
Old hag...?
You're...
...a nuisance!
However, since you're not
the dead one, I won't kill you.
Besides, Izumi seems fond of you.
Send the dead back to death!
Damn you!
Why...?
Why is this happening?
Kouichi?
Akazawa!
Who is that?
Takako!
Misaki Mei...!
You really are...
No, Akazawa!
Sugiura was...
I'll kill you!
If the dead person was gone,
all of these tragic things...
would end, right?
Misaki?
Misaki!
The Dead