I got it!
I heard Nakao
was hit by a boat.
So leaving Yomiyama
doesn't negate the curse?
I guess not.
Sheesh... So we can't escape it?
What should we do?
Hey... are you still
going on the class trip?
No way!
Why would we go on a class trip the summer when it happens?
We should just stay
locked up at home.
I suppose so.
But... why is this
happening to us?
It's so unfair.
Yeah.
If only that transfer student
hadn't spoken to Misaki...
I...
I protected them...
I left it for them...
...in the classroom.
Link
Well then, you two be careful.
Yes, ma'am.
How was Nakao that day?
He was carsick,
so he threw up a lot.
Anything else?
Let me think...
He couldn't swim well.
I see.
So, maybe he was right.
What do you mean?
Well, I spoke with the detective, Mr. Ohba, about what happened.
His suspicion was...
...that Nakao might have died
before the boat hit him.
The injury found on his head was
inconsistent with the collision to the boat.
The cistern obliteration, caused by cerebral
contusion, had already progressed significantly.
So it happened before
we went to the beach?
According to his family,
they heard a loud bang from
the staircase that morning.
When they went to take a look,
all they saw was Nakao
hurrying out of the door.
He must have hit his head then.
Most likely.
So the event that led to his
death took place in Yomiyama?
We can safely assume that.
Leaving Yomiyama without first going
to the hospital assured his death.
Hey, Misaki?
Yes?
No, never mind.
I'll tell you after I find out.
All right.
Did you find that class
photo from 26 years ago?
Not yet.
It's your fault.
It's your fault!
Inoya
The classroom?!
Did he really say that?
Yeah, he did.
He must mean ninth grade's
class 3 in the old building.
What did he hide?
I see. At the very least,
we have a location.
I'll just...
Wait.
Don't tell anyone else.
Why not?
If Nakao hadn't gone
to the beach with us,
he probably wouldn't have died.
Well, yeah...
That's why I don't want to
get anyone else involved.
I don't want
anyone else to die.
We shouldn't tell Akazawa, or the
countermeasures committee just yet.
If we do find something,
and if we need their help,
we'll tell them.
Makes sense.
I don't want to see Akazawa die.
So when should we go?
We aren't going right now?
I have plans with
my family tonight.
Tomorrow's better.
How about first thing
in the morning, then?
C'mon! Not the morning!
Okay... How about at noon?
There'll be a lot of
club members around,
and since the second
floor is blocked off...
Okay... How about
in the evening?
It's harder to look
for stuff at night.
Fine. We'll go at
three o'clock, then.
Okay.
Sounds good.
Mochizuki, the art club meets
in the old building, right?
Yeah.
Do any club members
come during summer break?
No, never.
So can we meet
in the club room?
Sure.
I have a key,
and no one would
question my being there.
Teshigawara, please don't
show up dressed like that.
Why not?
You'll stand out.
Inoya
That's the price to
pay for lookin' good!
Inoya
Oh? Is that Kouichi and Teshy?
What are the aces of the
go-home club doing at school?
Nothing, really.
We're meeting up with Mochizuki.
Are you two here for club stuff?
We wanted to meet
with Mr. Chibiki.
In the auxiliary library?
Not for that.
Mr. Chibiki is the
drama club's advisor.
Seriously?!
The guy who wears
nothing but black?
I didn't expect that.
He actually gives
good acting advice.
He also looks kinda cool
when he's acting. It's fascinating.
So?
Why exactly are you two here?
We're looking for a clue
to help stop the calamity.
We don't know what it is,
but if we find it,
we'll tell everyone about it.
Seriously?
There's really
something like that?
We want to stop class 3's
calamity ourselves, if possible.
You two wanna come with us?
Hey!
No thanks.
Same.
Goodbye, Kouichi.
See ya.
Later.
Misaki?
Where's Mochizuki?
I don't know.
I just got here.
Why are you here?
I had nothing to do,
and I didn't want
to stay at home.
I figured I'd come here and draw.
I see.
What about you two?
And... Mochizuki's coming too?
What are you three going to do?
Well...
Well... we're, uh... exploring?
Sorry, I'm late!
And where do you
three plan on exploring?
Well...
Well, Teshigawara said
we should meet here.
No, I...
Right!
Sakaki said he had
to look for something!
It's a bit important.
Do Not Enter
We don't know
what could happen,
so I'd rather you
stayed in the club room.
I'll be fine.
Are you sure?
You really are weird, Misaki.
Aren't you scared?
No, I don't think I am.
Which one is class 3's?
Probably the one in the middle.
There are only five classrooms.
By the way, didn't this old building
have like, seven mysteries or something?
Dunno.
I also don't give a shit
about some urban legends.
So you don't believe in
ghosts, curses, and the sort?
Hell no!
They're all just coincidences
or tricks of the eye.
Except for the calamity, of course.
Isn't "the secret of the auxiliary library"
one of those seven mysteries?
Is it?
They say you can hear
someone's voice coming from inside.
Have you heard of it?
Nope.
I heard there's an old
archive in its basement,
containing secret writings that
can't be revealed to the public,
and that a librarian once locked
himself inside to guard them.
So that librarian is still alive,
and you can hear his voice?
I bet it's just Chibiki.
I sometimes hear
voices in there.
Seriously?
Really?
Just kidding.
Let's let in some fresh air.
You're not fine at all.
Yes, I am. See?
You look fine to me.
We wouldn't want anyone to see us and turn us into another one of the seven mysteries.
So let's just keep
the windows closed.
Teshigawara!
You gotta be kidding me...
You seem fine.
Take care.
Yeah.
I'll call you.
Later.
I can't find anything.
I don't think it'd be in an
easy-to-find place, like in a desk.
It wouldn't be in an
impossible-to-find place, though.
There'd be no point in leaving it.
That's true.
It's probably not on the
floor, or in any desks.
What about in there?
All I see are cleaning supplies.
What's that?
Find something?
Something's written on it.
Let's see...
"To the future students who are undoubtedly
suffering from the senseless disaster of this class."
Bingo!
That's it!
Mr. Matsunaga must
have written that!
A/V Room
I think there's one in here.
Are we allowed to use it?
So long as no one finds out.
Found it.
All right. Let's play it.
Um...
My... My name is
Matsunaga Katsumi.
I'm a ninth grader
in 1983's class 3.
When I'm done recording,
I plan on hiding this
somewhere in the classroom.
If you're listening to this tape,
then you're most
likely in class 3 too.
I wonder if that's the case...
Ayano
You may also be terrified by the
senseless disaster that I—that we...
Ayano
But never mind that.
I have two reasons
for leaving this tape.
One is to confess a sin. My sin.
I want to tell
someone what I did,
and I want someone to listen.
The other is to give
you all some advice.
It's about the extra student
who gets mixed up in the class,
the calamity that
occurs as a result,
and how it can be stopped.
In other words...
Actually, I should start
from the beginning.
Our class went on a trip.
We all left on August 8th,
for three days and two nights.
Our homeroom teacher, Mr. Koga,
suggested that we visit a local shrine.
There's an old shrine in this town
called Yomiyama Shrine.
He said that if we all prayed there,
then the curse
would surely be lifted.
There were 22 students
total, including myself.
We were all skeptical.
On the second day,
we climbed the mountain
to visit the shrine.
It was very old and run-down.
As if it had been
abandoned by the world.
Even though it bears
the name of the city,
it looked like it hadn't
been maintained at all.
So while we were there,
we decided to clean up.
At the time, we hoped that
maybe this would lift the curse.
And after we prayed,
our teacher confidently declared,
"Everything will be all right now."
But it wasn't.
It wasn't that easy.
As soon as we left the shrine,
the clear skies suddenly
turned overcast,
and it began to rain.
There was even lightning.
We hurried down the mountain.
The first victim was
a boy named Hamaguchi.
He was kind of dumb.
He was the only one
who'd brought an umbrella.
And we were on a mountain,
during a lightning storm...
He was walking
in front of me, then...
For a second,
my vision went white,
and I heard a huge crash.
Hamaguchi had been
struck by lightning.
I still remember the smell
of his flesh burning...
Anyway, the students
panicked and bolted,
leaving Hamaguchi behind.
They were desperate to get off the
mountain as quickly as possible.
Moments after we
blindly took off...
The second victim was taken.
A girl named Hoshikawa.
In her panic,
she slipped and
fell off a tall, sheer cliff.
All we could do was call for help
at the foot of the mountain.
But in the end, we couldn't
save either of them.
Praying at the shrine
had absolutely no effect.
Now, this is the important part.
Right after we finally reached
the bottom of the mountain,
that's when it happened.
And by it, I mean...
I...
Crap!
That was close.
I was in a cold sweat.
Me too.
The tape!
Hey...
You idiot.
You've gotta be kidding!
We didn't get to hear
the important part!
What should we do?!
All we need to do is fix the tape.
It can be fixed?
I think so.
Great! Thanks, buddy!
We've gotta hear the rest!
Do you mind if we
leave it with you?
I'll do what I can.
Brother!
Jet Black