A girl in class 3 died.
Everybody's talking about it.
When she fell down the stairs, her umbrella
flew out of her hand and impaled her throat.
Seriously?
It was so horrific that the witnesses were told to never speak of it again.
Wasn't she a class officer?
I heard her mother died in
an accident that same day.
Do you think it's that curse?
You know of it?
It's the school's
most famous secret.
The curse of class 3, and the story that started it all 26 years ago.
Yeah...
Does that mean it's going
to happen again this year?
Who knows. Nothing
happened last year,
Once it's started, a person
dies every month, right?
Yeah. At least one person connected to the class dies per month.
Not just students?
Families are at risk too, they say.
Especially parents and siblings.
You sure know a lot about it.
One of the seniors in my
kendo club is in class 3.
He told me in private.
He seemed completely
skeptical, though.
But someone actually died.
I know, right?
It's probably best to
stay away from that class.
Yeah.
Silhouette
A
June 2 (Tue.)
Redial
Teshigawara
Hey, Sakakibara.
How's your lung doing?
It seems fine.
But you witnessed
such a gruesome event.
That sort of thing
can affect your body.
You know about that?
My little brother told me.
He's in the same class as you.
Mizuno Takeru.
He plays basketball.
Are you here for your checkup?
Yes.
Right. Let's talk afterwards, then.
I should be home by now. My shift ended hours ago, but things keep coming up.
Something weird is going on.
There was also
that other incident.
About that girl who
died here in April?
Try not to stress
yourself over it.
If you do have to be
hospitalized again,
I'll be sure to take
extra good care of you.
Great. Thanks in advance.
All right, I'll see you later.
This is nothing that should
affect school attendance.
However, no strenuous
activities just yet.
Let's keep an eye on things
for another month.
Okay.
Sorry to keep you.
How'd it go?
It looks like you won't
have to take care of me.
Aw, that's too bad.
It's a little late, but do you
want to grab lunch somewhere?
So Fujioka Misaki was the cousin of that girl with the eyepatch?
Anyway, I rarely talk to my little brother, but he did tell me a few things.
It seems your class has
some special circumstances.
Special circumstances?
Yep.
He wouldn't explain
anything, though.
You know, don't you?
About the circumstances?
I know something's going on,
but nobody will tell me.
Really?
My little brother
seemed to be scared.
Though, that's just a hunch.
What do you mean?
He doesn't think that the incident last week was an accident.
Not an accident?
And that's why he's scared?
Maybe...
Why...
Um, have you heard of
someone named Misaki Mei?
Misaki?
Misaki... Mei? Who's that?
A girl in class 3.
Has your brother
ever mentioned her?
I told you, we don't talk much.
Actually, the girl with the
eyepatch I told you about
is named Misaki Mei.
Oh?
So, Sakakibara,
do you like this Mei girl?
No, not that.
It's just... something's
been bothering me.
Something about her is different from the rest of the class.
Isn't that what it
means to like someone?
That's not it.
Fine, fine.
What's so different
about this Mei girl, then?
Well...
She's a bit strange.
At first, I thought she was
being bullied by the other kids,
but I don't think that's it.
It's more like
they're all scared of her.
Scared of her?
Well, not exactly...
Someone told me not to involve
myself with things that don't exist.
Things that don't exist?
She claims nobody else
in the class can see her.
Right after she told me,
that accident happened.
If you think about it logically,
it seems like a coincidence.
I mean, there's nothing
connecting those two events.
Right?
There's one more thing
that's bothering me.
They say it happened 26 years ago.
Have you heard about it?
Not until now.
But I went to South Middle.
I still don't know what
it has to do with all this,
but I can't help thinking
there's some connection.
I see.
This whole thing is turning
into quite the horror story.
So, do you want me to
ask my brother about it?
You're going to school
tomorrow, right?
Yes.
If I hear anything,
I'll let you know.
When's your next checkup?
This Saturday.
June 6th, huh?
I don't think Damien
is in this town...
At any rate, let's be careful.
Especially where unusual
accidents are concerned.
I don't think Damien
is in this town...
No way.
Oh! Look who I found!
Hiya, Kouichi! Skipping school?
No, I just left the hospital.
Oh, yeah. That makes sense.
What about you? Are you sick?
Yeah, that's right!
You're quite the actress.
I hate to say it, but
I'm happy you think so.
Happy?
Yeah! It means my hard work
in the club is paying off!
Which club?
To be, or not to be:
that is the question.
Oh, you're in the theater club?
Yep! With Izumi!
Izumi... Who was that?
Akazawa Izumi.
She tends to be a bit dramatic.
It shows in her acting.
But she's not a bad person.
So I hope you'll
help her out, too.
Uh, sure.
No... No! No! No!
I don't want to die!
No!
The Hollow
Blue Eyes of Yomi
at Twilight
Welcome.
My, it's unusual to see
a boy your age here.
Are you a customer? Or perhaps...
Hello.
Are you a junior high student?
In that case, I'll give you half price.
Thank you.
But please, take your
time looking around.
I have no other customers.
Fancy meeting
you here again.
What brings you here today?
I was on my way home
from the hospital,
and I just happened to walk by.
What about you?
Didn't you go to school?
I only go when I feel like it.
How are you feeling?
It looks like I won't
have to be readmitted.
After that accident...
how's the class been doing?
They're all terrified.
Of what?
They think it's begun.
"It's begun"?
Deep down, they may
have only half-believed.
But now...
Despite what they told you,
I don't think they fully believed.
But it looks like it really is true.
I'd say it's 100% likely
that it's already begun.
That's why...
Sakakibara, you still don't know?
You're better off that way.
It's best if you never find out.
Once you do...
What on Earth
happened to class 3?
Are you going back to school?
Yeah, tomorrow.
I probably shouldn't show up, then.
Why?
Be careful.
Hey, Misa—
Why? Why?
Yeah, that's what
I want to know.
Why? Good morning, Rei!
Good morning!
Kouichi?
Are you okay?
It's just a headache.
I've been getting
them a lot lately.
It's pretty annoying.
Maybe you're just exhausted.
Maybe.
Hey, Reiko?
You said there's a right time to
find out about everything, right?
How can I know when that is?
Did I say that?
Um, so...
Which class were you
in during ninth grade?
During ninth grade...?
Class 3.
Class 3?
So people talked about class 3 being cursed back then too?
I can't remember.
It was 15 years ago.
You're going to school
tomorrow, right?
Remember the tips I gave
you to prepare for Yomi North?
Yeah.
Including the third one?
Of course. And the fourth, too.
The third one was to always uphold the class rules, right?
Yes. That's...
Er, um... What was...
The third thing
I needed to know.
Oh, yeah. It's, uh...
Always uphold the class
rules. Which means that...
Are you okay?
I really am exhausted.
Sorry, Kouichi.
I can't help you.
Why—?
Don't say that!
I can't stand that damn bird!
June 3
(Wed.)
Sakuragi used the
west stairwell, right?
Why would she use
one so far away?
She must've had a reason.
Takako said she saw...
Sugiura Takako?
What did she see?
When Kouichi...
I honestly thought it
wouldn't happen this year.
There are two possibilities.
It's not happening this year,
and Yukari's death
was just a coincidence.
Or it started back in May.
As the head of countermeasures,
I can't rely on wishful thinking.
It'd be one thing
if it was just Yukari,
but her mom died too.
Is it because he broke the rules?
Why would they bring a new student to class 3, anyway?
It was convenient for the school.
The new principal still doesn't fully understand our situation.
Shouldn't the teachers
explain it to him?
They might have thought it was
best to keep it among the students.
So even the teachers want
nothing to do with this...
This is all because I was
absent on his first day.
If I had warned him earlier,
this wouldn't have happened.
What's done is done.
The question is,
what do we do now?
And how do we let him know?
It'll be difficult to
explain it to him now.
And explaining it poorly
could be dangerous.
Like getting caught
in our own trap.
This is a lot like the situation
this class was in two years ago.
Does that mean we need
new countermeasures?
That's what I heard.
Seriously?
H-Hello?
Where are you?
Uh...
Don't "uh" me. Where are you?
I've been trying to
call you all week.
Why aren't you answering?
Sorry! I was going
through some stuff...
Besides, you were sick.
You promised
you'd tell me in June.
You mentioned
"the first year", too.
What exactly happened?
Just hang on. Okay, Sakaki?
I did promise that, sure.
I know, but...
The situation has changed.
That's right! The
situation has changed!
Normally, it's up to the head of
countermeasures to handle this stuff.
But because this guy acted on
his own, things got complicated.
That's why.
You want me to pretend he
never made that promise?
Yes. As a favor to me.
Rather, to the entire class.
Fine.
But you said it's dangerous to involve myself with things that don't exist.
What did you mean by that?
Incoming Call
Mizuno
What were you thinking?!
Hello?
Well, I...
Are you on lunch break right now?
Explain yourself!
I'm sorry!
Do you have time to talk?
Do you realize what you've done?
What's up?
I wanted to check with
you on something.
We have enough to worry about as it is...
Check on what?
About that Mei girl you told me about yesterday. Misaki Mei.
Does she really exist?
Yes, she does.
Is she nearby?
For sure?
Where is she?
She didn't come
to school today.
So she's not there...
Why do you want to know?
I spoke to my
brother last night.
He refuses to talk about
the incident 26 years ago,
or the accident last week.
But when I asked
him about Mei,
his demeanor suddenly
changed, and he said,
"What are you talking about?!"
"There's no girl like
that in our class!"
He was incredibly stubborn.
That's... not true.
But he was dead serious.
He has no reason to lie.
Misaki Mei exists!
What?
Can you hear me?
I just got on the elevator.
I have to get back to work.
Oh, that explains the static.
But this is...
Mizuno, can you hear me?
What's going on?
Mizuno
Scattering