Did you hear about Ayano?
She tried to escape, right?
I think so.
Did she die because
she tried escaping?
I don't know.
Ogura's brother died
that day too, didn't he?
Yeah.
Wasn't he a shut-in?
I heard something
about the class trip.
Get this, apparently
it's important.
How so?
Like, asking the gods for help?
I heard the class was
saved before by doing that.
Stupid...
Stupid brother!
You idiot!
Ouch!
I'm sorry! Are you all right?
You okay?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Sakakibara Kouichi.
Jet Black
Sakitani
Memorial
Hall
Got the tape?
Yep.
Listen to it?
Not yet.
I'm too scared to do it alone.
Let's take a commemoration photo.
It's our last summer
break in junior high.
How about it?
Sakitani
Memorial Hall
Everyone line up over there.
Perfect.
Let's get the teachers in it too.
All right, almost ready.
Sakakibara and Misaki,
squeeze a little closer together.
Mochizuki, you
should be in one too.
I'll take it.
Here goes!
Hey, Mochizuki, you and
Ms. Mikami are too spread out.
You too, Sakaki and Misaki!
Kazami, you're fine there.
All right. Say, "Cheese"!
Tomorrow, we'll visit the
shrine to pray for our safety.
Right.
This is a nice lodge.
A local business donated
its recreation center.
A bit lavish for
students, if you ask me.
Welcome.
We've kept all the
rooms open for you.
Thank you for having us
for the next three days.
We're happy to.
Thanks for coming.
If you need anything,
don't hesitate to ask.
Okay.
Here we go.
—Now, this is the important part.
It happened after we reached
the bottom of the mountain.
And by it, I mean...
I...
It happened in the forest,
outside of the lodge.
I got into an argument
with a guy named—
We went at each other.
And... And...
...before I realized it,
he wasn't moving.
He was lying
under a huge tree.
When I took a closer look,
I noticed he'd been impaled by a branch.
—was dead.
I was terrified, so I ran back
to my room at the lodge.
They decided that we were
going to stay for another night.
The police also came to see us
about the lightning and the fall.
They asked me
a lot of questions,
but I couldn't
tell them about—
I hardly slept that night.
Surely everyone would freak out if they found the body of—
Come morning, it was evident that no one had found out,
so I went back into the
forest to take a look.
But... it wasn't there.
It had vanished
without a trace.
I was baffled.
I went to ask everyone
what had happened to—
But they just looked
at me like I was crazy.
They said, "Who's that?" and,
"I don't know anyone named that."
They even said there were 19
students on the trip, not 20.
That's when it dawned on me.
The guy I killed must have
been the extra student.
I knew without
a doubt that I killed—
Nothing can change that fact.
That's why I decided
to come clean.
This is my confession.
It's been two weeks
since that trip,
and only I, the person involved
with his death, can still remember—
I get the feeling it's only
a matter of time, though.
That's why, while I
can still remember,
I want to tell you the truth,
and how you can
stop the calamity.
Are you listening?
Send them back to death,
where they belong.
Send the dead back to death.
That's how to stop the
calamity once it's begun.
I couldn't make out his name.
Does that mean
this has been altered?
Probably.
It must be real, then.
There's no reason
to alter a fake.
Well, we don't need the name.
What matters is how
we stop the calamity.
They say there's no way to
tell the dead from the living,
and that they don't
know they're dead.
Is there any way to tell?
There doesn't seem to be.
Mr. Matsunaga's case
was pure coincidence.
You don't think the extra student
is here, at this lodge, do you?
Say we do figure out who it is...
What do we do?
Are we supposed to... kill them?
Well—
Could you kill a classmate?
You know, I've been thinking
about who the extra person could be.
Do you have someone in mind?
Well, I...
I just think there must be
some way to tell who it is.
Keep inhaler
in bag when
not in use.
Maybe there is, and we
just don't know about it yet.
Exactly.
May I have a moment,
Ms. Mikami?
Since we're all together,
there's something I'd like to say.
Is that all right?
S-Sure.
Go ahead, Akazawa.
Since May, we've experienced
nothing but misfortune.
Just last month, even
Mr. Kubodera became a victim.
For starters, I'd like to apologize for my
incompetence as the head of countermeasures.
Additionally, though it remains unclear whether or not this trip leads us toward a resolution,
I sincerely believe that you, Misaki,
hold some of the responsibility for these disasters.
Why...
I believe if Misaki had upheld her
role as the nonexistent student properly,
then no one would have died.
Hold on!
What happened was unavoidable.
She couldn't do anything about it.
Is that so?
If she had avoided all
contact with Sakakibara,
then the countermeasure
would have been a success.
But—
I believe the person responsible
for its failure is Misaki.
Wouldn't you all agree?
What do you expect
her to do about it now?
Apologize.
We have yet to hear one
word of apology from her.
Yet, the moment you
were allowed to exist again,
you carried on as if
nothing had happened.
It's pointless.
Apologizing changes nothing.
If you believe so, then I shall.
Misaki, you have
nothing to apologize for.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
It's not!
Stop it!
This is stupid!
We just need to figure
out who the extra st—
Hey, Wakui, are you okay?
Are you in pain?
Hey!
Is this boy asthmatic?
Yes. He always carries this.
An inhaler?
Shouldn't he use this?
It's empty?
Do you have a spare?
Call an ambulance!
Ms. Mikami, call an ambulance now!
Um...
Our phones haven't been working
since yesterday. We can't make any calls.
We've arranged for repairs...
It's out of range.
Does anyone have service?
Call 119! Get an
ambulance over here!
It says there's an antenna
here, but I can't connect!
Mine won't work, either.
There's no service.
I'll drive him to the hospital.
Are you all right?
I'm not the one you
should be worried about.
Maybe we shouldn't go up
the mountain tomorrow.
Maybe not.
Sakakibara.
Yeah?
Thanks for earlier.
Huh?
You stood up for me
in the dining room.
Oh. It was nothing.
It wasn't just me, you know.
There was Mochizuki
and Teshigawara too.
Thank you.
Will you come see me later?
I have my own room.
And...
I want to see the photo.
Where was it?
In a detached room at our house.
My grandma found it.
I don't know why it
was in there, though.
Really?
My aunt Reiko uses that room.
With
everyone
in grade 9,
class 3
March 16,
With
everyone
in grade 9,
class 3
March 16,
With
everyone
in grade 9,
class 3
March 16,
With
everyone
in grade 9,
class 3
March 16,
With
everyone
in grade 9,
class 3
March 16,
With
everyone
in grade 9,
class 3
March 16,
With
everyone
in grade 9,
class 3
March 16,
With
everyone
in grade 9,
class 3
March 16,
With
everyone
in grade 9,
class 3
March 16,
Can you tell which one
Yomiyama Misaki is?
Well, I can see that one
person looks strange.
Strange? Like how?
Like...
He's kind of blurry, compared
to the others in the photo.
Distorted, somehow.
That's right.
What about the color?
Do you see any strange colors?
No, not really.
Thank you.
Are these other photos
also your mom's?
Yeah.
They really did look alike.
Who?
Your mother and your aunt.
You think so?
Their faces look the
same, even as kids.
Does Reiko paint at home?
Yeah.
She considers it her "real" job.
I see.
You were drawing something
too, weren't you? An angel?
Who was the model for that?
It was...
Your cousin Misaki?
Maybe.
When we first met,
at the hospital,
were you taking that
doll to your late cousin?
Did you think it was odd?
Well...
It's sort of complicated.
I don't really like
talking about it.
Could you tell me?
Sure.
Kirika, my mother's,
real name is Yukiyo,
and Misaki's mother's
name is Mitsuyo.
They're twins, almost identical.
When they grew up,
they both got married,
and Mitsuyo became a mother.
To your cousin Misaki?
And one other.
She had twins.
Twins?
One year later, Yukiyo
became pregnant too,
but she miscarried.
You mentioned that.
Yukiyo was heartbroken.
She almost had a break down.
To make matters worse,
the Fujioka household,
where the twins were born,
was in financial trouble.
The Misaki household,
on the other hand,
needed something to
soothe Yukiyo's heart.
It was a matter of
supply and demand.
You mean—?
I was given to her.
I think they gave me
to her, instead of Misaki,
because of my name.
Your name?
If the Misakis took
in a daughter named Misaki,
then her name would
be Misaki Misaki, right?
I've been raised as Yukiyo—as Kirika's only daughter for as long as I can remember.
I think I was in fifth
grade when I found out.
My grandmother
accidentally let it slip.
I'd never seen my
mother so flustered.
She probably planned on keeping it a secret for the rest of my life.
What happened
when you found out?
I wanted to meet Fujioka
Mitsuyo, my other mother.
I told Kirika that.
At first, she looked
incredibly sad,
but then she was furious.
She didn't want you to
meet your birth mother?
I guess not.
She doesn't involve
herself in my life much.
Except for—as I've
mentioned—certain things.
Right. I remember.
I think she's anxious.
It's probably the reason why
she has me carry a cell phone.
Though, during all that,
I was secretly
meeting with Misaki.
By then, she also knew
that we were twins.
We felt that we were connected,
whether we wanted to be or not.
She would sneak into
my house sometimes.
She said she liked my house because
it was filled with pretty dolls.
When I asked her what she
wanted for her birthday in April,
she said, "I want that doll."
Soon after starting ninth
grade though, she suddenly...
That's what you were doing?
I had made a promise with her.
So you weren't cousins.
You were sisters.
Yes.
That's why you told me,
"It may have already begun."
You remember that?
Yes.
Why didn't you
tell me back then?
I...
I just...
I didn't want to believe it.
I didn't want to believe
Misaki had died
because of some crazy curse.
That's why...
I could only
call her my cousin.
I didn't want to say it.
The Misaki who died in
April was the first victim.
In that case...
Everyone else seems to think
the calamity began in May, but...
The extra student was already in the
class before I transferred to Yomi North.
Is that why you're so
certain that I'm not dead?
Yes.
Because I wasn't in
the class back in April?
There's that, but it's
not the main reason.
What's your main reason?
It's...
This eye.
This doll's eye
tells me you're not.
Your left eye?
I think I told you that it lets me see
things that should remain unseen.
Yeah. What can it see?
The...
...color of death.
The color of things
close to death.
Color?
What color is that?
A color I've never seen
with my right eye.
It doesn't belong with
colors like red and blue.
It's unique.
And you can only see that
color in someone who's dead?
It's clearest in dead people,
and faint in those with
serious illnesses or injuries.
You mean, you can tell
when people are about to die?
You can't understand how I
can see these things, right?
Well...
I've had to accept it.
I've never even talked
to Misaki about this.
At some point,
I decided to keep this eye
covered for the rest of my life.
That's why I wanted to see
that photo from 26 years ago.
You could see the color of
death in Yomiyama Misaki?
Yes.
It's the first time I've ever seen
that color so clearly in a photo.
I don't see the
color of death in you.
That's how I
know it's not you.
You're not the extra.
And you know it's not
you for the same reason?
Does that mean you already
know who the extra person is?
I try to keep my
eye patch on at school.
But you wrote
"Who is dead?" on your desk.
I didn't think finding out
would change anything.
I did wonder, though, so...
What about now?
Is the dead person
here with us?
The extra person...
...is here.
Who is it?
It's...
Sakaki!
I think I fucked up!
Tragedy