No... I can't do that!
Just do it!
Don't rush it!
Azure
All right!
He stopped it?
He stopped the
calamity 15 years ago?
That's what he says,
but he doesn't seem to
remember any details.
Reiko, do you remember
Mr. Matsunaga?
Of course. We were
in the same club.
Really?
Did he ever...
say how he stopped it?
I don't remember
hearing anything about it.
You went on a class trip during summer that year, didn't you?
Yeah.
We didn't think it was
a good idea to stay home.
What happened on that trip?
I'm sure something happened...
but I can't seem to remember what.
I see.
Sorry. I know I'm no help.
Don't worry.
I'm fine. You don't
need to go overboard.
So, Mr. Matsunaga
went on the trip too?
I think so...
Yeah. He did.
Was he acting strange?
I don't think so.
I guess our only
option is to ask him.
All right. I'll run it
by Matsu for you.
I'll tag along when
you go talk to him.
Morning!
Good morning!
Good morning.
What's with all that stuff?
I stocked up on supplies!
Sorry I'm late.
Are you okay?
You don't look so good.
I'm fine. I'm just a bit carsic—
He's a tough one.
You're coming as well, Akazawa?
Of course I am.
Why don't you ride in this car?
Yours doesn't look like
it can fit four people.
Don't worry.
This car runs better
than you'd think.
That was unnecessary.
I see.
All right, Teshigawara.
You're riding with me.
O-Okay.
Nakao, you're sitting in the
front since you get carsick.
Fine.
Okay. Let's go.
So, Mr. Matsunaga won't be
returning to Yomiyama for a while?
I spoke with his mother,
and she said he's living at the resort hotel where he works.
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
A
City of Yomiyama
Please Come Again!
We safely made it
out of Yomiyama.
Yeah.
All right, let's get going.
Um, Reiko?
What?
Uh, never mind...
Sheesh. If you're going to drive that slow, then get out of the fast lane.
I guess you can't judge
a book by its cover.
I think you're pretty easy to read.
Yeah?
Describe me, then.
Eh? Well...
Strong and dependable, I guess?
You think I'm that macho?
Well, you're tough, and you've
got a strong sense of responsibility.
Stuff like that.
You should at least say,
"That's not what I meant."
That's not what I meant.
What the hell? You're annoying.
I've gotta get back
at you every so often.
Oh, yeah. You're the head
of countermeasures, right?
How do you get picked for that?
It's usually chosen by the teacher.
It's not a very popular job.
You could say that they're responsible for the lives of everyone in the class.
So, you were appointed?
I nominated myself.
Why?
Perhaps nobody else
believed in the calamity,
but I was different.
I can't let a senseless
phenomenon exist.
That's why I'm going
to put an end to it.
It's hot as hell.
Matsunaga was called to
a reception, apparently.
I left my cell number with them,
so he should call
when he gets back, but...
What should we do until then?
No point sittin' around
doing nothing, right?
Yeah. We came all
this way, after all.
We're outside of Yomiyama,
so the calamity shouldn't affect us.
Right! Let's go swimming!
We are near the ocean.
All right!
I don't have my swimsuit
with me, though!
You can get some
at the hotel, right?
They're not expensive.
I'll even buy you a pair.
But... I'd feel bad.
If you're not going
to swim, then I won't.
Well, I thought this
might happen, so...
Eh? Don't tell me...
I knew you guys
brought too much stuff.
Well, we are near the ocean.
Not to mention we're
outside of Yomiyama.
It's also summer break.
It'd be depressing to sit inside all day.
We need to have some fun.
It's the ocean!
The summer ocean!
It's mine!
All right!
Misaki?
Sakakibara...?
My glasses! I can't see
without my glasses!
You'll pay for that!
Ready, and... dunk!
Hey, is your family's
summer house nearby?
Yes.
What does your dad do?
I'm not too sure.
He's rarely ever in Japan.
That's why, on the occasions he's actually
home, we put on these little family facades.
We might be family, but it
doesn't feel like we're related.
Not that I care.
Hey, if we found out who
the dead person is after this,
would making them
nonexistent stop the calamity?
I don't think that would work.
It's already been triggered.
I think it's too late
to try balancing it out.
They connected?
I guess so.
It's not so bad to connect
every now and then, right?
I suppose so.
Anyone up for lunch?
Yes!
Hey, wait!
Should we go back to the hotel?
I'm fine with going
to a convenience store.
There are shops along the coast.
Hold it, you three!
We're at the beach!
We should make the most
out of an outdoor life!
You want to cook here?
All right, Akazawa!
I knew you'd understand!
Huh?
How do you expect us
to cook without any tools?
I've got it covered!
Feast your eyes on
this flawless setup!
You're such an idiot.
So this is what you were carrying?
Are you going to cook?
Huh? Cook?
With what ingredients?
Duh! We'll get that locally!
You're such an idiot.
With all the stuff you
brought, I should've known...
I'm hungry.
Locally?
Mochizuki! You brought
the fishing gear, right?
Y-Yeah!
All right. Let's see who can
gather the most ingredients!
What are the prizes?
Whoever loses has to cook the food,
and whoever wins gets to eat it.
How's that?
Sounds interesting.
It's settled!
All right. I'll pick the teams.
First off, on the Head of
Countermeasures Team will be...
Akazawa!
Sugiura!
Naka— Actually, never mind him.
And me!
Now, on the Nonexistent Team will be...
Sakakibara!
Misaki!
Mochizuki!
But I exist—!
Yeah, but you don't
exist over here.
That's cruel.
So we're competing based on the number of fish we catch?
No. If you find
anything else, it counts.
Let me out!
That's sea lettuce. It tastes awful.
That's red algae.
You can't eat it by itself.
Got one!
It's a big one!
All right!
What is this?
It's kelp.
You're supposed to catch fish!
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Get it off...
I thought it was going to eat me.
Octopuses don't eat people.
They'll bite if you
poke at them, though.
What's up?
I think I've got a big one...
It's pulling pretty hard.
All right!
That's your big one?
At least it's a fish.
Cute.
I've got one!
Hey.
You're doing this
on purpose, aren't yo—
What is this?!
A sea cucumber?
Actually, I'm impressed
that you even caught one.
Maybe it just got caught on the line.
You creep! Useless jerk!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
A blowfish, an octopus,
and a starfish.
This is kelp, right?
And a sea cucumber, and...
What's in this shell?
A hermit crab...
I guess that's that.
The battle ends with a draw.
I picked up some
meat and vegetables,
so let's cook that.
Okay!
Fresh seafood is the best!
The crunch is so delicious.
We can't eat these guys.
Got it!
Reiko?
I tried calling your cell.
Is your battery dead?
Huh?
Oops...
Careless as ever, I see.
I'm surprised you found us.
It wasn't hard to figure out.
This is the closest
beach to the hotel.
I see.
But wow,
girls sure do change.
You used to be such a shrimp.
You've changed a bit, yourself.
You're an old geezer now.
Oh, shut it!
It's been 15 years, huh?
Technically, it's only been
14 years since our graduation.
Oh.
That makes us around 30, doesn't it?
Shut it.
Hey...
Haven't I seen you
around recently?
Where?
I don't remember seeing you.
It was probably someone else.
I don't think it was.
Maybe at Kentarou or
Natsuko's memorial service?
No, I only went to their funerals.
Oh.
I can't believe it's been
15 years since they died.
Who're the kids?
This year's class 3 students.
I see.
They're here to find out about what happened 15 years ago?
I can only remember bits and pieces about that summer.
Matsu, I heard that you
stopped the calamity.
Tomoka over at Inoya
asked me the same thing.
I can't remember a
damn thing, though.
Do you remember the class
trip we took that summer?
Yeah.
An accident happened
during it, right?
Do you remember anything about it?
Who are you?
Akazawa, the head
of countermeasures.
I see.
Truth be told,
I don't remember much.
I know that someone died
up on the mountain, but...
I can't remember either.
I can't even remember
what kind of accident it was.
Was the accident before or
after your visit to the shrine?
Why does that matter?
Well, if it was before,
then perhaps a blessing from
the shrine stopped the calamity.
I can't remember.
But I have a feeling that it was a
run-down, abandoned-looking shrine.
Yeah. The shrine...
I'm pretty sure we went to the shrine.
We all held hands and...
Crap. I can't remember a thing.
Um, Mr. Matsunaga,
didn't you leave something
behind, as a clue for the others?
Evidently I did, but...
What did you want to tell them?
All I can remember is having
this urgent need to tell them, but...
You can't remember
what it was about?
And you don't remember
what you left behind, or where?
Like, was it a note, or?
No... No, it wasn't paper... It was...
Yes?
I think I used something...
That's right! It's at the school!
I took something to the school!
The school?
Where in the school?
I got it!
How far out are you gonna go?
What is he doing?
This doesn't look good.
What the...?
Quit messing around, man!
Shit!
Why...?
I...
I protected them...
I left it for them...
...in the classroom.
Link