Crap! Let's run!
No!
I don't want to die!
This isn't normal.
The Dead
Why?
Has everyone lost their minds?
Mr. Chibiki!
No one else escaped?
Ow...
The bleeding has stopped.
It's nothing serious.
You three stay here.
All right?
Matsui!
Hel—
Hey, Sakakibara.
Do you remember this girl?
Of course I do!
Damn. Guess she wasn't it.
You guess? What the hell?
Sugiura already said
that it was Misaki,
but you know, I think
you're the dead person.
It all started this May, didn't it?
Logically, whoever joined the class during May is the dead person.
No! This all started in April!
You think I'm going
to fall for that shit?
Why... are you doing this?
I figured it out when
Teshigawara tried to kill me.
If I don't send the dead
back to death, I'll die.
Still—
Shut the fuck up!
If you hadn't transferred,
then Yukari wouldn't have died!
Sakuragi?
If only you hadn't talked
to that nonexistent girl...
Send the dead back to—
You idiot. Kouichi isn't dead.
You've killed two people, though.
You don't deserve to live.
I'll help you die.
Keep Yukari company.
Classmates shouldn't do something as stupid as killing one another.
Big talk there,
but someone who ran to the sidelines
because he was afraid of death,
has no right to say anything!
While it's true I ran away,
I can still save a student who's about to die for no reason.
A spectator like you
can't do anything!
You can't change anything!
The only ones who can fix this
are those living in death's jaws!
Get outside, Sakakibara!
Kazami?
Hey, Kazami!
Hey...
C'mon, cut it out.
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
Misaki's still here.
Misaki! If you're here,
say something!
Stop it!
Please, stop!
We're all going to die if I don't!
Even you could die—
No! Misaki's not dead!
If the calamity doesn't
cease after killing her,
then I'll believe you!
This is finally over.
You're wrong...
Why? I'm just...
I'm just trying to protect everyone! Why are you doing this?
If you really have a death wish,
then I'll just kill you too.
Big brother...
You idiot!
Ouch!
I'm sorry! Are you all right?
Are you okay?
You're not from Yomi North.
No, I'm from Tokyo.
I see.
Are you hurt?
No...
Someone I loved just died.
I see.
I guess...
...we're the same.
A year and a half ago,
I hit you with an empty can.
Do you remember?
Goodness. You're the worst.
Even if you don't, you're
supposed to say you remember.
Akazawa...
Misaki!
August 9 (Sun.)
Yes! I've got a signal!
Redial
Mei Misaki
Please connect!
Sakakibara?
Misaki! Are you okay?
Yes.
Where are you?
In the back yard.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I can't move, though.
I'm on my way. Just—
Don't.
Why?
You don't want to
come here, Sakakibara.
Why?!
I...
I have to stop it.
No way... Misaki, who is it?
You'll regret coming.
So...
Misaki!
Stay back.
We have to help!
We can't.
I... I can see the color of death.
Did... you figure it out just now?
I've known it for a while,
but I couldn't tell you.
Still...
Still... I have to stop it.
Wait!
No...
No way... No way!
It can't be!
She's... the extra person?
Are you sure?
Are you... really sure?
Ms. Mikami...
Reiko is the extra?
Kouichi.
Now, the fourth thing you need to know to prepare yourself for Yomi North is...
Keep my work and
personal life separate.
Try not to call me
Reiko mistakenly.
Remember that, during school,
I'm Ms. Mikami—the assistant homeroom teacher.
All right?
Is there another assistant
homeroom teacher in our school?
That's...
They don't.
Ninth grade's class 3 is the only one.
This year, our classroom had the correct number of desks,
and yet the calamity
began in April.
Why do you think that is?
Because the room
that was short one desk...
...was the faculty room.
No!
That's not true!
Sakakibara. Step aside.
I'll... I'll do it.
I'll send the dead back to death.
Kouichi...
I'm sorry, Reiko.
Don't!
Don't do this!
Is this okay?
Is this really okay?
Is this the right choice?
No mistaking it?
If we're wrong, then
I'll have murdered Reiko.
Is Misaki telling the truth?
Can I trust her?
I remembered that I saw it.
I was watching.
I saw Ms. Mikami being
murdered a year and a half ago!
Cheer! Cheer up!
Why? Why, Rei?
Certificate
of Excellence
Presented to
Reiko Mikami
It was about a year and a half ago.
It was at the pet shop.
How does it feel to be back in
Yomiyama after a year and a half?
A year and a half ago,
I hit you with an empty can.
Do you remember?
Mikami
A funeral always
follows one's death.
I'm so tired of
funerals... So very tired.
My poor Ritsuko and Reiko...
Trust me.
Reiko...
Goodbye, Reiko.
Goodbye, Mom.
Mikami
Family Grave
You're here too?
How are your lungs holding up?
Fine, I suppose.
I don't think I can participate
during gym, though.
Tombstone
29.10. Reiko
27.7. Ritsuko
No one else remembers Ms. Mikami.
We're the only ones?
She was probably worried about you becoming the ninth victim.
So eight people died?
Technically, there were
ten victims in August.
Who were the other two?
The manager and his wife.
They were Takabayashi's
maternal grandparents.
I'm told they were emotionally
broken since his death.
Ms. Mikami died during fall,
a year and a half ago.
She was stabbed by an
unknown assailant near the river.
I can't really remember, but...
Apparently Ms. Mikami was
the dead person this year?
That means there
were seven deaths
in the calamity two years ago.
Homeroom: Reiko Mikami
October 29,
murdered
Yes. There were seven "X" marks.
I saw the name "Akazawa"
on the file from that year.
Was that...
Yes, he was Akazawa's cousin,
but they were raised
more like siblings.
Do you two want a ride?
No, we'll be fine.
All right, then.
Be careful going home.
Wait...
I guess the calamity
is over now, huh?
When did you figure out that Reiko— that Ms. Mikami was the extra?
I wonder...
Dunno.
Why didn't you say anything?
Nothing good
would've come from it.
There was no way
I could tell you.
Ms. Mikami was special
to you, wasn't she?
Sorry. I mean, Reiko.
Want to go check out
that amusement park?
Huh?
The Ferris wheel.
I don't ride those.
Oh?
I tried to call your cell from
the hospital the other day,
but I couldn't connect.
Well...
I threw it in the
river after that day.
Why?
I hate those devices.
We don't always need to
be connected through them.
She's probably going to
give me another one, though.
If she does,
mind if I call you sometimes?
Sure.
Oh, yeah.
Mochizuki gave these to me.
You can see Reiko in them, right?
Yeah.
No one else could.
Even Mochizuki didn't
realize she was there.
Really?
What about the color?
What color is Reiko?
I can see the color of death.
I wonder if we
too will forget this.
The trip, what's
happened since April,
and everything that had
to do with Mikami Reiko.
Everything...
You don't want to forget?
You want to remember it forever?
It's all over, huh?
iroaseteku firumu no you ni
Just as the colors fade from old film
tashika na ima mo izure kasunde
the things I feel in the present fade from memory sooner or later
nande mo naku waraiatta setsuna no jikan to hikari
as will the short-lived times of happiness and innocence we enjoyed
tsunagatteyuku kioku no soko ni
I believe that the memories we have in common
dareka ga mitsukeru tame aru to shinjiteru
harbor the potential for finding love again deep within
ima demo
Even now I believe that
...and that's how you
stop the calamity.
To: The Students
of Grade 9, Class 3
Take it however you please.
To: The Students
of Grade 9, Class 3
Just make sure to consider
your actions carefully.
Think it over and discuss it
with everyone around you.
That way, there are no regrets.