What?!
Scattering
Mizuno Sanae, was it?
She and Kouchi often talked
about books together.
She was so young...
Hopefully her brothers will be okay.
Oh, she had brothers?
One of them is Takeru.
He's in my class.
Dear me, this is awful.
Didn't a girl in your class
recently die in an accident, too?
A funeral always
follows one's death.
I'm so tired of funerals... So very tired.
I'm so very tired of funerals...
June 4
(Thurs.)
I know how much of a shock it is to hear about Mizuno's sister,
but it'll be all right.
We can get through this
if we all stick together.
Hey.
She died.
Mizuno's sister died in
an accident yesterday.
I see.
Self-Study
Sketching
I wonder if Ms. Mikami is okay.
She might be sick.
She didn't look too good.
I hope she doesn't...
Hey, Sakakibara?
Yeah?
You don't think Ms. Mikami has some
serious, life-threatening illness, do you?
I'm sure she's fine.
You're probably right.
Are you that worried?
Well, after what
happened to Sakuragi...
And now with Mizuno's sister...
So...
Do you think there's some
connection between those accidents?
I-I don't...
Where are you going?
To do some research.
Yomiyama Prefectural Junior High School
Class of 1972
I see.
Of course I wouldn't
find Misaki's name here.
Mom...
Did you find her?
Yes.
Interesting. So she
graduated back in '72.
Which class was she in?
Class 3, just like me.
Oh? Which one is your mother?
This one.
Ritsuko...?
You know her?
Somewhat.
Ritsuko was...
But I heard she died.
When did that happen?
15 years ago.
Right after having me.
15 years ago?
I see. So that's what happened.
Kouichi.
Mr. Kubodera asked me to
send you to the faculty room.
I see. Thanks.
Allow me to apologize in advance.
I'm sorry, but this is for all of us.
So, forgive us.
You're aware that Mizuno Sanae died in an accident at the hospital yesterday, correct?
Yes, I do.
Excuse me, but am I being
suspected of something?
No, no. We know
it was an accident.
A very unfortunate accident.
But we found Ms. Mizuno's
cell phone in that elevator.
Were you speaking with her at around one o'clock yesterday?
Yes, I was.
She was on the roof
at the time, correct?
And then she went
into the elevator...
What caused the accident?
That's what we're investigating.
All we know is that the sheaves holding the cables in place came loose, causing it to fall.
That building is
several decades old,
and it's been through numerous
structural modifications.
At any rate, let's be careful.
Especially where unusual
accidents are concerned.
Ayano
Aya
Akazawa
Izumi
Sakakibara.
Are the police finished
questioning you?
Yes.
I see.
You're dismissed
for the day, then.
Um, where is everyone?
The new female class officer
was selected during homeroom.
It's Akazawa.
Where did everyone go, though?
Please be sure to uphold
the class rules at all times.
Do I make myself clear?
Who is
dead?aa
Yeah, sure.
Hey.
Wanna walk home together?
Where did everyone go
during sixth period?
We went to the meeting room to take care of some stuff.
What sort of stuff?
You've witnessed some strange occurrences since you've come here, haven't you?
If you know what's going on,
can you at least tell me?
Sorry, I can't.
All I can say is that something very
unpleasant might happen to you soon.
What?
During that meeting,
Akazawa said we needed
to discuss something,
without you there.
Even if you don't like what
happens, just try to deal with it.
Remember that you're
doing it for all of us.
So, please.
"All of us"?
...but this is for all of us.
So, forgive us.
Is this one of those class rules?
Yeah.
I don't get it...
Can I ask for one favor?
What is it?
I'd like a copy of the class roster.
You didn't get one?
It's just not fair.
I don't agree with how
Akazawa is handling this.
It's not fair to force her
ideas down our throats.
There must be a lot you
want to know, Sakakibara.
Yeah.
Feel free to ask me, then.
I'll tell you everything I know.
Wait, Takabayashi!
Are you serious?
Okay.
Does Misaki Mei exist?
Misaki Mei is...
Takabayashi! Takabayashi!
Good morning. You're early today.
June 5
(Fri.)
That's that, then.
Are there any other...
No, forget it.
Did something
happen this morning?
Let us pray so that Takabayashi's soul may rest in peace.
There have been many
depressing events as of late,
but do not lose heart,
and do not give up.
We will get through
all this together.
Remember to uphold the
class rules at all times.
Ms. Mikami is in a difficult position,
but she has agreed to cooperate
to the best of her ability.
Does everyone understand?
Hey.
What's with him?
Hey, Wakui?
What's going on?
The person you are
trying to reach currently
has their phone off or is
out of the service area.
Yo.
Hey...
Sorry.
Figures of Speech
Simile
Metaphor
Personification
"A rumor walks alone."
We see something that is not human being expressed with human-like behaviors.
This is known as personification.
Please note that these human-like behaviors are
being expressed by something that is not human.
Pascal once said, "Man is but a
reed, but he is a thinking reed."
This is not personification.
So that's what they meant.
It is a metaphor.
Does that make sense?
Hi.
What's wrong?
Your call was unexpected.
Sorry. Ask Misaki
to explain. -Mochizuki
Misaki Mei
So, you got a copy
of the class roster.
And?
Let me start from the beginning.
Did you hear that
Takabayashi died?
He had a heart attack.
I know he had
heart problems, but...
I see.
The second June death
was caused by illness.
And when I got to school today,
the whole class was acting weird.
They acted as if I wasn't there.
So that's what they
decided to do...
Does this mean I'm
just like you now?
How does it feel to not exist?
Not so great.
But in a way, it's a
load off my mind.
It is?
Because now I
know that you exist.
This is where you live, isn't it?
Yes.
But I thought you
already figured this out.
You did say you
lived around here.
And you're not a customer.
Was that your mother
who answered the phone?
She was surprised.
I very rarely get calls
from schoolmates.
Is Kirika your mom?
Yes. I guess you'd
call it a pseudonym.
She goes by Kirika.
She's a strange woman who isolates herself in the studio upstairs.
So the "M" in "Studio M"
stands for Misaki?
It all makes sense
now, doesn't it?
Let's go upstairs.
Did you know this was here?
Here you go.
Why don't you ask the questions?
It might be easier to
explain everything that way.
I thought you hated
being questioned.
I do, but for today...
I'll make a special exception.
First off, Misaki Mei...
...you exist, right?
Did you think I was a ghost?
Sort of.
I guess you couldn't help it.
But your doubts are
gone now, right?
Now that you know I
exist as a living human.
I'm only nonexistent
to the others in class 3.
Since when?
It started on May 1st.
That's pretty recent.
A lot of things seemed strange to you from the start, right?
And nobody would tell me why.
Not explaining the situation to you in the first place was a mistake.
How so?
You were supposed to treat me
as someone who didn't exist,
just like the rest of the class.
But now, you're the same as me.
How awful for you.
So they weren't bullying you?
I don't think anyone
thought of it like that.
I know that I no
longer exist to them,
but why are they doing this?
That's the question.
Do you remember the story about the Misaki who died 26 years ago?
Yeah.
That was the trigger.
After that, class 3
drew closer to death.
Death?
It happened to class 3 the year after Misaki's class graduated.
And, once it happens, once it begins,
somebody dies each month.
Either a student, or
someone from their family.
What is "it"?
It's when...
...the number of students
in the class increases by one.
Increases? So who is it?
Nobody knows.
They can never figure out
who the extra one is.
The extra one?
25 years ago, shortly after the new term began,
they realized that they were short one desk and chair.
Even though they had prepared enough for every student.
Couldn't they just check
the school records?
It was useless.
They tried many times.
The roster and records had
been altered to be inconsistent.
They were just one
desk and chair short.
So, someone rewrote the numbers?
I used the word
"altered" figuratively.
They say that everyone's
memories had changed as well.
Huh?
Sounds impossible, doesn't it?
But it's supposedly true.
I was told this type of
phenomenon could happen.
Phenomenon?
At first, they thought it was just an error and ignored it.
But starting in April, people connected to the class started to die each month.
Each month?
For the whole year?
That year, I think it was six
students and ten family members.
Clearly abnormal, right?
This phenomenon has
continued in class 3 ever since.
So a ninth grader in class 3,
named Misaki, died 26 years ago.
And the following year, there was an extra student in the class somehow.
After which, people connected to
the class started to die each month.
Why do people die when
there's an extra student?
Nobody knows the reason.
That's just what happens.
Plus, that extra student is...
...someone dead.
You mean the Misaki
who died 26 years ago?
Who is
dead?aa
Is it... a ghost, or something?
I think it's different from
what we'd call a ghost.
It seems to have a physical body.
There's no way to tell it
apart from the rest of us.
No way to tell?
That dead person has
a soul and its memories,
and they don't
realize they're dead.
Who are they?
The people connected to the class
who have died over the years.
This is how I see it.
Because of what class 3 did 26 years ago,
the class is now a place that invites the dead.
After that, the dead began to join the class and drew class 3 closer to death.
In response,
the students in class 3 came up with several "countermeasures" to try to escape this calamity.
Like exorcisms?
Possibly.
They tried moving to
a different classroom,
and changing the name
of class 3 to class C.
But that didn't stop it.
So the problem is with the students in the ninth grade's third class?
Seems to be.
Then, about ten years ago,
they found a way to
deal with the problem.
A method that prevented
people from dying each month.
Don't tell me...
They treat one student like they don't exist, to make up for the extra person.
That way, they return the
class to its correct number,
and they can avoid the
calamity for that year.
It's sort of like a charm.
The Two