Have you heard of Misaki?
She was in the ninth grade, class 3.
Was there someone
named Misaki in class 3?
It happened 26 years ago.
She'd been popular
since the seventh grade.
She was smart, pretty,
and had a great personality.
Both the teachers and
students adored her.
There's always someone
like that in every grade.
But shortly after
starting the ninth grade,
Misaki died.
How?
I heard it was an accident.
Of course, everyone
was completely shocked.
Until someone said it.
Said what?
He pointed to
Misaki's desk and said,
"Misaki's not dead.
She's right there."
And that was...?
Well, it was just an act.
But since then, class 3 continued
to act as if Misaki was still alive.
That's kinda creepy.
They continued the
act until graduation.
Do Not Enter
The principal even arranged to have Misaki's
seat included in their graduation ceremony.
Isn't that a good thing?
If that were the end.
There's more?
The rest of the story is...
Rough Sketch
How are you feeling?
Does it still hurt?
I'm fine.
My, what a way to
start your life here.
You poor thing.
Um...
I'm sorry, Grandma.
Goodness, no.
Don't you worry about that.
You couldn't help it.
Um, does my father know?
I haven't told him.
Yousuke is in India
right now, isn't he?
Want me to tell him?
I have his number.
No, thank you.
I'll call him myself.
That's probably best.
That Yousuke,
he's such a dutiful man.
In all this time
since Ritsuko died...
That's the Yomiyama River flowing
through the center of the town.
Can you see the
grounds beyond it?
Um...
You mean that building?
Yes.
That's the school
you'll be attending.
Is that the same school
you went to, Reiko?
Yep. That was
14 years ago, though.
So my mother went there, too?
That's right.
My sister, Ritsuko,
went to Yomi North, too.
Yomi North?
Yomiyama North Junior High.
Oh.
Public schools and
private schools differ a bit,
but it just takes
some getting used to.
I'm sure you'll get
used to it in no time.
I hope so.
You'll be fine.
Once you're out of the hospital,
I'll help you prepare
for life at Yomi North.
Oh! Now you're reading a novel by
Stephen King, mister horror lover?
Well, I'll leave you guys alone.
We're ninth grade students in class 3
of Yomiyama North Junior High.
I see.
I'm Kazami. Kazami Tomohiko.
This is Sakuragi.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Sakuragi Yukari.
And this is—
Akazawa Izumi.
Did you want something?
Oh, yes.
Sakuragi and I are class officers.
Akazawa is in charge
of countermeasures.
We're here today as
representatives of class 3.
Countermeasures?
You just transferred here, right?
We heard you were starting school on Monday, but that you suddenly fell ill.
So we decided to visit you
on behalf of the entire class.
Here. These are from all of us.
You're from Tokyo, right?
Yeah.
And you attended
a private school there?
Why did you transfer?
For family reasons.
Is this your first time
living in Yomiyama?
Yes.
Oh. I figured that
you used to live here.
I've visited before,
but I've never lived here.
How long did you visit for?
I can't say.
I don't remember.
I was still young,
so... maybe a while?
Here.
I've copied the notes from
the start of the first term.
Thank you!
I think my first day will
be after Golden Week,
so I'll see you then.
Um, Sakakibara?
Yes?
Well...
Sakakiba—
Your first name's Kouichi, right?
May we call you Kouichi?
Sure.
We look forward to getting
to know you, Kouichi.
Same here. Thanks.
Are you sure you haven't lived
in Yomiyama before, Kouichi?
I don't think so.
Dad
P-Pardon me.
Are you a student at Yomi North?
Do you have something to do
on the second basement level?
Yes.
But the second basement level is...
I'm delivering something.
My poor other half...
...is waiting for me there.
Hey, wait up.
What's your name?
Mei.
Misaki Mei.
Mechanical Room - Boiler Room
Morgue
Good morning, Rei!
How are you?
Good morning!
Good morning! How you doing?
Good morning.
It's two in the morning over here.
India's hot as hell!
What's up?
You start school today, don't you?
I'm calling to wish you
good luck. Be grateful!
Oh, sure.
How you feeling?
How're things since you
got out of the hospital?
Can you hear me, Kouichi? I wanted to say—
Hang on. The signal's bad over here.
I'm feeling better.
You don't have to worry.
Yeah, pneumothorax
isn't the end of the world.
I had one when I was a kid.
Really? I didn't know that.
I never told you.
I didn't want anyone
telling you it's hereditary.
Is it?
I actually had it twice,
but never again after that.
So if it's hereditary,
you're all done.
I sure hope so.
Just think of it as
something that's in the past,
and go enjoy your life.
I won't let it bother me.
Thatta boy! Remember to tell
your grandparents that I said hi!
Man, India is seriously hot!
Good morning, Rei!
Good morning!
Rei is your name, you know.
Cheer— Cheer up!
Sure. Thanks.
Moving along.
The third thing you need to know
to prepare yourself for Yomi North is:
Always uphold the class rules.
Okay.
Things might be
different in Tokyo,
but here in Yomiyama, the group
matters more than the individual.
I think I can handle that.
Good.
Now, the fourth thing
you need to know is—
Kouichi!
Breakfast is ready!
She said, "Breakfast is ready", Kouichi.
Good morning, Grandpa.
Good morning.
Are you going back
to the hospital today?
No, I've been discharged.
I start school today.
Ah, school.
You're already in
junior high, aren't you?
Yes, yes.
Must be good to be young.
I'm in the ninth grade now.
I'll be in high school next year.
If only that hadn't
happened to Ritsuko...
Kouichi! Go eat your breakfast.
Coming!
Why, Rei? Why?
I hope you'll be able to
get along with everyone.
If you have any troubles at all,
please don't hesitate to talk to me.
You can also talk to Ms. Mikami,
the assistant homeroom teacher.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
We look forward to
having you with us.
May 6 (Wed.)
Kouichi Sakakibara
I moved here because
of my father's job.
I'm living with my grandparents.
And, um... it's nice to meet you.
Please give our new
friend a warm welcome.
Help out each other,
and work hard together,
so that you can all graduate
in prime health next March.
You can take that seat
over there, Sakakibara.
Yes, sir.
Are you better now?
Yes, I feel much better.
How does this town
compare to Tokyo?
It's not that different.
But Tokyo sounds so great!
Rural areas like Yomiyama have
nothing going for them these days.
That's for sure.
Nothing interesting
happens here.
Tokyo has its downsides, too.
It's so noisy, you can't relax.
I guess it might seem that
way, if you've lived there.
You think so?
I'd love to live in Tokyo!
I like it better here.
It's much quieter.
You're surrounded by nature, too.
That's something you'd
only hear from a Tokyoite.
I heard your dad is
a college professor.
And that he's currently doing
research in a foreign country.
How did you know that?
Everyone knows.
Mr. Kubodera told us.
I see. Did he mention
my old school, too?
Pretty much everyone knows.
Ms. Mikami talked to us, too.
I see.
Sucks that Ms. Mikami
isn't our homeroom teacher.
She's beautiful, and she has a hot body!
Well, um...
Oh? You're not into
pretty women, Kouichi?
It's not that.
What kind of girls are
you into, Sakakibara?
Give me a break.
By the way, what country
is your dad in now?
India.
Spring marks his first year there.
India, huh?
I bet it's hot there.
I wouldn't be able to
do it. I hate the heat.
Consider yourself lucky, Teshy.
No matter how hard you try, you're never gonna do research in a place like India.
Yeah, yeah! I'm well aware.
What's wrong?
Is something bothering you?
No, nothing.
But I was wondering about
the other girl who visited me.
Akazawa, was it?
Is she absent today?
Yeah, looks like it.
Hey! Why don't we give you a
tour of the school during lunch?
It's tough not knowing
where stuff is, right?
Good idea. Let's do it.
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
Ready!
You look like you want to run.
Yeah. I love running.
Yeah?
So, you've run before.
Um, yeah.
I hear you have
a heart condition.
I was born with it,
so I don't know what
it feels like to run.
I wish I could run
with all my strength.
You might be able to someday.
Yeah, you're right.
Maybe someday.
I'm gonna...
...go to the nurse's
office to lie down.
Are you okay?
It happens all the time.
I can get there by myself.
Sakakibara?
Where did Takabayashi go?
To rest in the nurse's office.
Oh...
I fell yesterday and
sprained my ankle.
We don't have gym
with another class?
Only class 3 is different.
Classes 1 and 2, and classes
4 and 5, have gym together.
You walked around during lunch with
Kazami, Teshigawara, and the others, right?
Yeah.
Did they say anything to you?
They just gave me
a tour of the school.
That's all?
Yeah.
I see...
If we're not careful,
Akazawa will yell at us.
Hey, Sakuragi?
Yes?
I've been wondering...
Where's Misaki?
The girl named Misaki Mei.
You know, the one wearing
an eyepatch on her left eye.
I didn't see her in
the classroom at lunch.
Sakakibara?
Hey, Misaki.
You're watching gym class, too?
Are you allowed to be up here?
I don't know.
But there's no point in
watching from up close.
And you? Are you
allowed up here?
I don't know.
Were you drawing something?
How do you write "Mei"?
With the character
that means "cry".
The same character used
in "resonate" and "scream".
I see.
So, do you remember meeting me
at Yomiyama Hospital the other day?
In the elevator.
You got off at the
second basement level.
Did that happen?
What did you go to the
second basement level for?
You said you were
delivering something.
You were holding
some kind of white doll.
Is that what you were deliver—
Might be. I hate being questioned.
Oh, sorry.
I wasn't trying to
force you to tell me.
I just, well...
Something very sad
happened that day.
You are Sakakibara Kouichi, correct?
Yes.
Your classmates
haven't told you yet?
Told me what?
They associate
your name with death.
But not just any death.
A cruel, irrational death
that took place at this school.
This school is in a
place close to death,
especially the
ninth grade's class 3.
It's much, much closer to it
than any of the other classes.
To... death?
You really don't know
anything, Sakakibara?
Nothing at all?
Nobody has told you?
About what?
You'll find out soon enough.
You shouldn't try
to get close to me.
You shouldn't talk
to me anymore, either.
Why?
You'll find out soon enough.
But...
Good-bye,
Sa-ka-ki-ba-ra.
Are you getting along
with your classmates?
I suppose so.
Is something wrong?
No, nothing.
Speculation