Long time no see!
Yes.
Here's a get-well gift.
They're beautiful!
And you remembered
my favorite flowers!
I'm sorry to call you
.here so suddenly.
Won't you sit?
I read in the paper that the choir club took first place in nationals again this year.
It's not called the
.choir club anymore.
It's the choral group.
mune no oku ga takanaru atsui koe ni kizuitara
Once my heart knows of its burning voice
sutaatorain wa kimi no me no mae ni aru
it will carry what I do, and you will know too
mada mienai michi demo hashirihajimereba ii sa
Just run along your path, even if you can't see it
akirameru yori mo suteki da to omowanai
I don't think you should give up so easily
itsumo fuan wa sugu soba de
Anxiety is always nearby
kakedasu omoi wo shimetsukeru keredo
keeping a hold on your bold courage
ima wo koete arukidasu michi naru michi ni hikari wo
Get beyond the present and shed a light on your path
hajimete wo kurikaeshi tsukamitore ashita wo
Find the tomorrow that you dream of
sou sa bokutachi wa mugen no yume dakishime susumu no sa
We will embrace our countless dreams and walk onwards
kagayaiteru jibun wo shinjitai
A
t
J
I want to believe in myself
tachiageru chikara ni saidai no ai wo komete
Let us put love into our strength to stand up
omou mama tabidatou
t
A
C
Let us be happy
atarashii sekai no naka he
r
J
t
y
and walk into a new world
You're already in costume?
Huh? Is that bad?
It's fine.
I dig his enthusiasm.
Esteemed Western District shoppers!
Are you enjoying your
shopping experience?
Holy crap, he really
.went out there.
Do we have to go?
Seriously?
Let go of me, Sawa.
I could still run...
I'm a heroine, I'm a
heroine, I'm a heroine!
Let's go, team!
Okay.
From the ordinary
.to the extraordinary.
We've got everything you need!
Welcome the Western
Shopping District Heroes!
The Shop Rangers!
Episode 10
I'm going to need everyone's full cooperation, even those who are busy.
For what, exactly?
You're gonna get beat.
Beg your pardon?
Beaten to a pulp.
The Germ Squad is here!
We won't let you lay a finger
on the merchandise!
The Western Shopping District's fruit is the best in the world!
Its veggies are fresh!
Eat this! Curry Punch!
Why, you!
Behold the power of curry!
Damn, that hurt.
We'll get you for this,
Shop Rangers!
Kitaike.
We've protected the Western
Shopping District's peace!
And its tastiness!
To celebrate this victory,
we'll hold a thirty-minute
sale, starting now!
Say the code word
for ten percent off!
And the code word is...
Western Shopping District Heroes!
Shop Rangers!
Did I hear "sale"?
That's great!
Please read this flyer
.for more information.
Here you go.
Take one.
Thank you.
Fantastic job, guys.
Especially for your first time.
We passed out a lot of flyers, too.
But we can do so much better!
Our tempo and timing were subpar!
Your hero mode is intense...
Hero mode?
Kitaike's toast.
He threw his back.
Oh dear.
In that case...
Who can we get to take his place?
Desperate times...
For all your shopping needs,
visit the Western Shopping District!
Mango Beam!
Curry Punch!
Take this, you pesky Shop Rangers!
Bacteria Wave!
Don't give up, Green!
If you fall now,
who will protect the peace
of the shopping district?
You're right.
I can't let myself be defeated!
Take this!
Beta Carotene Shower!
Damn you, Shop Rangers!
We'll be back again tomorrow,
somewhere in this shopping district!
Mark my words!
We've protected the Western
Shopping District's peace!
Yeah!
Sakai.
We're the Western
Shopping District Heroes!
The Shop Rangers!
Oh boy, can you believe it?
They say I make
.the perfect villain.
I'm sorry to let you
.down like this.
Not at all.
Thanks to you,
today was a huge success.
Hey, is there any way you guys would consider extending our agreement?
Huh?
No?
We have the Ivory Fair coming up.
It's not like you practice
every day, right?
But we've barely done
.anything to get ready.
Like, wouldn't it be hard for you
to write your song between shifts?
I guess.
So she needs time to
...figure the song out...
What do you guys think?
If you want to do it,
it's fine with me.
I can get that song
written in no time!
Shiho's done a lot for us,
so it'd be rude to
.just brush her off.
It's not like you've finished
.anything for the festival, either.
I'm happy to keep going,
but could we have some
time to think it over?
Yes, of course.
Lessons in Composition
If you want to know more about composition, you should talk to the vice principal.
The song on that cassette tape was
.co-written by her and your mom.
We will now commence singing—
Loosen up, Nao!
Mahiru...
We'll now sing a song
that was born from Nao and me, and nurtured by our choir.
Miyamoto,
come to the staff room, please.
We need to talk.
What is it?
We'll discuss it there.
Come along.
What's with her?
Who knows.
Maybe it's about the Shop Rangers.
What about 'em?
I saw some girls from the
.choral group watching the show.
Why now, though?
We had permission.
When she's set on something,
she'll spin things any way it suits her.
Really?
We're here!
Why did you all come?
If this is about the choir club,
it concerns us too.
So you're all aware, then,
that after-school jobs
.are strictly forbidden.
But—
I shouldn't have to remind you to
.conduct yourselves as students at all times.
We were totally acting like students!
What am I going to do with you?
Everything we did, we did
.with your permission.
Um, we'd like your
...stamp of approval...
That was...
That was before you explained
.what you'd be doing.
I don't believe that makes a difference.
The shopping district's
.customers enjoyed our act.
We'll be using our pay
.for the Ivory Fair.
I fail to see the problem.
You're missing the point.
I'm willing to overlook this
.if you stop immediately,
but if not—
Madam Vice Principal.
Don't you think going back on
something you've already approved
is extremely unprofessional?
Why are you doing this?
Our club fully intends to finish its job.
What she said.
Excuse us.
We sure told her.
Wien?
Don't worry, Wien.
We schooled her good.
Thank you.
For telling her we wouldn't
.abandon the Shop Rangers.
Stop that, Wien! It's embarrassing.
I'm just so happy.
I figured it'd be all over
.if we were ordered to stop.
Thought we'd give in?
Of course not!
Once I got into the
.role of Curry Yellow,
it was pretty fun.
I forget what you call this...
I feel indented.
Oh, you mean indebted.
Long ago, a very poor
man named Ted
was lent a warm and durable
.Deb brand coat by his best friend.
By letting Ted wear his Deb coat,
that friend coined the term "in-deb-ted".
It's a touching tale of
priceless friendship!
Slow down!
I definitely need to
.share this with Jan.
I know one about
.flipping your debts.
Wait!
Stop messing with him, guys.
He takes you seriously.
Huh?
I was thinking something
like "ta-ri-ra-rira"!
But that's not what you sang before.
Really?
Yes, really.
So which will it be?
Both?
Please, Nao?
Is your name read as
Naoko or Naomi?
Your first name, I mean,
Madam Vice President.
Naoko. Why do you ask?
But my mother called you Nao, right?
Recording now!
We will now commence singing—
Ah, yes, she did.
Your mother and I belonged
.to the same club in high school.
The choir club?
That's right. That's what
.we called it back then.
Wait, did you ever visit my
mother in the hospital?
Yes.
Your mother wanted to see me,
so I went one time.
I see.
Why do you ask?
No reason.
If you're wondering why I didn't tell you that she and I were acquaintances,
it's because I must respect
.the rules of this school.
Okay.
No matter what happened in the past,
you are currently no more
.than one of my students.
I will treat you no better
.or worse than any other.
I understand that.
Then what do you want from me?
I'd like to ask you how my mother went about writing songs.
You two wrote that
song together, right?
I'm trying to finish a song of hers...
How should I go about it?
Or maybe...
Nao, say something!
I'm listening.
That's not enough.
Which do you like better?
You should sing too!
I can't just...
What?
It doesn't come naturally to me
...like it does for you...
What?
You're just overthinking it!
Don't you enjoy singing?
Music is about having fun with sound!
You gotta have fun!
Because you're not enjoying yourself.
You can't do it if you
.think you "have" to.
That's work.
A song is something that flows naturally
.from the depths of your heart.
In any case, I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't
.waste my time with such petty concerns.
I'm sorry. And...
Thank you!
I should go.
Oh, all right.
Get well soon.
Sheet music?
Yes.
I'd like to write a song
.with my daughter.
Just like you and I did.
Maybe if she's accepted to your school,
and joins the choir club,
she could be with you—
It's the choral group now.
I told you.
Right.
That song, and the original club,
were both essentially your creations.
That's not true.
I'll be going now.
Thank you, Nao.
I'm glad I could see you one last time.
What?
It seems I'm not going to make it.
No way.
Why not?
Some no-name group's album
.isn't worth a dime.
B-But this is a special edition,
and it's autographed!
I thought we could sell it
to raise money for the fair!
I mean, we can't keep doing this
.after-school job thing forever.
This is my biggest treasure.
Konatsu, I'm sorry.
I was in a bad mood the other day,
and I lashed out at you.
When?
When I said it was rude to reject Shiho.
But you were right.
We'll figure out what to do
.about the fair together.
If we quit now,
it'd be like letting the vice principal win.
We can handle the
Ivory Fair and a job!
No sweat!
That an order?
No, I was more pumping myself up.
I agree!
I'm in, too.
Same. And I'll get the song done.
You sure?
Don't forget to get the script checked.
Okay, okay!
Ivory Fair, here we come!
Great!
I'm feeling a lot of energy from Yellow.
Iwasaki Cleaning
We did it!
Yeah!
Iwasaki Cleaning
Western Shopping District Heroes!
Shop Rangers!
Join us again at 4:30,
in front of the traditional sweet shop.
Until we meet again!
That's mine!
Iwasaki Cleaning
Wien!
Evil will not be tolerated!
Wien, just leave it!
A true hero doesn't have
the choice to give up!
What the...
Dearest Jan:
I've decided to carry on Ganba Red's
mission, so I've been busy as of late
defending world peace.
Thankfully, I have four
.trustworthy friends at my side,
There!
and they are warriors imbued with
.the same passion for justice.
Like everyone, a defender of justice
.has his share of rough times,
but I refuse to be discouraged!
Why, you!
You did not just steal
a mere bag back there!
That's a proud symbol of
Yellow's dedication to her fri—
Let go!
Get off of me!
A hero never gives up!
Because we...
keep the Earth turning.
We can do it!
With beads of sweat gleaming in the light,
we reach for the future in front of us!
We're scared, but that's why we'll never give up!
We don't want to regret anything! Not anything!
The dreams we're chasing won't be easily destroyed!
So we'll take hold of it right now!
That moment where we can truly shine!
Yes!
Gan gan, it's courage time!
Gan gan, we'll fulfill our duty!
Our passion is blazing!
What is wrong with you people?!
Justice! Valor!
Friendship!
We're the Western
Shopping District Heroes!
Shop Rangers!
Great work! Local Superheroes
Dear Jan:
Wherever you are, I'm sure you're working hard, just as I am.
I believe I'll be able to give
.these letters to you someday,
so I'll keep on writing them.
hareta hi ame no hi demo minna ga ireba itsumo egao ni nareta
The sun shone sometimes, sometimes it rained,
but I always smiled when I was with you
kioku no kanata made omoidashitari tayutau koe mimi sumasou
Even in the farthest reaches of my memory, I feel the echo of your voices
saa te wo sashinoberarete wa no naka he
When I was introduced to the group,
hitori ja nai kuukan de muchuu ni natteru jikan
being suddenly surrounded by you all put me in a daze
kokochiyoi kaze ga fuite
A gentle wind blows here
warattari naitari utatte mitari
and we laugh and cry and sing
tojiteita kokoro wo hiraite omoide no fureezu kuchizusamu
My heart used to be shut off from the world,
yet now it opens and I can sing of my memories
kanadeyou
Let us make our dreams come true
I wanna play a prince.
No way! I don't do art!
This was originally Wakana
.and her mother's song.
Episode 11
Waxing
and Waning
Episode 11
Waxing
and Waning
Episode 11
Waxing
and Waning
I'm everyone's mom.
Almost got it.