Hopes and dreams are the
.power that moves humanity,
and keep the Earth turning!
Tomorrow doesn't come just because the sun rises in the morning!
The sun rises in the morning because people keep their hopes close to their hearts!
We keep the Earth turning!
We are the passionate heroes,
the Ganba Rangers!
Have a nice day.
Why...
Once my heart knows of its burning voice
mune no oku ga takanaru atsui koe ni kizuitara
it will carry what I do, and you will know too
sutaatorain wa kimi no me no mae ni aru
Just run along your path, even if you can't see it
mada mienai michi demo hashirihajimereba ii sa
I don't think you should give up so easily
akirameru yori mo suteki da to omowanai
Anxiety is always nearby
itsumo fuan wa sugu soba de
keeping a hold on your bold courage
kakedasu omoi wo shimetsukeru keredo
Get beyond the present and shed a light on your path
ima wo koete arukidasu michi naru michi ni hikari wo
Find the tomorrow that you dream of
hajimete wo kurikaeshi tsukamitore ashita wo
We will embrace our countless dreams and walk onwards
sou sa bokutachi wa mugen no yume dakishime susumu no sa
A
t
J
I want to believe in myself
kagayaiteru jibun wo shinjitai
Let us put love into our strength to stand up
tachiageru chikara ni saidai no ai wo komete
t
A
C
Let us be happy
omou mama tabidatou
r
J
t
y
and walk into a new world
atarashii sekai no naka he
Coffee?
Sure.
Too bitter.
How did Mom write songs?
Huh?
How?
The normal way?
She'd sing, and then sing...
Was the melody
already in her head?
Or did it come to her
as she went along?
I mean, even a cat could put
a song together if all the parts
were already floating
.around in its head.
But is that really
all there is to it?
There must be more!
Sorry, I just listen to music.
But I don't think you
.need to force it.
Take your time.
You're probably right.
Maybe I should talk to Shiho.
They went to school
.together, after all.
Oh, right.
That's a good idea.
Episode 9
Turn
ing
Wh
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
Turn
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
ing
Re
d
Turn
ing
Wh
ite
and
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
Turn
ing
Re
d
ite
Turn
ing
Re
d
ite
Turn
ing
Re
d
ite
Turn
There are other jobs out there
.that involve horses.
Like?
Training.
There's no weight limit for that?
You're so insensitive.
Ow.
My weight's not an issue.
I just can't picture
myself being happy
with other people riding
.the horses I raised.
That's understandable.
Sorry I'm late, folks.
I have an announcement!
For the upcoming Ivory Fair,
..our very own choir club...
And sometimes badminton club.
Musical Drama
...will perform a musical drama!
A musical drama?
That's right.
Obviously, singing is
.our top priority,
Musical Drama
but I want to include a solid story, dancing, great costumes, and a real stage!
Who'll do what?
And how?
I'll be the scriptwriter.
Musical Drama
And Wakana's already
writing a song, right?
We can use that as
our featured piece!
What?
You're writing a song?
Musical Drama
That's amazing!
I haven't written anything!
I don't even know if I can!
Sawa, you'll handle choreography.
Choreography?!
Sure. You've got the hottest moves.
Tanaka and Wien can take care
.of the stage and props,
and we'll all pitch in
to make costumes!
Musical Drama
You sound pretty serious.
Of course!
Almost too serious.
This'll cost a fortune.
Definitely. At least ten,
twenty thousand yen.
Can we even get a budget
that high for the Ivory Fair?
I doubt it.
So then, you have
other sources lined up?
That's what we're here
to brainstorm!
Figures.
Musical Drama
You need to work these
.things out in advance.
I don't mind singing,
but I'm not going to do any "my love, my heart, I'll die without you" stuff.
You want a kissing scene?
As if!
Wien, say something!
Like what?
Anything but that!
Haven't you been listening
and taking notes like usual?
No, I don't need notes anymore.
Hey, Sawa, how busy
is Shiho these days?
My mom?
No busier than usual.
Please take a look at the
.documents in front of you.
Western Shopping District Event Planning
Let's make this summer a hot one!
When you compare this district's revenue between this summer and the last,
you can see we're having
.a rather rough year.
Basically, we're in quite a tight spot.
Western Shopping District Event Planning
Let's make this summer a hot one!
Sure, but that's just
.a sign of the times.
It's tough everywhere.
And we're not getting any younger.
Sakazaki's in the hospital, you know.
He went for a full check-up.
Well, he does eat an awful lot.
Could you please refrain from
personal conversations?
It's fine.
We don't need an explanation,
since it's all written down.
But I thought I should give you a rundown
...before we started strategizing...
No need.
If we all put in a little
.elbow grease, it'll all work out.
Nothing beats honest effort.
By the way, have you heard
about Eikodo's girl?
They say she's pretty amazing.
Western Shopping District Event Planning
Let's make this summer a hot one!
How about local superheroes?
Local superheroes?
Oh, I understand.
You mean like mascots?
We need more than just
.people in costumes.
Let's make this summer a hot one!
We need superheroes!
Like the ones in groups of red,
white, yellow, and green.
Can you please clarify
what you're suggesting?
Let's make this summer a hot one!
They could do "So-and-So Superhero! So-and-So Ranger!" moves,
and hand out store flyers.
Like a sandwich board campaign?
That's a pretty good idea, Shiho!
Yes, yes.
I've already got an idea
.for the costumes,
so all that's left is to
.choose our heroes.
Boy, am I exhausted these days...
I can't shake these headaches...
Oh, my back...
I'll need at least three volunteers,
though I'd prefer five.
Who'd like to give our
shopping district a—
Oh, excuse me.
Hi, Mom.
Are you free soon?
Yeah.
What's up?
Wakana wanted to ask you
.about a few things.
Wakana?
Are you guys heading home
from your club meeting?
Do you have five people there?
Yeah, why?
That's perfect! Bring them all over.
I'll treat you all to
some delicious cake.
Okay. I'll ask them.
Make sure they come, okay?
.I'll meet you there.
Western Shopping District Event Planning
Let's make this summer a hot one!
Someone get some delicious cake over here, on the double!
Well, we're not gonna
.turn down cake.
Right?
Right.
Then Tanaka can come with us.
You think Shiho can help you?
Wien could take the
...train with Konatsu...
I'm not sure.
I'm just trying to figure out what my mom thought about when she wrote songs.
Like if she ever felt scared...
Scared? What do you mean?
Like, if she ever doubted herself,
or worried if the finished
.product was any good.
I just... I need to know
more about my mom
if I'm going to write
.a song with her.
That's deep.
Here you are!
Welcome, everyone! Dig in.
Why are you smiling like that?
Thank you!
Thank you.
Say, would you like to
make some money?
We sure would!
Konatsu.
My grandma said there are two kinds of people you should never let take you for a ride.
Slick talkers, and
.rollercoaster operators.
Just hear me out.
Wouldn't you like to be superheroes?
What do you mean?
Want the details?
Yes.
Yes!
Careful.
Sure.
Suits & Masks
(Hero Costumes for Promotional Use)
Suits and masks?
What are those?
Suits & Masks
(Hero Costumes for Promotional Use)
Oh, here we are.
These are...
Superhero outfits!
Red, pink, yellow, white...
Thank goodness.
They look perfectly usable.
There's green, too.
Just like the Ganba Rangers!
Mom, what is this all about?
These were used for a lunch box contest in the shopping district a while back.
Aren't these a bit small?
They're soft, so you can
.stretch them out.
Oh, hey. They've got boots, too.
You wore those?
They're pretty old, but
.the sizes should be okay.
For a lunch box contest?
Yeah, but we overstuffed it and failed.
Wow, they really do stretch.
I can't believe these
.were hidden here.
Our ambitions didn't fit in the box!
You can stop talking now.
The association's hoping you'll
.wear them this weekend.
How does 30,000 yen sound?
For all five of us?
When would we start?
How many hours
would we work?
We'd like to be able to use
.all five of you if we can.
You'd be doing five
.ten-minute shifts each day.
30,000 yen for a weekend's
work is fair, don't you think?
We'd also need time to rehearse...
What do you think?
Why do I have to decide?
You're in for sure, daughter of mine.
Wakana wants to ask you
.about her mother.
Then if you scratch my back,
I'll scratch yours.
Traitor.
Please!
You're the only ones I can
ask to be superheroes!
This is a worthy mission.
It's worthy,
because it inspires hopes and dreams.
Hopes and dreams are the
powers that move humanity
and keep the Earth turning.
Wien?
Tomorrow doesn't come just because the sun rises in the morning!
The sun rises in the morning
...because people keep their hopes...
...close to their hearts!
We keep the Earth turning!
I'd forgotten something important.
How could I allow myself to lose hope?
Can you please repeat
our job description?
Sure... We'd like you to work over
...the weekend, for ten minutes at a...
Wien sure is passionate.
Was he always like this?
Those were Ganba Red's words.
"The passionate heroes,
...the Ganba Rangers."
We saw them in his room, remember?
Oh, yeah.
So this flipped his superhero switch.
So, you guys are in, right?
Yup!
We can rehearse tomorrow at my house!
Not wasting any time, huh?
The battle is upon us!
You want to know how
Mahiru wrote her songs?
Well, I was only ever a singer...
She was easy to talk to, but I don't
.think that subject ever came up.
Oh, I see.
I never saw her worry
.much about that, though.
I'm pretty sure she was the type
.to just let inspiration strike.
Oh?
I wish I had talked to her
.more about these things.
Well, if you want to know
.more about composition,
you should talk to the vice principal.
The song on that cassette tape
was co-written by her and your mom.
Mahiru told us she wanted us
.to write our own song.
At first, we all thought
.she was joking.
But Takakura has always
.been quite serious,
so she got swept up
.in the whole affair.
We were surprised when they
.actually finished a real song.
It's a sweet song,
don't you think?
Yes.
Takakura could be hard
.to approach at times,
but I think she was someone
.we could look up to.
Probably.
Is that so?
Thank you for telling me all this.
I'm going to head home now.
Good luck!
What is a song, anyway?
Hey!
I came up with a concept
.for the superheroes.
Concept?
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western Shopping District Heroes...
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Snop Rangers?
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
Western
Shopping
District
Heroes
Shop Rangers
I think that's a "h".
Shop Rangers!
Since we represent the
.Western Shopping District,
it makes sense, right?
So that's it?
The Shop Rangers are here
to fight for galactic peace and
.great bargains for our customers.
These heroes of justice will
.ensure you enjoy your visit.
Meat Red? Fruit Pink?
Whitebait White?
Actually, I was thinking...
Are we really wearing these?
Who's gonna be which color?
I like red.
Sawa, red is for the leader.
Favorite colors don't
.come into play here.
Huh?
Of course, if you think
.you're ready to be Red,
I will do the right thing
.and step aside.
I can do that... I think...
But first,
I have to ask if you
.truly are ready to be Red.
Red's qualifications are
a sense of justice—
No, no, no, I've got no
.qualifications at all.
Are you okay with Pink, Wakana?
You can be Red.
I want to be Yellow.
Okay, then Miyamoto
.can be Curry Yellow.
There's no curry place
.in the shopping district.
I don't like curry.
I was thinking of asking you to
.make us a theme song, Wakana,
but since you're busy writing
.our song for the Ivory Fair,
we can just use the
Ganba Rangers theme.
The most important thing
.is their trademark phrase.
Full Power!
Energy Charge!
Meat Red!
Taichi, you're up!
Me? Uh, well...
Straight from the source!
Bursting with flavor!
Whitebait White!
You need to sound cooler!
The kids are never gonna buy that!
Sawa, your turn.
Uh...
Vitamins, minerals, and nutrients!
Veggie Green defends your health!
Put more feeling into it!
And do a pose with each word!
Wakana, go.
You first, Konatsu.
Curry Yellow loves curry! Try it!
Try what, some roux?
You sound like a commercial.
Be serious, you guys!
This might just be a small
.show in a small town,
but being superheroes for little kids
is an important mission!
Serious?
It's just to draw crowds.
We'll be fine.
Did something happen?
Air mail?
From who?
I had mailed them
.to a friend in Wien,
but they were sent back.
A girl?
Konatsu!
It says there's no person named "Jan" living there anymore,
so I should stop sending letters.
Have you tried calling them
or sending an email?
Jan's just a kid.
He'll turn seven this year.
We'd watch the Ganba Rangers video my grandpa sent, over and over.
Ganba Red was our hero.
But then I had to
.move back to Japan.
Are you really going?
I'll miss you.
Don't worry.
Ganba Red will protect you.
Right.
Will you write to me
once you're back home?
I'd like to know more about Japan.
You bet I will!
So that's it.
Did you write about cultivating
..excellence and saying "to arms"?
And the white rhino in
the school's basement?
Yes, all of it.
Too bad it all came back.
You know, Wien...
It's okay.
I get the feeling I'll see
.Jan again, someday.
Until then, all I can do is
.trust Jan is doing his best.
And I'll do my best, too.
As a West Shopping
District Hero. As Red!
All right!
I just thought of a new pose.
Straight from the source!
Bursting with flavor,
Whitebait White!
That's way better!
Yeah, huh?
You see the whitebait, right?
If you move like this,
it'll look even more natural.
Like this?
Hey, this doesn't
.come with a skirt.
It'll show everything!
I guess these characters were
.supposed to be boys.
Jeez.
Don't worry! You
.have a great figure.
Yep.
And it's not like you can see
.our undies through these,
so we don't need skirts.
This smells like the
.main hall at my house.
Like the temple?!
Can you guys hurry up?
Are you done?
Open that door and I'll kill you.
Oh crap, it ripped!
It did? Where?
What the hell are they doing?
Hey...
Red.
Red!
It's gonna be a long day.
What is the meaning of this?
I was against it, of course.
But even as principal,
I'm also an employee.
If my superiors—
This is outrageous.
It's just too sudden.
It's irresponsible!
Can you honestly accept this?
Have you forgotten all the work we put in,
and the emotions we shared, during the days
when you were the
choir club's advisor?
I'm sorry.
Shirahamazaka High School Rule 18:
Except in special circumstances, students are prohibited from having after-school jobs.
Doesn't this qualify as
special circumstances?
Wow, you're raising
money for the Ivory Fair?
I'm so proud!
The vice principal?
Keep dreaming.
Ain't happening.
Nope.
Well, worrying won't
solve the problem!
Let's try!
Excuse us.
Madam Vice Principal,
we've come to ask permission
.to take on an after-school job.
If we're to perform
.at the Ivory Fair,
the choir club needs
.to raise funds.
It would be different
if we were given
an ample budget,
like the choral group,
but our club is poorer
than a church mouse!
Jobs are allowed under
special circumstances, right?
This is exactly that kind
.of special circumstance.
Huh?
Um, we'd like your
...stamp of approval...
Oh, I see.
Thank you very much.
The sun shone sometimes, sometimes it rained,
but I always smiled when I was with you
hareta hi ame no hi demo minna ga ireba itsumo egao ni nareta
Even in the farthest reaches of my memory, I feel the echo of your voices
kioku no kanata made omoidashitari tayutau koe mimi sumasou
When I was introduced to the group,
saa te wo sashinoberarete wa no naka he
being suddenly surrounded by you all put me in a daze
hitori ja nai kuukan de muchuu ni natteru jikan
A gentle wind blows here
kokochiyoi kaze ga fuite
and we laugh and cry and sing
warattari naitari utatte mitari
My heart used to be shut off from the world,
yet now it opens and I can sing of my memories
tojiteita kokoro wo hiraite omoide no fureezu kuchizusamu
Let us make our dreams come true
kanadeyou
We did it, we did it!
That was easy!
Don't you think the vice principal was acting kind of weird?
I told you!
Yeah.
It was too easy.
Great job, Konatsu.
You're already in costume?
Beta Carotene Shower!
Curry Punch!
Episode 10
Crushing
and Burning
Episode 10
Crushing
and Burning
Episode 10
Crushing
and Burning
Mango Beam!
Our tempo and
timing were subpar!