That was your last
.supplementary class. Great work.
Thank you very much.
Yes! Now I can—
Not yours, hers.
mune no oku ga takanaru atsui koe ni kizuitara
Once my heart knows of its burning voice
sutaatorain wa kimi no me no mae ni aru
it will carry what I do, and you will know too
mada mienai michi demo hashirihajimereba ii sa
Just run along your path, even if you can't see it
akirameru yori mo suteki da to omowanai
I don't think you should give up so easily
itsumo fuan wa sugu soba de
Anxiety is always nearby
kakedasu omoi wo shimetsukeru keredo
keeping a hold on your bold courage
ima wo koete arukidasu michi naru michi ni hikari wo
Get beyond the present and shed a light on your path
hajimete wo kurikaeshi tsukamitore ashita wo
Find the tomorrow that you dream of
sou sa bokutachi wa mugen no yume dakishime susumu no sa
We will embrace our countless dreams and walk onwards
kagayaiteru jibun wo shinjitai
A
t
J
I want to believe in myself
tachiageru chikara ni saidai no ai wo komete
Let us put love into our strength to stand up
omou mama tabidatou
t
A
C
Let us be happy
atarashii sekai no naka he
r
J
t
y
and walk into a new world
This is your note.
And, go.
You sound great together.
Episode 7
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
and
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
and
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
and
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
and
Los
Spinn
ing in
Circ
les
and
Los
ing
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
ing in
Circ
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
Spinn
ing in
Circ
ing in
Circ
ing in
Circ
ing in
Circ
Circ
and Sometimes Badminton
^
Choir Club Meeting
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
Now that she's
.joined up for real,
let's start by having
.Sakai Wakana introduce herself.
You should've warned me!
Please stand, Miss Sakai.
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
Go on.
Do I have to?
Hurry up.
You can do it!
Choir Club Meeting
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
^
and Sometimes Badminton
Choir Club Meeting
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
^
and Sometimes Badminton
Jeez... What should I say?
Choir Club Meeting
Go get 'em!
and Sometimes Badminton
^
Choir Club Meeting
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
Um...
I've decided to start taking part in the choir club's activities.
My name is Sakai Wakana.
I know I haven't
.been participating,
and Sometimes Badminton
^
Choir Club Meeting
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
and my attitude
.could've been better,
so I'd like to apol—
and Sometimes Badminton
^
Choir Club Meeting
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
and Sometimes Badminton
^
Choir Club Meeting
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
and Sometimes Badminton
^
Choir Club Meeting
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
and Sometimes Badminton
^
Choir Club Meeting
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
and Sometimes Badminton
^
Choir Club Meeting
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
Let's cut off the
.formalities right there.
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
Choir Club Meeting
Shtop it, Wawana!
Okay, time to talk
.about the Ivory.
Question!
Yes, Wien.
What is the "Ivory"?
The basics, huh?
It's a white rhinoceros.
It's the culture fair.
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
Huh?
It's a white rhinoceros.
You mean, with the horn?
That's right.
Didn't you know there's a
white rhino under the gym?
There is?!
Did you know?
Of course.
They let it out once a year for a festival and parade, where it sings and dances!
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
Welcome Ivory!
Makes sense.
It'd be pretty mean
.to keep it locked up.
Today, we'll discuss what
.our club will do for the fair,
and Sometimes Badminton
^
Choir Club Meeting
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
so give me all your ideas!
Okay!
Girls are scary.
Hello.
Oh, thank you.
Thanks!
Horsemanship Class
Badminton Class
Cat Café
Hero Show
Eating Contest
Today's Agenda: Ivory Fair Discussion
Horsemanship Class
Badminton Class
Cat Café
Hero Show
Eating Contest
Cat Café
Hero Show
Badminton Class
Cat Café
Hero Show
Badminton Class
No, no, and no!
Cat Café
Hero Show
Eating Contest
Cat Café
Hero Show
Eating Contest
These don't have anything
to do with singing!
We could do singing
lessons on horseback?
Singing badminton?
A hero musical?
Singing cat café?
Singing eating contest?
No!
We'll sing on stage, in the gym.
It'll be packed with visitors!
This is our first and
final chance to shine!
Will the rhino be there?
Get over the rhino.
Can't we just do a
normal choir piece?
But then we'll be upstaged
.by the choral group.
The bigger group will
.be more impressive.
I don't want to give the
.vice principal that satisfaction.
What about an opera?
Nice!
With five people?
Plus, we can barely
.manage regular songs.
Opera is way out of our league.
Yeah, I guess so.
It's not a competition.
What matters is that
.we sing our own song.
Wow.
Pretty smooth!
What the hell?
I'm right, aren't I?
Yeah, that's the bottom line.
Yeah.
All right!
Let's show the vice principal
and her choral group!
Move.
Uh, okay.
Your friends?
Yeah. Ueno's in the choral group.
Isn't this one a bit easy?
And Hirohata's the president.
Yeah, but let's take it anyway.
I see you've found some new friends to goof off with. Just as well.
Huh?
Most people in our choral group are seriously thinking about their futures,
so I'm glad you're not
.getting in our way anymore.
Ciao, strepitoso.
Ciao!
Strepitoso?
It means "noisy".
"Strepitoso" is a musical term meaning noisy or boisterous.
Works for me!
I really don't want to
.be outdone by them.
I'm off to the
.student council room.
Godspeed to you, my people.
I've got mounted archery
.practice, so I need to take off.
My cram school
.classes start today.
Cram school?
I'm prepping for entrance exams.
I thought you had
.an athletic scholarship.
I do, but I can't count on that.
If I fail my entrance exams,
I can't play badminton.
See ya around.
Okay.
Bye.
I guess everyone's
.thinking about the future.
What do you want to do?
I don't know yet.
I guess we have that in common.
There's something I
.want to create right now,
so I'm focusing on that first.
I need to hit the library.
Later.
Uh, yeah.
Excuse me.
Oh, Makoto.
What have we here,
another dirty book?
I'd like to reserve the
.main stage for the culture fair.
Mr. Assistant Secretary sure
.has a lot of time on his hands.
Here.
Fill out your application, then get lost.
Yes, sir!
Let's see...
"Our performance will
consist of singing and dancing."
Guess that's good enough for now.
Do you honestly think that'll pass?
Huh?
Why wouldn't it?
There's a screening process in place because of the
.large number of applications that come in every year.
That doesn't apply to
official clubs though, right?
It does now.
Before, only established groups
.with good track records applied.
What are you trying to say?
That the vice principal is in charge of running the main stage.
Seriously?
Yes!
Sabure,
we've got practice on Sunday.
After I graduate, we'll
...probably have to say goodbye...
Let's make the most of our time.
I'm home.
You opened it?!
I can't believe you!
I've told you this
a thousand times:
Keep riding as a hobby.
Have you considered the
consequences if you fail?
Some obstacles can't be
.overcome by hard work alone.
Especially as a woman.
Horseracing is a gamble.
You don't have to succeed the
.temple business if you don't want to,
but at least get a
.government position,
or any other real job,
and ride in your free time.
I have nothing to
.say to you anymore.
How will you make a living?
I've been saving my pay!
It's not that much yet, but...
What about the rest?
Listen to me.
Your food, your tuition,
and even the clothes on your back
were all paid for
.through honest work.
Supporting a family through
.your job is what working is all about.
Horseback riding does
.not constitute work.
It's play!
Get off my back!
I didn't ask for your opinion!
If that's how it's gonna be,
you can have them!
Might as well sell it all
and get your money back!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Having fun in here?
You know, there are
.better ways to talk about this.
This is a world of winners and losers.
It's not as nice as you think.
I hate you.
I hope you go bald!
Hey!
She hopes you go bald.
Quiet.
Meisetsu Music Dictionary
Classical Music
Yamaai Publishing
Meisetsu Music Dictionary
Classical Music
Yamaai Publishing
Meisetsu Music Dictionary
Classical Music
Yamaai Publishing
Meisetsu Music Dictionary
Classical Music
Yamaai Publishing
Revised Edition
Meisetsu Music Dictionary
Classical Music
Yamaai Publishing
Revised Edition
Meisetsu Music Dictionary
Classical Music
Yamaai Publishing
Revised Edition
Meisetsu Music Dictionary
Classical Music
Yamaai Publishing
Revised Edition
Meisetsu Music Dictionary
Classical Music
Yamaai Publishing
Revised Edition
Meisetsu Music Dictionary
Classical Music
Yamaai Publishing
Revised Edition
Meisetsu Music Dictionary
Classical Music
Yamaai Publishing
Career Planning Sheet
My dear friend Jan,
My friends in the choir club
are all working hard
.to reach their goals.
I'm happy for them, of course,
but my heart is uneasy.
I wonder if I'll also
.find my calling.
Where have I come from,
and where am I going?
This is no good.
I shouldn't sound so depressed.
I have something
amazing to tell you!
They keep a white rhino
in the basement of the gym here!
They let it out once a year,
and hold a festival to celebrate!
Wakana, aren't you up yet?
It's pretty rare for you to sleep in.
Why didn't you wake me earlier?
You mean, "Thank you for
making me breakfast", right?
Thank you.
Can you feed Dora, too?
"Please feed her, Father dearest."
Please feed her, Father dearest.
By the way, Sugi from the sake shop got me some tickets again.
How 'bout checking out a musical with your old man for a change?
I want to go with my friends!
Can you ask him if he
can get you another one?
What?
Please, Father dearest.
Sure. And here,
I made you lunch.
Oh, thank you.
See you later.
Have a good day.
What's wrong?
Huh? Uh, nothing.
What?
Is that all you're eating?
Huh?
Yeah.
Did you eat earlier?
I'm just not that hungry.
Why are you covering that up?
Oh wow, it's a heart!
Is not! I overslept this morning, and my dad
.made this for me, for some weird reason.
He's just doing this to bug me!
Whole lotta daddy
.love in that lunch.
There is not!
It's totally love, right?
Love, huh?
Oh hey, I have tickets
.for a musical in town.
You guys want to go?
It could help give us
.ideas for the Ivory Fair.
Really? I'm in!
Yeah...
Opera might be out, but we
.could definitely do a musical.
We could sing in cat costumes!
Indeed, that would be splendid!
Keep spinning like that
and you'll fall again.
Fear not, for it shall
work... some... how!
Right, Sawa?
What?
Huh?
What's wrong?
You haven't touched
.your rice ball.
I don't have much
.of an appetite today.
Sorry.
You eat it.
I'm heading out.
What's with her?
Think she's on a diet?
What're you doing
for the culture fair?
Maybe a concert or something.
Great idea. I could play bass for you.
Cool, let's do it!
I sense the coming of spring.
What?
Y-Yes!
Come on in.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Oh, it's just you.
There's an issue
.with the choir club.
They want to use the
main stage during the cult—
I leave that all in your hands.
But, sir...
All in your hands.
Certainly, sir.
Good day, Mr. Chairman.
I've been waiting for you.
Thank you so much for coming.
How may I be of assistance today?
How are you feeling?
Much better, thank you.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
You didn't.
My only concern is how this might adversely affect my business plan.
So it's a sure thing?
Yes, though the schedule
.has been slightly accelerated.
That's what I'm here to discuss.
If you want a comfortable retirement,
you'll have to work for it.
Yes, of course.
What's wrong?
Just a stomach ache.
Do you need some medicine?
It's not that bad, thanks.
Raise your velum, open your throat,
and let your tone be bright.
Listen to each other.
Sawa?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Should I get the nurse?
Here, sit down.
Are you anemic?
Of course not.
I'm fine.
You're really pale.
Have you been dieting?
Aren't you going a bit overboard?
You're on a diet?
But you're like,
so far from being fat.
Girls worry about this stuff too—
Shut up, Tanaka.
Idiot.
Insensitive.
Jackass.
Jackass!
Stupid.
What the hell?
I'm worried about her too!
Sorry, but I don't
.feel so good today.
I'm going home.
She's been acting so weird lately.
Yeah.
She hasn't been herself.
We should go after her.
Definitely.
Was that my fault?
No clue.
Please, just give me a chance!
I've always...
Being passionate isn't enough?
But I have thought
it through! I'm serious!
Can we at least meet in person?
Please!
She fell in love.
She fell in love?
Yup. No doubt about it.
Are you sure?
Her head's been way
.up in the clouds lately,
and now she's
.suddenly started a diet.
You probably don't understand because you lack experience,
but this is a clear
.case of lovesickness.
That phone call makes me
.think it must be an older guy.
Could he be married with children?
Konatsu!
My romance radar
is never wrong!
Good morning.
Sorry I'm late.
Morning!
Feeling better today?
Of course.
Shall we go?
That was awesome.
Boy, do I love singing!
You guys feel like going
to a café or something?
Sure!
I found this pretty cool place,
but I felt weird going in alone.
I'm going home.
I've got mounted archery practice.
Practice doesn't
.....start until evening...
I know.
But I'm taking Sabure
.with me today.
I need to get home early
.and get everything ready.
Sorry.
This is serious.
Want to head to that café
and come up with a plan?
Can we take a little detour first?
Composition for Dummies
So Easy, Even A Cat Could Do It!
Composition?
My mom left me a song she'd
.begun to write, but it's not complete.
So you're going to finish it?
Yeah.
I promised her.
That's great!
I'm feeling inspired!
But first, let's scope out
.the newest manga.
Special!!
Arts College Corner
Okita.
Okita, please start.
Right!
hareta hi ame no hi demo minna ga ireba itsumo egao ni nareta
The sun shone sometimes, sometimes it rained,
but I always smiled when I was with you
kioku no kanata made omoidashitari tayutau koe mimi sumasou
Even in the farthest reaches of my memory, I feel the echo of your voices
saa te wo sashinoberarete wa no naka he
When I was introduced to the group,
hitori ja nai kuukan de muchuu ni natteru jikan
being suddenly surrounded by you all put me in a daze
kokochiyoi kaze ga fuite
A gentle wind blows here
warattari naitari utatte mitari
and we laugh and cry and sing
tojiteita kokoro wo hiraite omoide no fureezu kuchizusamu
My heart used to be shut off from the world,
yet now it opens and I can sing of my memories
kanadeyou
Let us make our dreams come true
Ambulance!
Somebody call an ambulance!
Right away.
Excuse me, someone's been hurt!
So you're not going to
ride professionally?
You can hug me too!
That's not okay!
I might as well just quit.
Episode 8
Worrying
and Racing Ahead
Episode 8
Worrying
and Racing Ahead
Episode 8
Worrying
and Racing Ahead
I'm on my way, so wait right there.