Hey, you busy?
You wanna hang out?
Do you know what
a doppelganger is?
A doppel...
A second you.
When you see that person,
bad things will happen.
What are you talking abou—
What happened?
That was great!
Did you see his face?
I knew you were on your way,
so I talked to him for a bit.
Looks like he misunderstood.
What happened to your eye?
It's a sty or something.
My eyelid is inflamed.
It'll get better soon.
Yeah, but still...
It's kinda annoying.
yoru wo oou mabuta hirake
Open your eyes and bare the darkness within
magaki kage wo osoreru nakare
Don't fear the evil in them
honokuraki hitsugi kara
Like a puppet that was
umiotosareta ningyou no you ni
disgorged by a gloomy coffin
karada wa akaku kogoe
your body is covered in blood-red ice
kokoro wa yami ni ayasaresodatsu
and blackness is the cradle of your soul
kimi ni boku ga mieru kai
Can you see me?
tsunagu te no tsumetasa ni
I can feel the chill of your hands
senketsu no tsume tateru
Raise your blood-stained talons
mayu yosete goran yo
Scowl at the world around you
kowashiaou saki ni
Let us destroy each other
tsuzuku nazo ni michiru ketsumatsu wo
and evade a future where all is clad in doubt and confusion
hane mo ashi mo mogareta mama
Otherwise, with our wings and feet ripped from us
kokuu no naka kuchihateru yori
we will rot away under this empty sky
mou hitori boku ga ite
There is a second me
dareka wo itai hodo aishiteiru n da
which loves someone so much it draws blood
saa docchi ga maboroshi darou ne
Tell me now, which is the real one?
- Karma -
We'll be ninth graders next month.
Yeah.
We'll be fifteen too.
Not looking forward to it?
Not really. It's nothing special.
We'll just have high
school entry exams.
Sheesh! Don't remind me.
Is this too flashy?
Kinda boring.
You think? I kinda like it.
Weren't you going
to buy it for me?
It's for me.
It's easier to use you as a
model than using a mirror.
Oh, I hadn't thought of that.
Doesn't really suit you, huh?
I don't really like it.
You think?
Too out of style.
That's kinda mean.
You think?
This one...
Now, who's the real one?
Don't you think?
What?
Look at me.
Didn't you say that eye
lets you see things?
Yeah.
Do you see anything
when you look at me?
No, I don't.
I think it's cute!
I like how it's different
from your right eye.
What was it called?
Heterochromia?
Mismatched colors.
You shouldn't hide it.
Your face is too cute
for an eye patch.
Isn't that some roundabout
way of calling yourself cute?
Yep.
You can't deny it, though.
Yay!
Mister, I'll take that one!
What! Why not?
Dang. It was cute too.
You have strange taste.
You think?
Do you think that's cute?
It looks dumb.
Really?
What about that elephant?
It's cute!
I don't understand you.
I wanna go to a
real amusement park.
Wanna go next time?
How's next week sound?
My mom's going to be at a
doll expo in Tokyo next week.
I have to watch the shop.
That's perfect!
If your mom isn't there,
I can come over.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm outside.
Yeah. Right outside.
It's April, so how come
there is still snow here?
I love how you have so many beautiful dolls in your house.
Siblings are second-degree relatives.
Degree?
Oh, right.
Parents are first, grandparents and siblings are second, right?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
There are some rumors
going around in my new class.
How's your new class?
Are there any cool people?
I dunno.
It's just... kind of a weird class.
Weird?
I don't know how to explain it.
I guess it's cursed, or something?
Cursed?
Well, that's what everyone is saying.
That really is weird.
So there aren't any
cool people in your class...
Should I introduce
you to someone?
What do you mean?
You know. Guys.
You said there aren't any
cool guys in your class.
No, thanks.
You're like an old woman
selling souvenirs.
C'mon, don't say that.
This is my first time down here.
It's pretty cool.
What's this? It's so cute!
That?
Did my aunt make that?
Yeah.
Mei.
Yeah?
I'd like you to
forgive our mother.
You mean my aunt?
Not your aunt.
Your mother.
There's nothing to forgive.
She still thinks of
you as her daughter.
I think she wants to see you.
But she feels bad
because of the adoption.
She hasn't forgiven
herself for giving you away.
She won't admit it,
but I'm sure she's in pain.
So, c'mon.
I don't resent her.
Oh, okay.
Besides, Kirika
feels the same way.
She separated two sisters.
But even more so, she's scared.
Scared?
She's worried that I might
go back to my real mother.
Is that why we're not
allowed to hang out?
I can't blame her.
It's not a good idea for
newcomers to stay down here.
Let's go upstairs.
Wait, what?
The dolls are empty.
Wow! It's so big!
Is it?
My room has four and a
half tatami mats and a futon.
Wow! So cool!
I wish I had a room like this!
Hey, you're not a kid anymore.
Don't start acting so mature!
We're twins; we're the same age.
Except I was born a few
minutes before you, right?
Who knows!
I think whoever's
stronger is the eldest.
What—
Looks like I'm the eldest.
I'll get you back!
Working girls are strong!
So that's how it
looks to other people.
You're a lot more
thin than I thought.
I'm relieved.
I wonder.
Even though I'm thin,
you might not be.
What'd you say?
Gotcha!
Well, haven't you grown?
Hey!
What's wrong?
Ah! It's fr-freezing!
When did you become
such a pervert, Misaki?
How many times do you
think we've bathed together?
I don't really remember our childhood, but maybe two or three times?
I wonder when our first was.
Maybe fifth grade?
That sounds about right.
When granny Amane let it slide.
Actually, I guessed it earlier. We just look too much alike!
Well, you're right.
I'd always thought it was strange.
I don't have any baby pictures.
I figured they wouldn't throw 'em out, so I searched the house for them.
I did find them.
You did?
Yeah.
The pictures from
when we were born.
You and I were lying
side by side on those pictures.
We had the same exact face!
I couldn't help but laugh.
Oh, right.
Let's go to the
amusement park tomorrow.
Which one?
Don't you remember?
The one Mom took us to.
That was ages ago.
I know.
My aunt got really
upset back then.
Yeah, I used to wonder
why she got so upset.
So, you wanna go?
Sure.
Do you have a crush on anyone?
Nope.
What about you?
Yeah, I do.
What's he like?
He's normal.
So he's normal.
Yeah, he's the quiet type.
He likes heavy metal.
So he likes the
same bands as you?
Yeah.
So what made
you fall for him?
I dunno.
There has to be something, right?
Like a moment or something.
I don't remember.
Is that how it is?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah. You called
yourself a working girl earlier.
Do you have a part-time job?
Yeah, at a nearby tofu shop.
Why did you get one?
I don't get enough allowance.
I can't even pay
my cell phone bills.
I need to start
earning my own money.
That's pretty cool.
My dad's birthday
is coming up too.
So...
You're surrounded
by people, aren't you?
She's fast asleep.
Why?
What's wrong?
Oh, just a feeling.
How strange.
I could've sworn
this park was bigger.
Well, we have
grown up, you know.
That's right.
The river of time is cruel.
What's wrong?
I thought you'd bump into him.
That was a close call.
Yay!
It's like you're the eldest today.
It's nice once in a while.
Let me protect you.
Protect? You're exaggerating.
I'm sorry, Mei.
Sorry for what?
I only... you know.
It's not your fault.
It's only because
..my name is Misaki...
You lost your eye because
..of the adoption, you know...
Do you think it's your fault?
Well...
That's a crazy assumption.
I lost my eye because of a sickness,
not because of the adoption or any person.
I don't hold any grudges
to you or my parents.
You know, I used to think about why I had to go through all that,
but in the end, I thought
it would just be the same.
The same?
Yeah.
If you had been put up for
adoption and lost your left eye,
then I would've suffered
just as much as you.
So, it's fine.
I'm sorry, Mei... I'm so sorry...
Hey, isn't that your
house over there?
Maybe.
Yomiyama is so small.
Yeah.
I wonder if I have
to get out of there.
Do you want to live in a city?
No, not like that.
I meant because of school.
School?
I... want to do
something with music.
So, a music school?
Possibly.
That would be nice.
I wish I went on a diet.
You're lighter than me.
I'll save you.
It's fine, Mei.
You'll only fall with me.
No! I'll never let go!
You...
I'm sorry, Mei.
Huh?
Looks like I survived.
Thank goodness.
I'm so happy.
Wow, that was scary.
It basically scared me dumb!
You mean it scared you silly?
You know what I mean.
I used to be scared of this.
Really? I liked them.
You're actually pretty strong.
What do you mean?
Don't you think so?
I guess.
It's over already?
I thought I'd die, but I had fun.
Don't joke about that.
Goodness.
You scared me half to death.
Me too.
I'll see you later.
'kay, see you.
This sucks so much.
You saw what happened at the
amusement park and it wasn't a big deal.
Will you get better?
You look so worried again.
Do you know what
chemotherapy is?
Leukemia can be treated now.
If the medicine doesn't work, I think you can
have a bone marrow transplant. You can use mine.
The doctors said you'd
be the best donor.
Thank you.
Let's hang out
when they release you.
Your birthday's coming up, isn't it?
What do you want?
It'll be your birthday too.
I want you to get
better. How's that?
That's a hard nut to crack.
I want what I saw
there at your place.
You know, that doll.
Okay. I'll see what I can do.
Oh, sorry.
Hey, what's your name?
Mei. Misaki Mei.
iroaseteku firumu no you ni
Just as the colors fade from old film
tashika na ima mo izure kasunde
the things I feel in the present fade from memory sooner or later
nande mo naku waraiatta setsuna no jikan to hikari
as will the short-lived times of happiness and innocence we enjoyed
tsunagatteyuku kioku no soko ni
I believe that the memories we have in common
dareka ga mitsukeru tame aru to shinjiteru
harbor the potential for finding love again deep within
ima demo
Even now I believe that